Chapter 831: Lurk 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At the outskirts of Blackboard Region.

In the wilderness, a crippled, half transparent red-white mech materialized and landed gently on the ground as it flew out from a black electric ball that had momentarily appeared in the sky.

“Hahaha!! I managed to escape! That fucking bitch! Sooner or later I will strip her bare and enjoy myself on a bed!!” the Red-White Mech tumbled a few steps forward before laying on the ground. White smoke was coming out from its body and weird noises were coming out from it as well.

“Where is this?”

The Mech shrunk with the cockpit as the epicenter to the point it became a small white ring. A man in a tight white suit, whose body was smoking, appeared underneath as the ring fell onto his palm.

“The Body is ninety percent damaged… sh*t!!… What a terrifying woman. Even the Absolute Light Curtain wasn’t able to completely block her attack,” the man had white hair and looked rather pale as he gritted his teeth and cursed under his breath.

He raised his head and looked towards the horizon, in the direction of the Blackboard Region.

“I’m close to the target. Unfortunately, my communication device is broken, I wouldn’t be able to know how the others are doing.”

He took out a white small item that resembled a compass and gently pressed on it. Immediately, red blinking dots started appearing on the screen.

“I’m the first one to get close to the target?” Hehehe… There’s still hope!” the man’s eyes glowed.

Howl…

Suddenly a deep roar could be heard from behind.

Behind him, at least ten grey giant wolves that stood at the height of half a man appeared. These wolves growled at him as their eyes glowed green in color. Each and every one of them looked extremely hungry.

“Evolved Creatures?” the man turned around. “Normal class Evolved Creatures dare to approach an elite like me? You’re courting death!”

The Evolved Creatures came about when the humans entered the interplanetary era, and interplanetary interactions caused the virus to spread and mutate from one planet to another. After a long period of time, the powerful Evolved Creatures were born. Most of these creatures maintained their physical features and had their physical attributes boosted tremendously to adapt to the ever harsh environment.

Simply put, they were the latest generation of wild creatures. Although they were stronger than their ancestors, they were still ranked lower on the food chain when faced with humans.

The man gently touched his forehead with his finger and an invisible ripple spread out. As these ripples came in contact with the wolves, tens of these wolves immediately exploded and died.

The impact of a level five Willpower was so powerful that it could easily kill these lower Willpower beasts with a small ripple. This was because their Willpower was much lower, even when compared to a commoner.

“It’s time to infiltrate the region, heh. The Forbidden Core… it’s something that is hindering all the good stuff,” the man stood up and his shirt automatically transformed into an outdoor photographer’s get up. He even had an anesthesia gun on his back for self-defense.

The man adjusted his looks and smiled satisfactorily as he walked directly towards the Blackboard Region. There was a perfect boundary line over there. There were quite wide boundary zones separating the regions. These zones were uninhabitable by humans as most of these places contained high radiation and their environments were very harsh. After all, most of the planets that were populated by humans weren’t a hundred percent livable for humans, and most of these places had their environments altered artificially by atmospheric alteration technology to suit human needs. Even so, there were many places that were dangerous and uninhabitable for humans upon the surface of the planet.

***********

“Life No. 1! Attack!!”

Ugh!!…

Red Moon almost vomited a mouthful of blood as he stared at Clint, who was surrounded by a bunch of stupidly huge Mechs with an awkwardness that couldn’t be described by words. He couldn’t believe that the Mech that he’d assembled with his blood, sweat, and tears had been called Life No. 1!?

He then shifted his attention to the table beside Baylon. The appearance was according to the regulation as it once again turned into a small red pin.

“Why are you naming them so casually..!!?” Red Moon stared at the Black Mech in the garden helplessly. “My order to you is to assemble these mechs as fast as you can. Why are you not increasing your pace!”

Clint changed into a black attire as he walked around the Mech with a stupid smile on his face. “This is a Mech!! Hahahaha! I too have a Mech now!! Hahaha…”

“This… I’ve finished applying the machine oil for you… Lord Red Moon,” Baylon mustered up her courage to speak up softly as she put away the handkerchief that had been used to apply oil onto the pin.

“Okay. It feels good after taking a bath. Put me back into where I fit, quickly,” Red Moon was rather satisfied with her.

“Alright…” after Baylon knew about her transformation and Red Moon’s identity, she was quick to accept reality. Although this person looked weak and fragile, she too had harbored a dream of becoming a pilot for a long time and the people who gave her the opportunity were Red Moon and Clint. She was very grateful to them, so she would do everything to the best of her abilities for them.

“Is there anything else you want me to do, Lord Red Moon?” Baylon asked softly.

“Hmmm, there’s nothing for you to do now. You haven’t slept since you came back yesterday so you should go and have a good rest. Compared to that idiot over there, you sure are quick to accept the truth, and you have a strong mental fortitude as well,” Red Moon admired Baylon.

“Understood. Thank you for your praise, Lord Red Moon…” Baylon felt shy as she lowered her head. “Although I’m useless… I can still do some simple house chores.”

“Alright. Go get some rest and leave the rest to me!” Red Moon urged.

“Okay.”

Baylon stood up with her face red and walked into the house.

The incidents were still replaying endlessly in her mind.

With all of these sudden changes, her tone had started to turn neutral. She had always thought that she wasn’t manly enough and this transformation seemed to have ripened this temperament. Her chest started bulging and underneath her…

Although her brain was filled with a lot of explanations, the training method consisted of its relevant explanation, which was obviously added in by Lord Red Moon. However, Baylon still felt like hiding her figure from the public. After cleaning herself up yesterday, she’d immediately covered herself up from the top down to her leg with a black attire, which was made out of a combination of two black shirts. In addition to that, she’d even used a mask to cover half of her face, revealing only her eyes. To make herself even more hidden, Baylon even wore a pair of huge spectacles to hide her face.

“Pilot…” she sat at the edge of her bed as she clenched her fist silently. “It feels just like a dream… Do I really have the potential to become a pilot?”

She still couldn’t believe it herself.

“Don’t worry. Soon the opportunity will present itself,” Red Moon’s voice had directly pierced through her soul.

“Lord Red Moon…”

Ahhh…!!

Outside, Clint started shouting loudly as if something bad had happened to him.

After the explosion incident, they had crafted a lie that they were caught in the battle between Mechs and fed it to his sister. They had then temporarily settled down in this secluded garden.

The bakery shop owner whom Clint’s sister worked for soon returned back into the city to handle the inquiries, and this morning Red Moon had just realized that the secluded areas were now locked down and no one could go in and out freely. The strange behavior was obvious and it might be because Blackboard Region may have discovered the importance of the ripples that he had spread out. In order to protect himself, Red Moon was on the move once more…

“Quickly set up my Mech! Stop slacking!” Red Moon shouted loudly.

“I understand!!! Ah!” Clint, who was a very careless person, needed to be scolded and supervised daily by Red Moon. If not, he wouldn’t be able to finish his tasks in assembling the Mech in time.

“I’ve exhausted what little amount of energy I have left to disguise the environment for a maximum of twelve hours. If you’re not done within twelve hours, we’re all going to die!” Red Moon scolded angrily.

Inside the house, Baylon lay down and looked at her broken Watch Terminal.

“I wonder if mum and dad are worried… There’s even brother and sister… Perhaps as someone who isn’t that significant, no one would be sad over my disappearance…”

Her family had sacrificed her sister and her future to place all their hopes on her brother Nonosiva as he was admitted into the Blackboard Academy. Everyone hoped that he could turn the family’s condition around for the better. No matter if it was her parents or grandparents, they didn’t really care for her and her sister at all; all they cared about was her elder brother Nono for he had been the favorite son since young.

Baylon was still fine as many of her friends were friendly and comforted her. However, it was a different story for her sister as she had been mixing with others on the streets since young. She had given up on herself and decided to not care for anything as she didn’t have the money to attend school. Technically speaking, she and her sister were on totally different paths.

Inside the garden.

Clint exhaled as he placed the big mechanical piece in his hand into a sunken part.

Suddenly a red line appeared in between them and two parts were immediately pulled together and fit in.

With a mechanical noise, the final part of the Mech had been successfully assembled.

“I’ve already set up the connection installation procedure beforehand so that the assembly wouldn’t be too difficult. The only problem with this is that it would require a considerable amount of strength. You don’t lack the strength but if you were smarter, the assembly would’ve finished a long time ago.”

Red Moon started to complain about him with an unhappy tone.

“Isn’t this finished…” Clint felt helpless.

“Finished my *ss! If it was another person, he would’ve finished two Mechs with the time you’ve taken! You piece of shit. How dare you talk back with such low efficiency!”

“Yes yes, I am a piece of shit…” Clint was already immune to his insults as he talked back while he climbed up the Mech through its knee with some difficulty. With Red Moon’s instructions, he soon finished assembling the cockpit’s entry as well.

Sizzle…

White gas started to spew out slowly from the cockpit as it opened up slowly. Inside, it was completely filled with the smell of chemical and mechanical oil.

“Well, hurry up! Go in there and try it out!”

“Okay…”

As Clint sat inside the cockpit, he felt that he had sat on something sticky and wet. After all, the environment inside was still rather humid.

“Currently, the habitation system isn’t installed in the cockpit. There is no hydraulic suspension, radiation reduction, nothing. This is because I made this Mech from scratch, so other than the control system, every other system is currently down. Those that can still be used have already been taken off since most of their parts were abandoned due to the high repair fee. They’re not functional even though I’ve fixed them.” Red Moon’s voice could be heard from the outside. “Next, you need to try and pour in your Willpower and learn to walk.”

Chapter 832: Lurk 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Understood!” Clint sat in the cockpit as he recalled the few times he saw a Pilot’s behavior inside. He then felt inspired and tried to mimic what he recalled from the movie.

“Life No. 1! Engage!!’

“Engage my ass!! Stop it!!”

Boom!!

The Black Mech immediately fell down in the center of the garden, and dust flew up into the air. The Black Mech looked like an old farmer carrying a huge wok on its back as its arms were dismally crossed over its chest while it toppled facedown onto the ground.

The whole garden shook along with a few of the toys hanging on the wall. Alarms blared and red lights swung about, but fortunately, there were no more movements and the red light started to dim down over time.

“You idiot!! Get your ass up!!” Red Moon’s shouting had Clint trembling from head to toe as he quickly ordered the Mech to stand up.

As long as he had enough Willpower, it would be very easy to make the Mech walk. It was just that he had been too caught up in the moment and the problem had arisen.

“It’s my fault boss! Boss!!” the first thing Clint did was to beg for forgiveness. However, it was too late…

“Ahhh!!!!”

With the terrified cry, even Baylon, who was inside the room, was scared to the point she curled up.

Inside the cockpit, Clint twitched his body to fit in as he sat in a very awkward position.

“Alright, let that be a lesson for you. You know what’ll happen if you fool around with the Mech next time,” Red Moon was angry, but at the same time, he’d calmed down. “Alright, now listen to me.”

“Yes…” Clint was running out of strength.

“This Mech will listen to your orders and it’s named the Life No.1. However, these are not important. What’s important is what I’m going to tell you right now!” it was one of those rare moments where Red Moon spoke seriously.

Clint immediately sat properly and focused. Although he was tortured by Red Moon on a daily basis, he knew that Red Moon really wanted the best for him deep in his heart. Hence he was actually very grateful to Red Moon.

“Firstly, the current Mech you’re driving has no Habitable System, Hydraulic Suspension, nothing. This means that the moment you enter into those harsh environments, you can only rely on your body to stay alive. These include high-pressure environments, vacuum space, and even high inertial momentum. You have to be careful as the moment the Mech enters these harsh environments, your life will be in grave danger.”

Clint listened half-heartedly as he already knew of these troublesome conditions from all the Mech movies he’d watched. However, he didn’t have a general idea how dangerous it really was as his brain was all muddled. However, Red Moon didn’t care what his current state of mind was and continued.

“However, you have your advantages as well, especially the advantage that I’ve given you!”

He paused for a moment, “To others, this Mech is technically garbage, as they may complain that it uses up too much energy for even attempting to pick up a heavy object. However, this Mech is something very useful to you because you’re different from the other Pilots.”

Red Moon’s tone turned more serious over time.

“The Forbidden Mech’s strength comes from its forbidden power source!”

“Its forbidden power source?”

Noting that Clint asking a question, Red Moon held a satisfied expression on his face and continued.

“The Forbidden Mech has all sorts of unique abilities, and my strongest ability is the Memory of War!!”

“Memory of War? What’s that?” Clint’s instincts told him that it was something incredible.

“Memory of War means that you’re able to obtain the other Pilot’s technique and experience if you’ve sat in their Mech before. You would keep absorbing their experiences and attain powerful strength through this. This skill or ability belongs uniquely to me. A powerful ability that only Lord Red Moon possesses!” Red Moon explained proudly.

“Oh~~~!”

“In other words, as long as you have a Mech and enough combat experience with a Mech, you’re able to activate the previous techniques that you used. This is the true strength of the Forbidden Mech and the reason why it’s forbidden!” Red Moon said. “This is also the reason why I wanted you to collect those broken parts.”

**********

“It’s a pleasure meeting you, we’re the Charm mercenary group that you’ve hired.”

Inside a hotel outside the Academy, the moment Garen entered the room, he saw a few beautiful women waving and smiling at him.

Under the soft yellow light, he was in a white suit that he had just changed into. He closed the door and looked at these five young women who were either standing up or sitting down.

Among these girls, the oldest one was not more than thirty and the youngest one was only about fifteen to sixteen years old. Just as what he’d understood from earlier, they were all beautiful and elegant and all of them were in tight black miniskirt uniforms. The moment he opened the door and glanced at them, Garen knew that the golden curly hair girl in the center was the leader.

“Who’s Captain Inari? I came here the moment I finished my class. My schedule is very tight so we need to schedule our time as soon as possible.”Garen didn’t plan to beat around the bush with these girls and went straight to the main point.

“That’s cool. I’m Inari,” as expected, the golden curly hair girl walked forward and replied firmly, giving off a very noble, lady-like vibe.

“Have you received the employment contract?” Garen asked immediately.

“Yes. We do not have any additional requests here,” Inari replied instantly.

“Same goes to me. Let’s sign the agreement then. I’ll give you the money based on the schedule we’ve set earlier, where I will give you the first half and the remaining half after everything is over,” Garen said calmly.

“No problem.”

Inari nodded and both parties pointed their Watch Terminals at each other’s. After a while, a soft ring of confirmation came from their Terminals.

Garen was currently in a very panicked state.

The White Light Terrorist Group was running rampant, causing the Blackboard Region’s security to tighten up considerably. If he were to slack further, he might not be able to reach the edge in such a short time. Hence he had to make a quick decision.

After discussing with Celine, he decided to hire the Charm mercenary group to protect himself as he traveled to the Polar Region to meet the honorable noble.

At the same time, if he were able to sell himself with his profit and obtain a small piece of land, that would be the best course for him.

“I need to head towards the Polar Region and meet a very important person right now. Hence I need you guys to follow me to that region,” Garen went straight to the point.

“What!” “I just arrived and we’re going out again…” “It can’t be~~~”

All of the beautiful women started complaining.

Inari was slightly surprised as well and reassessed Garen once more. Their motive in approaching Nonosiva was just a peak in interest as they wanted to steal his training method back home. However, their actual motive lay elsewhere, and if possible, they wanted to get in contact with the Blackboard Academy’s Blue Narcissus with Nonosiva as the bridge. They wanted to obtain the seed of those talented men and return back to their country.

“It’s fine if you don’t wish to go. I can always hire someone else,” Garen couldn’t care less of what they thought as he had already applied a vacation leave to the academy and Instructor Hamm had already sent it to the academy on his behalf. The notice would be processed in a very short while.

“As the region doesn’t allow non-military civilians to operate a Mech, we are unable to use them and we have sent all the Mechs for maintenance. I’m afraid we may not be able to take them out…” it was obvious that Inari wasn’t willing to leave the place.

“Then I’ll assign you another mission. You guys can protect my family in the dark. My house address is located here up north in the region,” Garen sent his house address to them via his Watch Terminal. Although he knew that they already knew of this due to their prior research, he still had to act it through.

“I’m fine with that,” Charm was hoping that their mission would have some free time in between as well. These women weren’t just a breeding team from Maria, they were also highly ranked intelligence spies in disguise. They would occasionally assassinate a person or two, so it’s normal for them to change up their identities and relax for a bit.

Although Garen didn’t consider up to such an extent, based on his probing, he knew that the opponent had an even more important objective than to steal his technique. Hence he didn’t bother with them. With his vast experience in martial arts, he knew that four out of five of these women were no longer virgins based on their physical structure. Furthermore, they’re all veterans acting pure and innocent.

He wasn’t interested in them at all, as the most important objective to him was to meet the honorable noble. He didn’t want to miss this opportunity Celine had presented to him. If he managed to establish a connection with him, his future development would be much easier.

“Then it shall be arranged so. I hope you guys can do your best,” Garen glanced at them emotionlessly as he felt that they were a bunch of mysterious people.

“Don’t worry about it. Being a bodyguard is a very simple and easy task,” Inari nodded as she smiled.

“I’m glad to hear that. I shall take my leave now,” Garen didn’t hesitate for a moment as he turned around and walked towards the door.

As Garen walked out of the room, a waiter was pushing a dining car across the corridor. As Garen stood by the door as he waited for the dining car to pass through, he was thinking how to shake off the attention from the people paying attention to him so that he could successfully meeting the honorable noble. If Blue Narcissus were to find out that he had given the profit to the honorable noble, it might create some bad reputation. Hence he had to be extremely careful before finishing his objective.

He walked on the thick red carpet towards the elevator. As he pressed the button and waiting for the arrival of the elevator, a fat merchant holding onto two beautiful women walked out of the elevator. The tipsy merchant glanced at Garen and gave him a few more looks the moment he saw the Blackboard Academy’s emblem on his uniform.

Garen walked into the elevator to see two female hotel workers who seemed to have just finished their work whispering to each other at the corner of the elevator. As they saw Garen entering, they stopped talking as they noticed the Blackboard Academy’s emblem.

As the elevator slowly closed its door, out of nowhere.

“Hmm…!?” Garen immediately opened his eyes and saw a white-haired man walking past him on the red carpet through the gap of the door. He had come out from another elevator from the right.

“That man…” he shivered. That man seemed to be as strong as him. His presence was similar to of a monster and extremely powerful. He gave off a vibe that he was like a nuclear bomb that could explode at any given moment.

In that instant, that white-haired man seemed to have felt his gaze as well. He turned around but unfortunately, he was unable to see Garen inside the elevator as the door had completely shut.

“What was that thing? It didn’t feel like a human…” the sensation was indeed very strange. He narrowed his eyes but he didn’t think of it further as his body was very tired. “I should rest first since the target has already reached the city. Hehe… looks like it’s my time to shine.”

Chapter 833: Extraterritorial 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the dark green night.

The ground was full of black spikes protruding from the floor. Some of them were humongous metal plates, some were the battleship’s bow, but most of them were strips of broken alloy steel bars. The entire ground was densely covered with a large jungle, erected with steel trees.

Between various metal trees rising from the ground, there was a small path that was the width of an earthworm, stretching and leading towards the distance.

On a small black road, the white motorcade was moving as slow as a snail, driving along the small and winding path.

Hoot…

The engine sounds of the motorcade were extremely low. The yellow lamp post constantly swept across its surroundings, then penetrated its light through the green mist and into the distance.

The motorcade was formed with four white armored cars. At the back of each car, it was equipped with a thick and solid turret. Furthermore, each car was twenty meters long, six meters tall. When you look up at it, it was like a moving beast. But among these giant steel trees, it suddenly seemed extremely small.

In forth car, the space inside was split into blocks of private rooms. Each private room was in a round ball-like shape occupied with two bunk beds that could accommodate four people.

Garen was placed on the third bed, on one of the top bunk; beside him was the car’s window. His head was inclined slightly to the side while it was covered with the blankets. Looking out of the window, he caught the night scenes that were constantly changing, feeling a sense of novelty.

The large land of metal trees outside looked like real giant trees that had its fangs out, claws spread, and limbs extending, giving people a spooky feeling. Staring out at the window, he could make out the nearby remaining signs of the production trademark on the top that was illuminated by a light beam. Yet, when he looked further beyond the distance, he could see darkness.

Three planets in blue, white, and white were suspended in the sky, taking over half of the sky. However, as they intertwined with the moonlight that was shining down, it formed a mysterious green color through the night sky and fog.

Garen looked at the scenery outside his window and felt slightly depressed.

“Is this your first time away?”

The uncle, who was his roommate on the lower bunk, asked while he had his hand behind his head.

“The scenery out there is the radiation belt between cities. The belt of our Mother Planet Federation is considered minimal. At least it doesn’t affect laypeople’s body functions as long as they don’t stay there for long.”

Garen did not make a sound. He only moved his body.

Though the uncle did not mind, so he continued.

“Out there, it’s like living in the deep ends of an ocean — the cold, deep radiation of the poisonous fog is everywhere. Even plants are killed by the distortion of the radiation. Only a few types of microbe spores are still surviving,” he took out a lighter to light his cigarette up and then took a nice puff.

“I have missed this…”

Garen frowned slightly.

“Is it possible for you not to smoke? I hate the smell of smoke.”

“Really? I apologize. I forgot that young look of yours. Hahaha…” The uncle chuckled as he pressed the cigarette bud into the ashtray that was on his bedside table.

“Can you talk about the radiation belt that is in between the cities?” Garen continued to observe the green environment outside and asked in a low voice. “It is indeed my first time out of the city. Before that, I thought that it would be a very nice natural environment. I did not cross my mind that it would be like this…”

“Is it too miserable?” The uncle laughed again, “Young one, you really are very lucky, to have such a hardworking father who fought hard to build you a solid foundation or maybe it was the luck from your ancestors, that allowed you to successfully become a citizen in the Inter-Region. But a lot of other people do not have that fate.” He paused for a bit, as if he was recalling his memories.

“The rest of the Mother Planet Federation places have not been in contact with each other for over tens of years. I’m not quite sure about their situation but I understand our Mother Planet better. Furthermore, I’ve been traveling around this planet for quite a long time now.”

“Oh? Uncle, why don’t you tell me something?” Garen suddenly showed interest. “How can the Inter-Region be such a desolate scene with no signs of life at all?”

“Not all Inter-Regions are like that. Some places are still normal, filled with nature and even though this is the outer part of the Blackboard Region, it is still pretty normal during the day. It only happens to this part of the Region when night falls — the radiation belt would appear. In this Interstellar Era, it has given humans tremendous scientific and technological advancement. We can now move mountains and sea, there’s nothing we can’t do! Even the sun has succumbed to the feet of humanity. However, with such strong scientific technology, it has brought us the same awful destruction. And that is the side effect of technology that is caused by the radiation belt. Our excessive exploitation of the planet’s resources, over-extraction of heat from the planet’s crust, and excessively drawing and consuming stellar heat energy that can benefit the radiation belt have ruined the planet’s ecological cycle. Without enough radiation from the sun and without enough heat energy from the planet, without taking into account the areas that are within scientific technology, other places have slowly become desolated or strange,” the uncle explained fluently and poured out his emotions.

“So that’s the drawbacks of this Interstellar Era?” Garen could understand it very well.

“Yes. Substance Annihilation Energy is one of the last century’s greatest human invention. But who would’ve thought that was the real root cause to the destruction of the environment? At the cost of destroying substances, a tremendous amount of energy was released. This energy is the most basic force that could construct planetary substances. By constantly stimulating the consumption, in the end, the planet substances’ most basic source is consumed just like the ancient nuclear power research. Everybody was ecstatic when they discovered nuclear power — the same as when they discovered fossil fuel and coal! Since the planet is so big, people think that there must be tons of fossil fuel and coal and they will never be able to use it all. The same logic applies here where people think that there are tons of radioactive substances and since the universe is so big anyway, they definitely would not be able to finish it…”

The uncle nagged incessantly in a low voice.

As he went on, Garen could not hear him clearly anymore. Instead, the two sleeping women opposite from them were snoring louder and louder.

They were two fat women. By the looks of it, it seemed like they were in their thirties or forties. They both wore a gold necklace and they snored repeatedly as they slept on their bed.

Outside the window, the faint engine sound of the motorcade could be heard.

“Kid, after leaving Blackboard Region, where do you plan to go? You look like you’re either from Blackboard Region or a citizen from the Inner Region,” the uncle at the bottom bunk asked softly. “Anyway, since the both of them opposite from us are still here and I can’t sleep, why don’t let’s chat for a bit?”

“I’m going to the Polar Region.” Garen changed into a set of normal clothes when he got onto the car — a black t-shirt and grey long pants. He did not look like he would attract attention. More so, he looked like a young worker from a poor family.

“The standard of living in Polar Region is a little higher than Blackboard Region’s pricing. Even the salary is a little higher. It’ll be much harder working there but at least you’ll get to save some money, so it’s not bad.” The uncle seemed like an expert in this area.

“Is that so? How’s the situation there?” Garen casually asked. He had planned to go there quietly first. Whether it’s after solving the territorial issues or carrying out his own plan within legal parameters, it all had to be extremely concealed. So, in order to get rid of those who were keeping track of his actions behind his back, he took a long time to succeed. However, even then, he did not know whether that would work at all.

“Polar Region is built from an Empire. Different nobility’s territorial has different rules. Since Blackboard Region is an Alliance, the citizens are treated very well and you can definitely find a good living there. Though the quality of education there isn’t the best. So such as you, a citizen from a strong region would be a better talent compared to their own people. There are more positions that you can hold…”

The uncle was talking incessantly again.

Garen answered him from time to time. From Blackboard Region, he took a train to the border of Masiro City, then he took another train to Ice City. Finally, he found the transit motorcade that crosses the border without being noticed and it did not travel on the same tracks as the official motorcade. Garen chose this kind of transit motorcade that seemed like the smuggle people across borders to travel towards the Polar Region.

Only then could he stop and limit his course of action from being known to others.

Yet along this journey, he fully acknowledged the number of people, among the citizens, who practiced Willpower.

Basically, there was one out of ten of them in Blackboard Region. By the borders of Ice City, he could identify one out of twenty or thirty people. The majority of the remaining ones were normal people who did not have Willpower. After all, not everyone liked the fighting lifestyle of a Mech Pilot. A lot of people wanted a balanced and simple life.

However, after they were out of the city, he could barely see people who were Willpower practitioners. One day when he was on the train, he could sense a group of Mercenaries who had a certain level of fighting and shooting skills, but he could not see Willpower among any of them. On this aspect, it was obvious that the Academy’s management of their Training Method was very strict.

When the internet mentioned that there were thousands of Willpower practitioners on this planet, he sometimes doubted how they could calculate that. But when he thought expensive the Training Method was, it suddenly all made sense.

It must be that the Willpower practitioners were all gathered in very few places.

As Garen listened to the uncle’s dull rambling, he slowly slipped into a dream state.

Without knowing how long it had been.

Bang!

A loud, deafening sound suddenly rang out and woke Garen up from his sleep.

He forced his eyes open and his muscles were unusually tensed, prepared to be alert of his surroundings.

“What’s wrong? What happened?”

Travelers from the other rooms were asking as well.

“The sky is not bright yet! What is the problem? Why did the car stop?” Somebody scolded.

The uncle on the lower bunk scratched his head when he woke up. The two fat ladies on the opposite side seemed to have hit their bodies as they sat up crying in pain.

“It’s the Solemn Fire! Tsk tsk, it is beautiful! Quickly, take a picture!” As if the uncle suddenly realized something.

Garen quickly followed his vision and realized it was happening outside the window. Then, he looked out the window.

In the green night scene outside and between countless steel trees, he could see a strip of pale yellow flame burning vertically out of thin air in the distance and floated into mid-air like a pupil dilating vertically in the night. Looking at it carefully, those with good vision could see the flames jumping up and down.

“What is that?” It was the first time Garen saw this scenery.

“That’s called the Solemn Fire, but nobody knows why! Anyway, it is said that some scholars have studied it before. Other than a pile of technical terms, the main effect is to induce the natural phenomena of the poisonous fog from the radiation, similar to the wildfire produced by the phosphorus combustion. Traveling tourists would see it as a sign of safety for the journey. It represents good luck and safe journey.”

Very quickly, or maybe the drivers stopped to take pictures of the Solemn Fire, the motorcade slowly moved forwards once again.

“There were many Solemn Fires here a few years ago. It’s lesser now; it’s quite rare to see it and it feels great,” the uncle crossed his legs.

“Solemn Fire, huh?”

Chapter 834: Extraterritorial 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In his knowledge, there was also a record of this sorts in the Totem World. The features that were recorded were the same, but it wasn’t called Solemn Fire, it was called the Green Crystal Fire. It was an effect of self-ignition caused by a low-ignition mineral deposit of the Green Crystal. These mineral deposits were unusual. Its flames did not ignite on his body. Instead, it ignited by itself when it was ten meters above him.

“If it’s Green Crystal, maybe I can try to make a nutrient solution to improve the cellular quality. If Willpower really comes from the Willpower cells in the whole body, then by directly tackling to strengthen the Region’s cells, it might be able to create a good effect,” Garen’s head scanned through huge amounts of drugs that were in the Totem World. He had learned all of this from the pharmacist that was his subordinate. If there’s a chance, maybe he might give it a try.

After he broke through his Level 1 of Willpower, he started to switch up the new Training Methods he just bought.

‘Galactic Halo — A complex manipulation explosive Training Method. Your Willpower would be able to split into numbers. At the same time, it could subtly manipulate multiple units to attack. The split quantity is determined and divided by level — Level 1, one split; Level 2, two splits; Level 3, three splits. It is suitable for Mech Pilots who are obstructive. Price per level is 260 thousand points.’

Three levels in total would cost more than 800 thousand points. The transaction tax and platform fees would be shockingly high.

Now, he had just started practicing Level 1. The depth of the Galactic Halo had to be much stronger than Blackboard Training Method. Not only on its efficiency, but also a variety of basic knowledge. Regarding the improvement in his future progress, all aspects would go beyond what he has right now.

“The excavation of the nature of Willpower cells — by looking at it this way, there seems to be some research on Totem World’s drugs. Although it is not very developed, when looking at it from another angle of research, it seems very innovate,” Garen pondered carefully. Unknowingly, the sky had brightened up slowly.

Whereas on how to excavate the Willpower of these cells, he felt that these Training Methods of Willpower seemed similar to the birth of the secret weapon. Who knew, maybe he could even use other universes’ space and time, interchangeably.

He got out of bed in the morning and hurriedly ate the breakfast of dry food in which he brought. Holding onto the carton of milk, he went back to his bed to continue with his rest and pondered.

Without noticing, it had started pouring with rain outside and it had soaked through the land of metal trees. As they entered into a huge patch of field, leopards could be seen crossing the field in the far distance, from time to time. Each giant leopard was fifty to sixty meters long, excluding the tail. When they ran, they were heavy and fast. The leopard’s dazzling gold stripes reflected under the sun and gave out a stunning shine.

The passengers in the car each took out their cameras to capture the sight. However, only passengers in the black motorcade had a chance to catch that view. If they were on the standard tracks, only the express train could be taken to travel between countries. It would then take a fixed track and the speed would be extremely fast, so all the scenery would have been hard to catch.

As noon approached, the rain got heavier and heavier. The fields started to become slightly troublesome swamps. The speed of the motorcade started to slow down as well.

During noon, one of the cars fell into a small swamp and could not get out. The motorcade crews had to get down to sort it out. Even a few gunmen walked around the area to chase away the monsters that might appear.

It took them quite a while to pull out the car — it was very tough. By that time, it was already night time and it was obvious that they could not arrive by the estimated timing.

At night, there were people playing with cards in the compartments. They even had a few guards who came in to drink and sing along. The sound was so loud, nobody could sleep.

This lifestyle lasted for the next few days. Finally, by noon of the third day, the motorcade entered the border of Polar Region.

Just as they were about to arrive at the scheduled destination, Cairo Morgan City, he took the chance to escape the Motorcade quietly when he went to pee. Following the route that he had investigated before, he went out alone, towards the destination he had planned.

*******************

Roar!

Thunder and lightning flashed across the sky. For a moment, it illuminated the huge silver city down below.

Beyond the sky, a black single aircraft was spinning a huge propellor and was headed towards this direction at a high speed. An aircraft and a helicopter had similar features, but the difference was in the seat-like thing that was hanging under the propeller, just nice to fit one person.

When Garen sat on the chair, he looked down.

“This is…?” He pulled out the map on his watch and looked. The side of the Terminal was blinking red, the screen was showing a row of words, ‘Warning! The huge source of radiation would affect the terminal signal transmission. Please leave the radiation area immediately.”

Ignoring the warnings, Garen immediately started to download the map

Along the borders and into the Inter-Region, in between Blackboard Region and Polar Region, there were three deserted areas that did not matter. It had no resources, only extremely harmful radiation. When people show up here, even if they were driving a Mech, they would need to increase their energy consumption to resist the power of the radiation source. This would be a dangerous area that is harmful towards the human.

“Mechanical ruins — over here should be the ancient city of mechanical ruins. The place in which I want to go to is the Colorful Lake. So, I will still need to keep walking forward.”

Garen gave a tap on his watch. The top part suddenly revealed his current location. If he walked forward towards the winding road that stretches far, he would only be able to arrive at this destination in other few more hours.

“In total, there are a total of six Colorful Lakes that are nearby. Here, it is one of the safest out of two. The huge radiation area…” Garen extended his hand and pulled out the protective suit on the other hand. Underneath him, he felt a huge radiation energy. It felt just like static energy, where goosebumps rise as if the hairs on his body were all standing.

He checked his Attribute Pane.

“There is no effect. Comparing the radiation to Hellfrost Peacock, this is nasty radiation of the ancestor of all living monsters,” he pulled his zipper with satisfaction.

Overlooking down from the sky, it was a panoramic view of everything underneath.

The silver building, that was like the building block factory, was built one after the other. The neatly slanted metal pillars were lined on both sides of the buildings like spider legs. Though, it looked more like the ends of an electronic component that had been inlaid on the silver ground.

The wind whistled as it passed, suddenly the sound of fine metal clashing sounds was heard.

Garen just flew into the city of ruins. Looking over from his position, he could not see the border completely. The buildings shone brightly as if it was not abandoned at all. No one would be able to make out that this place was the ancient City of Ruins that had been abandoned for more than three thousand years.

As he flew inward, the radiation inside felt stronger. Although Garen was wearing a protective suit, he could feel his hair standing on his whole body.

He let out a slight cold energy radiation that the Hellfrost Peacock had been suppressing. The moment the cold energy radiation was let out, it instantly pushed downwards in a shapeless form to neutralize the radiation.

The air was getting colder. From a temperature of over ten degrees, it quickly dropped down to below zero degrees. However, the strange thing was that not the slightest snow could be seen from the huge city below.

“There isn’t a single breath of life here…” Garen kept looking outwards but his line of vision still could not catch any signs of the city border.

He held on tight to the handle on his right and lifted it up.

Hoot…

The single aircraft suddenly rose up and flew towards a higher altitude.

Beep beep beep…

The square display in front of him showed the altitude of the aircraft: 1124 meters.

“Almost there.”

Garen stopped pulling the handle that raised the aircraft’s altitude. Instead, he looked down again.

On the right side, in front of the Machinery City, a metal cliff extended above a bunch of buildings like the flight deck of an aircraft carrier. A long stretch that led to a sudden huge thing.

An old and shabby black airshift was floating on the deck. The airship had no light, no flame of power. It only floated up and down a little.

“This city is a little strange. With so much metal resources and equipment, someone should come back for some recycling. Why hasn’t anyone come over to use this block of ruins in over three thousand years?

Garen was a little suspicious. For it to have existed for such a long time, it must have had its reasons.

“Enough. The less trouble, the better. My current strength is not strong enough for me to deal with a lot of possible dangers. Let me look for Colorful Lake, and then I can continue this debate.” He suppressed his curiosity. Then, he started maneuvering the aircraft around the center of the city and flew towards the established route.

After more than ten hours of passing through the city of mechanical ruins, Garen finally saw the rolling red mountains in front.

In between the gigantic red mountains, he could make out a giant arc that stood there, from afar.

The height of the stone arc was towering over hundreds of meters. Just like the arch of a tree root, a hollow space was formed from the ground and a piece of dark red disc that was hundreds of meters in diameter floated in the middle of the hollow space.

The dark red disc was densely packed with numerous patterns and symbols. All of them shone with a breathing-like rhythmic light, and they were still turning a little.

“I’m here, the gate of the inter-domain border.”

Garen knew he was almost there when he saw the stone cave.

From afar, the border gate looked like a round-arched door, except that there was no knocker at the center. Instead, a round disc, formed with rays of dark red light was floating in the middle. The round disc wasn’t an entity, but it was a huge pattern intertwined with numerous rays of light.

“From the records, the establishment of the inter-domain border gate on the Mother Planet has at least been five thousand years. It has a long history and the craftsmanship is ancient. Until now, none of the scholars know the purpose and significance of this disc pattern that is formed with rays of light. No matter how they map or experiment, it only shows that this is a simple map that does not involve lights.”

Garen stopped for a while to observe the huge Light-Patterned Disc carefully. Then, he continued to fly towards his destination.

However, he was still within the huge radiation range of the city of machinery ruins. After Garen flew passed the border gate, it had been another ten hours or more. From the night before up to the morning of the second day, he could finally see the edge of the Colorful Lake.

The edge was dark green as if the algae had covered the ground, like a blanket. He was flying above this ground for about a few minutes until a full picture of the lake appeared in front of him.

“This is the legendary Colorful Lake?”

Borrowing the morning sun, Garen looked forwards and he was stunned.

The huge dark green lake sat quietly in the middle of the land, like a big and round green basin that is filled with thick, green lake water.

There were things floating on the surface of the lake. It was either rubbish or it was some floating pale-yellow paste that revealed some soft, pale green plants that were growing out of the water. Looking for afar, these pale green plants were like a pattern that was formed with the natural condensation of the paste in the lake.

Some of it were only half a meter tall, and some others were much taller than that. Some of it looked like some water plant, and some of them looked like a dry small tree, but there were also some that had grown into a plant with big leaves, just like a lotus leaf. All of them floated motionless on the water. The more he looked, the more like looked disgusting and lifeless.

From far away, Garen could already smell the disgusting, and unpleasant smell.

“This is not the fluid of the Peacock’s mucus…” He looked at the lake. He could not even sense a single hint of Peacock mucus from the inside. “This is purely the substances that have been contaminated by the radiation. In this case, if the substances I’ve absorbed from the White Rainbow Stone are from this environment, then my Peacock Technique…”

He suddenly felt a little faint. The closer he got to the lake, the more he felt the suffocating, poisonous gas and the horrible stench of odor.

Chapter 835: Truth 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As the sky darkened and the clouds grew thicker, the previous sunny weather was nowhere to be seen.

Garen floated over the Colorful Lake, slightly nauseated at the disgusting smell and radiation.

As the sound of the wind grew louder, he lowered the aircraft and headed downwards slowly. As he approached the Colorful Lake, the horrible stench bombarded his sense of smell, making his eyes water.

The dark green lake was like a huge pot of gooey paste with some places bubbling non-stop. The bubbles swelled up and became like balloons; they floated up and left the surface of the lake, but they did not fly high before popping, leaving rancid green droplets behind.

Garen gently landed on a blanket of green algae by the lake and raised his hand to look at his protective clothing. The original black protective clothing had become slightly yellow. The huge amount of radiation had suppressed Garen’s cold energy radiation until it had retreated into the protective clothing before it barely managed to go against it.

“The pollution here is too serious…” he looked around and saw no living things or any plants in the surrounding.

“Firstly, I should look for the site where the White Rainbow Stones are,” he slowly walked along the edge of the lake.

Before long, at a place between the lake and the blanket of algae, he could vaguely see colorful stones of different sizes. There were white, red, green, yellow and even more colors.

Garen went forward, picked up a white stone and shook off the lake water on it.

“It does contain the kind of material that the Peacock’s mucus has and it can provide help to my Peacock’s technique to evolve and train… This place is an uncomfortable and disgusting place for others but for me, it’s a blessed land…”

Garen gently pressed on the white stone. Immediately, the white stone looked as though it was weathered away and turned into powder, which was sprinkled down by Garen into the lake. It melted into the lake and there were no signs of it again.

The sky got darker, and there were only a few lights peeking through the thick dark clouds. Without the light, Colorful Lake appeared an even darker shade of green and the bubbles from the lake had lessened, making the lake appear calmer.

“I need to find a good place, a place with more white stones to concentrate on absorbing…”

He squatted down, enduring the stench, and dipped his hand slightly into the green lake.

Hiss…

A trace of white smoke came out from the fingertip of the protective glove and the smell of something burnt wafted in the air.

The stench was just like a toilet after taking a dump, mixed with the smell of burnt plastics; pungent and disgusting.

Garen held his breath. There was a small hole on the fingertip of his protective glove, which had been corroded by the lake water. At the moment the lake water touched the skin on his finger, it was surrounded by a large number of blue threads.

“Devour!” he retracted his finger and the little bit of lake water surrounded by the blue threads immediately drilled back into his skin.

Putong!

Suddenly, Garen heard a loud heartbeat of his own heart.

The lake water that was wrapped up was decomposed into tiny bits of unknown black materials. These black materials were unable to be used by Peacock technique, as the nutrients and energy contained inside were too little and most of it was poisonous toxins. After being swallowed by the blue threads, it was categorized as impurities and was directly transferred to the ‘tumor’ in his chest.

“Lake water that has no worth… It can only be used for Distorted Seed…” Garen frowned and stood up.

Resuming his walk along the edge of the lake, Garen carefully observed the distribution of the white stones.

After more than two hours when the sky was totally dark, he switched on the radioactive light. The green light illuminated the surroundings not far from him.

“Fortunately, the cold energy radiation surrounds my body, or else the radioactive light might get damaged,” Garen held the lantern-like radioactive light and continued his observation on the distribution.

Before he knew it, time flew by quickly.

“Hai!”

Suddenly, a voice came from the sky. It was a voice that belonged to a man.

“This is our turf, stranger!”

Garen looked up and saw that in the distance, a small group of miniature black Mechs was flying towards him. This kind of Mech was only half the size of a normal Mech. Around two meters tall, it looked like a layer of dark metal armor that was wrapped around a person. Rather than a Mech, calling it a metal coat was more fitting.

The number of members of this small group of Mechs totaled to six units. The sound of the engines billowing flames came from their back. The yellow flames that were spat out were very small and inconspicuous in the night sky.

The other party was wearing night goggles which obviously meant that they could still see without light.

“This Colorful Lake belonged to us, Hornet, get out, get the hell out of here!”

“Super-miniature Mechs?” Garen recognized the other party’s equipment. This kind of super-miniature Mech was one of the most popular armed devices for people without Willpower.

A flexible operation, strong defensive ability, adaptability to many kinds of harsh environment and it could also fly freely. With the addition of various weapon systems, it could even threaten ordinary Mech pilots. Generally, three or four units of super-miniature Mechs could threaten regular Mech pilots if they had plenty of weapons. Their defensive abilities were equivalent to one-fifth up to one-third of the normal Mech’s, but they were much more dexterous. It was just that their cost was very high; the price of two units of normal Mech was equivalent to that of one unit of super-miniature Mech…

“Did you hear me?” the Mech at the front shouted loudly after seeing that Garen gave no response.

“Forget it, kill him and throw into the lake and nobody will ever find out. This is the secret location that we found, no outsiders must know about it.”

A Mech behind said in a low voice.

Below, Garen scowled.

In this kind of situation, the other party easily said things that meant to silence him by killing. It was clear that the chaos in this region had slightly exceeded what he imagined.

Before he’d finished gathering his thoughts, Garen saw flames being shot at him from the hand of the Mech in front.

Almost at the same time, he moved to the left. The ground he’d stood on originally was now full of small holes the size of bullets.

“Ordinary guns? They’re still using this outdated primitive weapon,” Garen dodged and looked at his original position.

At the fourth level of the Peacock technique, the overall quality of his body had greatly improved. Although there was still quite some distance to the peak of his strength from before, he had some confidence in dealing with any danger. Coincidently, he also wanted to try out the power when he combined the Peacock technique with martial arts.

“This brat is so slippery!” he heard a shout from a Mech above.

Regardless, Garen lightly jumped and incredibly crossed over four or five meters and landed on a stone beside the lake and stomped.

Peng!!

He jumped to a height of seven or eight meters and in the blink of an eye, he abruptly appeared in front of the Mech which had opened fire.

“Single Whip’s Mark!”

His right hand suddenly swelled up to almost twice its original size in mid-air, and like a black metallic fan, it swung down upon the Mech.

Weng!!

The Mech did not even make a sound nor reaction before it crashed downwards into the lake, creating large waves.

“I never thought that the oriental martial arts absorbed from the previous world to be so useful,” Garen slowly landed, stood at his original position and moved his body.

His actual strength was not as terrifying as what it appeared to be. It was because, as a Mech pilot, he was very clear on the weaknesses that Mechs had. Against the super-miniature Mech coat, he could naturally find the flaws they had and proceed to deal a fatal blow to the thruster. It was not so much that the other party was blown downwards by him, it was more of the other party getting crushed by the immense weight of their Mech coat.

However, the people in the sky above did not know this. All they saw was a guy wearing a common protective clothing jumping and slamming down a Mech.

They did not respond for a long time to what had happened. They just remained afloat in mid-air.

“Henry… Henry was knocked down by that guy with a single blow!” a Mech started to turn around, intending to escape.

“What are you afraid of?! It’s just an accident! Henry’s thruster was suddenly out of flames, I saw it clearly!” the first voice that had suggested killing him suddenly sounded and quickly calmed down his companions.

For a time, the remaining five Mechs began to hover in the air, staring at Garen. Soon, they switched to covert communications and began to fly upwards.

“Kill him!!”

Garen was able to sneak attack a Mech just now, in fact, it was just that the angle had coincidentally been in his favor. Now that the other party had become vigilant, it would be more difficult for him.

He only had a body that was twice as good as the general human body. Against the strength of alloy in this era, he was still powerless and unable to penetrate through it.

Looking at the Mechs that got higher and higher above, Garen did not feel anything. He had fought countless battles in his life. Even now that he had to fight Mechs with his physical body in such a harsh environment, he did not waver.

He had seen too many environments that were much worse than this, this little handicap was nothing.

“Except, how do I get rid of the rest of them…?” just as this thought flashed through his mind, he saw bursts of fire and the sky was filled with bullets raining down on him. A large barrage of bullets flew downwards, forcing him to move around quickly to avoid them.

Some of the large stones on the ground were riddled with bullets until countless holes were seen, and the blanket of algae on the ground had been shot into pulp. Clouds of dust-like green gas billowed up.

In the midst of his rapid movements, Garen picked up a few blocks of stones and used them as hidden weapons to fling mercilessly at the Mechs in the sky.

The man who had been hit only shook a few times before continuing to attack without any effect whatsoever.

“Such a tough alloy!” Garen realized, it was unlike the era of Secret Techniques, where a wall that was more than ten centimeters would be directly smashed. Even if it was that tough metallic armor, the shock produced by the high speed would make the pilot inside feel terrible.

But now, it seemed that the Mechs had pretty good shock absorber devices.

“Using the physical body to go against the Mechs, even the most fragile super-miniature Mechs, is so difficult…what a hassle,” Garen moved quickly, picking up a dark green branch by the lake and dipping into the lake.

“Let’s see what this can do.”

He jumped to the left side and borrowed the force from a green tree by the lake to fling the branch in his hand after a backward flip.

The branch flew directly towards the Mech giving out the commands in the sky. The end that was dipped into the lake hit the right side of the head of the Mech.

Pa!

With a crisp sound, the lake water from the branch splashed on the head of the machine.

“Ah!!!” he screamed and fell straight down, and no more sound was heard from him.

The remaining four Mechs were dumbfounded. For a moment, the sound of gunfire stopped.

Pa Pa Pa!

Three more branches covered with lake water was shot up and hit the same places on the Mechs.

The three Mechs also let out screams before falling downwards.

The last Mech was trembling and the gun in its hand was almost dropped. It remained suspended in mid-air, afraid of making any movements.

Chapter 836: Truth 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Beneath, Garen was gasping for breath. It was easy for him to throw out so many branches, but for all of them to accurately hit the tiny opening in the air filtration system, it was a demanding yet delicate task which exhausted most of his concentration. It was partly because he also had to pay attention to avoid the rain of bullets while being careful of where he stepped on in his high-speed movements all around the place.

“Luckily, I’m familiar with the super-miniature Mech since the content of my classes included information about it, or else I really wouldn’t know how to deal with such a troublesome turtle shell. I can’t penetrate it and the impact would be dealt with by the shock absorber device…”

He walked to the side of the only Mech that had not fallen into the lake and gave it a kick. There was no response.

“You, come down.”

He looked up at the last Mech and said.

That guy gave a shudder and obediently flew down in front of Garen. He quickly threw away the gun in his hand and raise his hands in submission.

“Take off the Mech coat on this guy,” Garen ordered.

“Ye… Yes!”

The last person managed to give a reply while being scared stiff and immediately started to skillfully strip the Mech coat off the person on the ground.

Garen stood watching at the side and casually asked a few questions.

“Just now, I heard that you guys called yourselves Hornets and that this is your turf?”

After sensing that Garen did not have the intention to kill him, this person began to relax for a bit.

“Yes Boss, we, the Hornets are the owners of this site. We owned all the resources like the Rainbow stones and Black sands.”

“How many people are there in the Hornets? With Mechs like you guys,” Garen asked while observing his actions.

“Around twenty. We are the fifth team and the larger team among the two small teams, and there is only one boss,” that person put the Mech coat beside Garen.

The one who had been wearing the Mech coat was a dark-skinned middle-aged woman who lay senseless. When she came into contact with the air, with a slight twitch, her body began to rot and melt like a burning candle. Starting from her skin, she began to melt into a puddle of dark green liquid that flowed towards the Colorful Lake.

Garen already knew that this person had died a while ago. From the moment the lake water entered the air filtration system, both layers of air filtration devices were corroded and the air within had instantly turned poisonous and disgusting. With these people’s physiques, they naturally could not stand it for even half a second and were immediately poisoned to death.

“This is your Mech coat…” this person stood at a side with a somewhat subservient attitude and placed the Mech coat in front of Garen.

“Are there any other forces around here? You guys have been living in this place?” Garen asked in a low voice.

“Yes, we are radioactive people whose bodies were contaminated in some parts and have a certain degree of toxicity. We were not allowed to live in any regions except for certain areas that were designated,” that person answered hastily. “You are not a radioactive person, so why would you come here? Generally, the regular people are not willing to contact us, even for a little bit.”

“Why?” Garen picked up the Mech coat and examined it.

“Because the radiation in radioactive people is contagious. This is a disease that has no cure. A slight inattention and the natural people would get infected as well. All the natural people that are infected will be expelled from the region and then they can join the radioactive people,” this person explained in a small voice. “We have no way to live, so we can only hoard the small bit of resources left in between the regions, collect them and exchange them with the natural people’s government and merchants for necessities. Food and drinks, things needed in our homes and also water that has no contamination, everything we need.”

“Doesn’t it rain often?” Garen furrowed his brows. From this person’s words, he seemed to have touched on a side that was not exposed in this world.

“That’s right, but the pollution on the planet is so serious that even the rain is polluted and poisonous. Without a good filtration system, the water cannot be drunk in any way. Those who drink them will get sick and die off quickly. The natural people’s government does not care about us. No medicine, no medical facilities, and even clean water requires for us to trade our lives for it!” when talking about the tragedy of the radiation, this person seemed to have forgotten his fear earlier and spoke with resentment. His tone was full of envy of the natural people and hatred for the government.

“Natural people…radioactive people…” Garen had never noticed any information about this on the Web. It had obviously been censored by the government so that the natural people would not know anything about this dark side of them.

“Are there a lot of radioactive people?” he continued asking.

“A lot,” this person answered in a low voice.

“What’s your name?” Garen looked at the man carefully.

“I am called Mondeo, sir,” this guy took out a small thing from his waist and handed it over. “Sir, this is a map of the Hornets’ turf.”

Garen took Mondeo’s map and lightly pressed the button on this little device.

With a beep, a red light shot out from a small hole in front of this little thing and projected directly a crude map on the ground. The names on top of it were written badly.

The Blackboard region and Polar Region were among them.

The thing that surprised Garen the most was that as compared to other territories, the two regions were like two sesame seeds on top of layered flatbread [1] and completely inconspicuous.

He took a deep breath before he moved his finger to other vast territories outside the regions.

“These territories are all under the influence of radiation?!”

That’s right, sir!” Mondeo nodded. “The natural people’s regions are only small areas that radioactive people yearn for. There is no need to worry about the food we eat and the clothes we wear. There’s no need to worry about fighting with dangerous mutated life forms and no need to rob territory and food by killing people. A place where every radioactive people aspires to live in. Some people have calculated that even if there were radioactive people dying every day, our number will still be more than ten times that of the natural people. And with the pollution getting worse, every day, there will be natural people being driven out for various reasons to become radioactive people.”

At this moment, Garen truly understood the extent to which the Mother Planet Federation had decayed.

Radioactive people… this huge group of people was completely covered up by the government. The region had even established a perfect blockade system so that the people could continue to live on in ignorance.

“Has there been any radioactive people that have entered the region?” Garen asked.

“Not that I have heard of,” Mondeo shook his head. “But sir, you must be a natural person, right? If you have a Watch Terminal, then after coming to the radiation belt, you will need to go through radiation checkup. There may also be a memory sweep.”

“Radiation checkup? Memory sweep…?” Garen knew what these two meant, especially the checkup for radiation. The Cold radiation in his body must not be detected. And the memory sweep… This technology was used to enter the memory and let other people take a look layer by layer and make changes to them!

The natural people did not know the details, thinking that only the recent part of the memory would be eliminated, but as a student in Blackboard Academy, Garen knew better. This technology was a method that completely discarded human rights laws!

For a time, his face under the protective clothing turned gloomy.

“Once the fact that you have been to the radiation belt is identified, you will be ordered to go through a memory sweep, which is the rule,” Mondeo continued. “Rumor has it that there was once a region’s big shot’s nephew who came out to the radiation belt, and when he went back, he was still ordered to go through the memory sweep. Although the big shot was furious, he could not do anything about it and a lot of his family’s secrets were leaked out.”

“Is there a lot of this radiation belt between the domains? Does it only exist in between the Polar Region and Blackboard Region?”

Garen pondered for a bit and asked again.

“No, it’s like this everywhere. Our team has one that came from another radiation belt. Every region separates the area where they conduct their activities, and outside their activity area is entirely radiation belt. No natural person is willing to approach the radiation belt because they may never be able to go back,” Mondeo sighed.

Garen carefully sorted out all the relevant information he had received in the past.

Mother Planet’s huge environment and their borders rearranged themselves in his mind.

On the huge blue planet, on the pieces of continents, the regions were like gems dotted in the earth, small and precious, while outside, the periphery was all the radiation belt that was caused by pollution from the technology era.

The Academies Union was the most powerful force; they controlled everything, maintained order and blocked everything from the outside, but there was also a civil war raging inside. They should be the mastermind that sustained the current relationship between the natural people and the radioactive people.

“Alright let’s stop talking about all these,” Garen diverted the conversation. “How many Colorful Lakes are here?”

“Colorful Lake… there’s only one that has reached this Flaming light level. We have to send people to patrol every day and it’s our team’s turn today,” Mondeo quickly answered. He guessed that Garen should be a natural person that had been expelled today and did not know the importance of resources.

“Sir, if it’s necessary, you’d better collect some Rainbow stones as resources to exchange for food and water. Food and water are very precious in the radiation belt.”

“Thanks for the reminder,” Garen nodded. The Rainbow stones were common items inside the region, and he would have never thought that in the radiation belt, it had become one of the precious and important resources needed for survival. If he had not come out, he would have never have known that the Mother Planet was in such a bad state.

“Aside from the billions of people on Mother Planet, how many people are living in the radiation belt? This number is a big unknown…” he pondered with a heavy heart.

“Alright, you can go now,” Garen waved his hand, indicating that Mondeo could leave now. This guy was quite smart. In the beginning, he was still so scared that he wanted to escape but now he was very cooperative with no indication of doing anything else.

Mondeo looked as though he was granted amnesty and quickly ran far away. After some distance, he turned to look back and saw that Garen did not have any intention to kill him. Only then did he fly up and rush away.

Garen watched until he was completely out of sight before picking up a piece of the Mech parts on the ground.

“An outdated technology… It’s an equipment with materials from at least fifty or sixty years ago.” he touched the production label on one of the parts: Polar ——13329760.

Looking back at the Colorful Lake, so far, he had only found small white stones which could not even compare to the batches that other people had brought over for him to absorb.

He had understood completely now. The white stones he had absorbed previously must have been accumulated by a lot of radioactive people.

“This is far less efficient than getting accumulated and absorbed all at once. Forget it, it’s better to go back. Luckily, the Watch Terminal was frozen by my Cold Energy radiation and its functions were suspended.”

He looked around and his gaze settled on the large Colorful Lake.

“But, since I have come, I can’t just go back empty-handed. This Colorful Lake…”

TL note:

[1] Raws stated Shaobing (烧饼), translated to layered flatbread.

Chapter 837: Absorption 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Pu!

The sound of bubbling water filled his surroundings.

His vision was a field of dark green and nothing else. His whole body exuded a strong Cold Energy radiation which resisted the highly poisonous water that was constantly trying to attack the surface of his skin. He held his breath and continued swimming down.

The lake water was very viscous. Without using any special skills, he could not even begin diving. Garen had even hung a big stone from his body to help get himself downwards.

Not long after he’d dived in, his arms seemed to have touched something hard. It seemed to be moveable.

“What’s that?”

Garen pulled it over and suddenly a pale face appeared in front of him. The face belonged to a female corpse and one of her arms had been grabbed by Garen.

The female corpse’s eyes were wide open, though her eyeballs were waterlogged to the extent they were green and black. Her clothes had been corroded and destroyed and most of her body was covered in rotting holes.

Throwing it aside, Garen continued to dive quietly while remaining vigilant at all times.

Gu lu…

A few bubbles floated upwards. The deeper he went, the clearer the water got; from dark green, it gradually turned to a shade of pale green similar to fresh water.

Garen could hold his breath for half an hour without any problems. The constitution of his body had become something that far exceeded normal humans after the transformation by the Hellfrost Peacock Technique. It was becoming the basic larva of the gigantic universe creature, the Hellfrost Peacock. After the foundations, he would completely become the basic larva. In his current state, the radiation which was deadly to normal people would not affect him as long as the Cold Energy around him did not disappear.

Hua…

Suddenly, Garen seemed to have heard a sound from his right. He looked over through his protective goggles but he could not see anything at all aside from the water’s green tint.

Then, finger-long black worms appeared around him in the lake water. They were just like caterpillars with their whole body ensconced in a black and shiny black shell. They moved their body segment by segment and crept towards Garen from all over the place.

Garen was surprised and hurriedly increased the Cold Energy, enlarging the perimeter until it reached a meter away from him.

Soon, the first caterpillar entered the range of the Cold Energy. It quickly turned into an ice stick and sank downwards. The second one also entered into the range and frozen into ice. The same went for the third and the fourth… until the twenty-fifth one.

Only then did Garen sigh in relief. In order to kill these worms, he had consumed at least half of his Cold Energy.

He swam for a bit while looking around, but he did not see any more of these caterpillars.

He began to consider if he should continue diving down…

“With my capabilities, if I continue diving down, the pressure may shorten my diving time, it’d be better if I have diving equipment on.”

He stretched out his hand and stirred the lake water. After brushing away some muddy sediments, he could faintly see some things a few meters away.

He seemed to have seen a dark shadow swimming towards him.

“What is that?”

The dark shadow swam nearer and nearer…

Soon, it entered the Garen’s visual range.

It was a black water snake. The length of its body was around ten meters, but only had the thickness of an arm. It had teeth that were similar to those of cutlassfish and its eyes glow green in the lake.

Garen was not surprised but he was a little happy; this guy was obviously a beast that lived in this water.

He reached out his hand towards the head of the snake and a faint fluctuation spread out.

A look of awe and delight flashed in the eyes of the snake, showing its extraordinary intelligence. It let Garen stroke its head and gently wrapped its body around Garen, forming a circle.

“Bring me to a place that has a lot of this thing…” Garen took out a fist-sized white stone from the pocket of his protective clothing, shaking it at the snake.

His eyes flashed with a faint trace of gold color from the Ancient Nine-Headed Dragon, it was purely a wave that was used for communication. After passing the message to the snake using the way of the Totem World, he was still not sure whether it could understand him and could only keep a close eye on this guy.

The water snake’s eyes revealed doubts at this but it bit the white stone and turned around, swimming downwards towards the left.

Garen hurriedly grabbed onto its tail and his body was brought downwards at a high speed.

The flow of water on both his sides rushed around in a fast manner. The snake’s body simply flowed freely and it was ten times faster than him. After half a minute, there was a dark cliff wall that was full of caves of different sizes like a honeycomb.

The water snake led Garen into a large cave and drilled inside for several minutes. In the middle of it, he encountered a lot of those black worms again. They had grouped together and seemed to be eating something.

The water snake seemed to be wary of the worms and the worms also took the initiative to avoid the water snake. Both groups did not encroach upon each other and only passed by.

Garen, who was still holding onto the tail of the water snake, also felt his scalp tingling. He had killed off more than twenty of them just now using half of his Cold Energy. Now there were even more of them here, at least thousands of them. If they fought under such circumstances, then the chances of him dying would be very high.

Fortunately, the Will of the spirit of the Ancient Nine-Headed Dragon allowed him to be closer to the water snakes and avoid being entangled by these worms.

Glancing back at the thing that was being eaten by the swarm of worms, it was a piece of broken metal alloy. The worms’ sharp teeth constantly tore away at the piece of metal, making cracking sounds.

Passing by the swarm of worms, the water snake began to go up along the tunnel of the cave swiftly.

After some time, around ten minutes to twenty minutes, there was a sloshing sound of water above him.

Garen suddenly felt that he had broken through the surface of the water. He had been brought by the water snake into a somewhat warm cave.

He took a deep breath. The air outside was quickly filtered through the air filtration system in his protective clothing and was replaced by air that was safe to breathe. After that, he began to take a look around his surroundings.

The cave was not big; it was only about the size of a small living room.

However, Garen’s eyes suddenly opened wide with traces of joy.

All around the walls of the cave, including the ground, was paved in white. Surprisingly, it was all large chunks of White Peacock Stone!!

The whole cave was made up of the White Peacock Stone!

“This is the mine for the White Peacock Stone!”

Garen patted the water snake’s head to express his satisfaction.

The snake gave a hissing sound that displayed its happiness. It then turned around in circles before spitting out the White Peacock Stone in its mouth.

“Go ahead, go and take a good rest.”

Garen let go of the water snake and began to explore the structure of the cave carefully. Walking up to the wall, he pressed a button on the collar of the protective clothing.

‘Recording the route taken…’ a line of words appeared on Garen’s goggles.

The route that was taken to come here was quickly recorded down by the chip in the protective clothing.

Sorting out the route, Garen pondered for a bit before going to the wall on the right side, where he removed his protective clothing and exposed his hand directly to the air.

He no longer suppressed the natural release of the Cold Energy radiation and pressed his palm to the wall.

Hiss… Peng!

After the hissing sound, white smoke came out from between his palm and the wall.

A large number of blue threads came out from Garen’s palm and drilled into the stone wall as though they were greedy parasites, absorbing the matter in the White Peacock Stone.

The stone wall soon broke down into powder. As though it was contagious, the area that broke down from the contact with Garen’s palm soon spread out. Less than half a minute later, the stone wall around the cave began to shake slightly. All the White Peacock stone began to break down into a large amount of powder and fell down.

Garen stood in front of the wall with his eyes closed, his body produced some creaking sounds and blue scales started appearing on the surface of his body. His face, body, arms, ears, the skin all over him was covered with scales similar to those of snakes. The protective clothing was gradually filled with a disgusting smell, which was becoming more and more unpleasant.

Opening his eyes, Garen saw the changes on his body.

“The closer you get to the Fifth level, the more the body becomes inhuman…”

Looking at the progress on his Attribute Panel, the completion of the Fifth level had already reached 42% and it was still rapidly increasing.

“As long as I reach the Basic level, there should be a very high qualitative change which should not disappoint me,” Garen recalled the record of the Living Secret Technique and closed his eyes again to absorb the essence of the White Peacock Stone.

His body began to change more and more. his arms began to grow out some sharp points, and on his back, dark blue filaments that were as dense as grass was beginning to grow out; it was similar to hair, but it could easily move around.

The biggest change was his body size and his height began to grow from the original 1.78 meter until it was almost 2 meters. His body’s muscles became more distinct and the scales on his skin became more obvious. He looked like a warrior that was wearing an armor made of snake scales.

Time passed by, as Garen gradually became immersed in the thrill of getting stronger.

******************

Beside the Colorful Lake

The sky gradually turned bright and in the distance, there were more than ten black Mech coats. This group of people was all in the same super-miniature Mechs just like the previous group of Hornets.

This group of Mechs landed and started searching around the lake.

“Boss! I found one aircraft for single use, the model is very new! It should be something that those natural people brought out!”

One of the Mech coats found the single aircraft that was left behind by Garen.

Hearing of the clues, the tallest among the group flew over and landed in front of the aircraft and knocked on the aircraft’s propeller.

“It must be that natural person. Since it was casually put here, then it’s either that he threw it aside or he couldn’t take it away,” his voice was rough but his words revealed his attentiveness.

There was a slight commotion. There seemed to be some people who did not understand the meaning of these words.

“Boss means that this person either left this thing alone or there was an accident and he couldn’t come back temporarily,” a female voice explained on one side.

“Mondeo, are you sure that that natural person killed off your team without wearing any Mech!?” Boss turned around and asked the Mech coat at the very back.

“Yes, absolutely. If it was not for my wits or the fact that he wanted to leave someone alive to ask for information, I’m afraid I won’t be alive and standing here!” Mondeo quickly answered.

The Boss went silent for a while and saw that the group of Mech users was waiting for him to make a decision.

A natural person, a powerful one that appeared abruptly in this place with the ability to quickly kill off five Mech coats was likely to be able to kill off this group of ten Mech coats.

“Do not provoke him, this person is very strong. Maybe it’s an expert that was sent out by those big shots in the region to carry out a task. Even if he’s not, he alone is not someone we can deal with.”

“Those five Mech coats were found, Boss. Why not just retreat first?” someone suggested.

“Retreat, leave this area alone for a while. Do not come here until after that man leaves,” the Boss took the suggestion without being embarrassed about it. In the radiation belt, the strong ruled. Avoidance and escape were not shameful.

The group of people brought the Mech coats and quickly left. Mondeo finally fell in at the end of the line and looked back at the Colorful Lake.

“Natural person…” a trace of longing flashed through his eyes.

Chapter 838: Absorption 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Hua…

The cave that Garen was in had its size increased from the original 10 meters’ width to 20 meters.

The White Peacock Stone that formed the wall had also begun to turn yellowish; apparently, its purity was decreasing. The ground had now accumulated a thick layer of fine white powder.

The water snake had been hiding in the lake, circling around while waiting for Garen. Its pair of green eyes stared at Garen’s location with curiosity and awe.

Cough cough…

After a few coughs, a figure walked out from amidst the white powder. It was Garen who was wearing his black protective clothing.

The surface of his protective clothing was covered in white powder and his body had returned to its original state without any abnormalities.

“There’s nothing left to absorb… The quantity this time is very good. But compared to the accumulation that was transported for me to absorb previously, the efficiency is not much higher. The stones that were collected by them were all high purity stones and their quantity was also significant. The absorption from that time was equivalent to a third of what I absorbed here.”

Garen brushed away the powder on his body and compared the harvest this time.

“Even so, the advantage of coming out is that I can freely do the absorption. As long as I find the place, I can absorb straight away without any repercussions.”

Looking at his Attribute Panel, the progress of the Fifth level had increased again.

‘Secret Technique — Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Living Secret Technique, Fourth Level, Fifth Level completion rate: 72%.’

“If I could find such a place again, I should be able to completely break through to the Fifth level,” Garen was in a great mood.

Looking around at the powder on the ground, it was all high-energy fuel powder. Although it was not purified and there were a lot of impurities, it could still be used.

Garen stretched out his hand and blue threads came out.

“Devour!”

The skill was activated fully and the places where the threads made contact, all of the white powder there disappeared soundlessly.

At the same time, Garen felt that the Distorted Seed in his chest was growing heavier and larger.

A few minutes later, the entire layer of white powder, which had been more than a meter thick, was completely absorbed into Garen’s body.

He already had a bulge on his chest.

Rip!!

After a ripping sound, a hole appeared at the bulge on his chest. Garen quickly pulled down the zipper on the protective clothing. With a sticky sound from the hole, a ball of flesh was squeezed out.

The hole in the chest quickly closed up and recovered.

Garen pressed on the wound. There was not a single hint of pain.

“It was as I thought, this Living Secret Technique is a path of evolution, and the more I move forward, the less human I become,” he murmured while looking at the lump of flesh in his hand.

“This is the Distorted Seed?”

The meat ball was the size of a rugby ball. Its surface was smooth but covered with the white and red muscles that branched all over like a web.

“What’s the use of this thing?” Garen did not find a way to use it with the Living Secret Technique. He gently threw it away and took a few steps back.

The Distorted Seed fell on the floor and squirmed for a bit.

Peng!!

A violent explosion occurred and a large amount of blood and transparent liquid burst out, affecting a wide area which was more than half of the cave. All the places that were affected were all covered in a thick layer of blue frost.

“What is this? A portable bomb?” Garen shook his head. “Completely useless. If it was in the ancient times, the power is certainly strong, but in this age of technology, the power is too small, the area it covers is also small and the way to manufacture it is also inconvenient. As expected, the Distorted Seed was a liability.”

Garen looked at the water snake in the lake, where it was trying to shrink itself. It seemed to fear the ice that had been produced from the explosion.

“Come here,” Garen beckoned it over.

The water snake sprang out of the lake’s surface and slithered to the Garen’s side while hissing.

“Bring me to another place that’s like this.”

Without any hesitation, the water snake motioned for Garen to grab on to its tail, turned around and slid back towards the lake.

This time, the water snake took only a few minutes before finding a similar cave.

Garen spent another half an hour absorbing the essence of the cave. The completion of the Fifth Level reached 92%. Then, the third time…

Repeating this over and over, Garen did not know how many times he had let the water snake take him to find the White Peacock Stones. Sometimes it was in caves and sometimes it was at the bottom of the lake, but there was never a time that he returned empty-handed. A large amount of powder was swallowed up by him to form Distorted Seeds that were left at each location.

In this manner, he stayed at the Colorful Lake for two days until the agreed time to leave the border. Garen was reluctant to leave the Colorful Lake. After checking the aircraft, he flew towards the direction where he came from. At the same time, all the Distorted Seeds that he had deposited were all detonated at the same time, forming an ice cold zone at the bottom of the lake. This was to eliminate any potential danger that could come out of others discovering a large amount of highly explosive powder.

That water snake was given a name, Black Line. At the time when Garen was leaving, it circled around Garen many times to display its reluctance. This snake was considered to have quite a high intelligence similar to trained dogs. Now it had some kind of attachment to Garen. After swimming for a long time on the surface of the lake, it slowly dove down. Before Garen left, he had fed it a little bit of his blood as repayment for its help during these last few days. That drop of blood contained the transformation power of the Hellfrost Peacock, but he did not know whether the water snake could absorb it.

********************

The border of the Polar Region

In the red glow of the evening sky, there were milky, translucent circles fluttering about. They looked like smoke rings in the yellowish red sky tinted with light green, similar to someone using a paintbrush to leave traces in the sky.

The land was formed of smooth plains and rolling hills. There was a meandering green river flowing between the hills, like a light green silk belt that grew out of the earth, flat yet reflective of the luster of the sky.

At a place at the riverbank, a single black aircraft landed unsteadily. A man covered in black protective clothing was pouring water over his body in the river, washing away the large amounts of radiation residue and dirt off the protective clothing. It was Garen, who had just come from the direction of the Colorful Lake.

Beep beep beep…

The beeping sound came from the aircraft.

Garen turned around to look at it and then as though he had heard something, he looked up at the sky.

A huge black and gray disk slowly came out from the sky above him. Its body was flashing with black lightning, which was the residual energy from space jumping.

The flying disk was hundreds of meters in diameter and covered in serrated folds. A few white electric lights were flashing and a ring that looked like a suction cup hung below it.

The flying saucer flew to the top of Garen before the ring underneath it turned and slowly opened in the middle, revealing another circular plate within.

Garen pressed on the Watch Terminal within his protective clothing, sending out a message that could be received in an open channel.

Shua…

The second layer of the flying saucer slowly opened and an invisible gravitational attraction was cast over Garen.

Zap!

The black lightning flashed and then Garen turned into a ball of black lightning that shot towards the bottom of the flying saucer.

The two layers quickly closed up and the flying saucer slowly continued to fly into the distance.

Only the aircraft was left behind on the ground beside the river.

*************

“Welcome, guest from Blackboard Region.”

In the dark, Garen heard a pleasant voice ringing in his ears.

He opened his eyes and before him was a big dark blue hall.

The smooth ground looked as though it was made from a translucent material similar to a sapphire crystal, and it clearly reflected his own image.

His surroundings were empty and on top was an image of the huge ring pattern of the flying saucer, though the ceiling was a silvery white color. The entire hall was circular in shape and surrounded by circular windows, through which the sights of the beautiful Polar Region could be seen.

The evening hue of the sky dyed the earth red and the aurora circles in the sky continued moving about as though they were alive.

With a glance, he could see the landscape far away.

However, all of these did not appeal to Garen. What attracted his attention the most was the three one-meter wide silver metal balls that were floating not far away from him.

The three metal balls were arranged in an equilateral triangle and they were constantly floating up and down while slightly rotating.

“Are you Your Highness Mingway?”

Garen looked around but no one was visible around him.

“Yes, I am Mingway. Since you’re Celine’s friend, then you wouldn’t find me for no reason. Say it, what is it that requires me to use a flying saucer to get you?”

The voice said calmly.

“I have a business here, but unfortunately, I cannot support it alone. I need to find a powerful collaborator, so Celine recommended you,” Garen carefully picked his words. “High-energy fuel powder, have you ever heard of this thing?”

“Fuel powder? There are more than ten kinds of High-energy fuel powder businesses in my hands, which one are you talking about?” that voice seemed to be a little interested and asked carefully.

“It’s the powder that is extracted from Rainbow stones,” Garen reminded. Looking at this flying saucer, he knew that this Honorable Noble called Mingway had a high status and was rich to a certain extent.

“Oh, it’s that one… what about the profit margin?”

The middle silver metal ball among the three slowly stopped rotating and the features of a male face slowly appeared on its surface.

The face slowly opened its eyes. They were pitch black and the face silently stared at Garen below.

“I’m different from that Celine; although I also like martial arts, since someone had sent money to me, I will naturally accept.”

Garen’s expression remained unchanged.

“There may be earnings of up to ten millions of Units per month.”

The face then pondered.

“Okay, I accept this splitting. Say it, what kind of help do you need? This is not a small amount, what is it do you want to exchange?”

Before Garen came here, he had already thought it over. Wanting a territory was not realistic, especially after he had gone to the radiation belt’s Colorful Lake, found the White Peacock stones mine and gauged the absorption’s efficiency. He might have a significant increase in a short period of time, but this progress could not be relied upon for long-term improvements. It was better to let others help him collect them. The efficiency of the absorption was still not very good.

Therefore, this territory plan was not that useful. In that case, the deal this time should include diverting attention and greedy people away from himself and also exchanging for some things that were hard to get…like training methods.

“I want Level Four and Level Five of the training method Galaxy Glow.”

Garen thought for a bit before conveying his first intention.

Chapter 839: Mingway 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Galaxy Glow?” Mingway pondered. A moment later, he slowly answered, “I’m sorry, I can’t promise you this. I do have the follow-up of the Galaxy Glow training methods but I don’t have the qualification to sell it. The right belongs to the Academies Union.”

“Not qualified?” Garen’s heart sank. If even the Honorable Noble was not qualified, then perhaps the only chance he had was with the Academies Union.

“The follow-up training methods of Galaxy Glow are very precious. It is not something that you can buy with money alone. If you need other training methods, then I can give you a full set. With the profit that you provided this time, I can offer you a full set of Level Five training methods. How about it?” Mingway tempted him.

“Level Five…quite low…” Garen shook his head although he did need a training method to outline the path that he could take.

If the Living Secret Technique could forcefully increase Willpower as a power source that could be manipulated, then training methods could draw out his direction and the way forward. Without it, he could not forcefully continue to upgrade the Level of his Willpower.

Originally, when he had come to this world, he had intended to mainly absorb and use the world’s local power system while using his own martial arts as a supplement.

“Quite low? Hehe…” Mingway could not help but laugh. The little guy in front of him only had Level One Willpower, yet he still thought that a Level Five training method was quite low? A lot of people could spend a lifetime training and yet be unable to reach Level Four Willpower. For a normal qualified pilot, a Level Five training method was already a godly training manual. If he was lucky enough to reach Level Five, then he could enter the ranks of top experts. As long as he did not meet those abnormal inheriting pilots, for everything else, it could be counted as a lifetime of abundant wealth.

“Let me tell you the truth. Count it as me giving Celine face, I’ll give you an in-depth explanation,” he stopped laughing.

Garen was not angry. He only looked at the face in the ball calmly.

“Level Five, in the Blackboard Region alone, which has hundreds of millions of people, there are fewer than two hundred people who have their hands on it. This ratio is one in a million. If you can reach Level Five in this lifetime, you would already be thanking gods, as this is the peak for normal people. Perhaps you’re comparing yourself to people like Celine, but the power they have behind them is beyond your imagination. It would be better for you to be humble and take a step at a time. Slow and steady wins the race, don’t bite off more than you can chew,” Mingway kindly explained and reminded him.

Garen’s expression remained the same and nodded lightly.

“It seems that I was too naive. Then let’s exchange for the full set of Level Five training methods but just that one is not enough.”

“Of course, I’ll let you pick two more things from my stash, how about it?” Mingway answered generously. “The treasures in the stash are at least worth tens of millions per piece. If you’re lucky and have good eyesight, you may even get treasures that are worth hundreds of millions and maybe even billions~” he gave a triumphant laughter.

“As expected of an Honorable Noble, you even dare to bring treasures that are worth billions around with you…”Garen said with a sigh.

“Honorable Nobles like us may still lack things, but money and antiques are just too much to count. To be honest, if what you offered was not a business of high-energy fuel powder, I wouldn’t even have bothered with you,” after this deal had been settled, Mingway’s voice became languid. “Alright, I have two of these full sets of training methods. There’re not many of these, and those that can be spread around without consequences are even fewer. So, I can only give you two choices.”

With a swish sound, a board of crystal rose out from the ground before Garen. There were several lines of words in there mixed with three-dimensional diagrams.

The first one was a diagram of a soaring black eagle followed by a text explanation.

‘Crouched Eagle Talon: Level Five training method, a training method that trains Willpower based around attacks using claws with high-speed charges. Every Level will increase the speed of the Mech by a level. A field of Willpower will appear to strengthen the hands of the Mech and greatly increase the hardness of defense.’

The second one was a pair of triangular silver pieces that were stacked together in a fragmented way.

‘Block Lock: Level Five Training Method, greatly increases compatibility with the Mech, a great number of parts can be applied to the Mech during maintenance. Every Level can increase the defensive performance level. Level Five can unlock the ability to analyze the weakness of enemy’s Mech.’

“There’re only these two?” Garen wrinkled his brows. At the top of each Level increase, there was a label. These were strictly classified in accordance with the standard set by the Mother Planet Federation.

The performance of Mechs from Level One until Level Five, each model of a new series of Mech that appeared would give out five levels of data of their theoretical best values.

Speed, Strength, Armor defense, Compatibility, Detection range and so on would all have their corresponding levels. To increase the value on top of the Mech’s original values by a level, this was a basic trait of the general training methods.

Both the training methods that Mingway gave out were very mediocre. Their saving grace was the high levels that prevented them from appearing on the market.

“If it’s only these two kinds, with a little bit of luck I would be able to get them from the Blackboard Academy. Don’t forget, I’m also a member of the Blue Narcissus,” Garen added.

“True, you can get Level Five training methods as long as you can meet the requirements of the Blackboard Academy and you’re also the academy’s prospective elite student. There is a great possibility. If it’s like that, this will really be a loss for you,” Mingway also felt a bit embarrassed, “Let’s do it this way, if you’re not afraid of trouble, I can give you other sets of the more troublesome training methods. These training methods were acquired through some not so legal means. Once someone finds out that you’re training these, you may get into trouble. Are you afraid?”

“The power?”

“Of course I won’t let you down.”

“Fine then, let me see first!” Garen answered decisively without any hesitation.

Mingway’s could not help but take a few more looks at him.

“What a personality, no wonder Celine praised and recommended you.”

With a swish sound, the crystal board in front of Garen change immediately. Three new training methods surfaced. There were no diagrams this time, only lines of words.

‘Yuri’s Kiss: Level Five training method. The basic version of the inherited training methods Yuri’s Kiss. Each Level will increase the practitioner’s speed and strength by 1.5 times. Side effects: The process can cause extreme pain, one practitioner fell into insanity while training it.’

‘Moonlight: Level Five training method, incomplete version, originally one of the nine training methods of the Moonlight Saintly Sect. Each level can theoretically increase speed by two levels. Side effects: twice the pressure on the body. A speed that is too fast can create a strong burden on the pilot; more than two times the pressure is put on normal pilots. Some practitioners had trained to a certain level but died abruptly due to their own physical deficiencies.’

‘Glowing Radiance: Level Five training method, one of the self-created training methods by a master from the west, a special training method that was designed to create Modulated Biochemical Pool for personal use. Each level of Modulated Biochemical Pool can enhance 0.5 level of armor enhancement. Side effect: The progress is very difficult.’

“What is this thing from the last one?” Garen asked. When he saw this Modulated Biochemical Pool, his mind clicked.

“The Modulated Biochemical Pool is a miniature factory used to create biochemical machine soldiers. This kind of technology has almost ceased to exist now because the training method is very difficult and the soldiers that are created from the biochemical pool are far less powerful than pilots. It belongs to the category of technology that has been eliminated but since it’s quite good to be used purely for research,” Mingway casually explained, “I collected it out of curiosity. I bet no one is training this sort of ancient and outdated training method now. You’re better off not using it.”

“So what’s the problem with this training method?” Garen was very interested in this. The use of the Biochemical Pool might be able to complement his current condition.

“The problem is that increasing the Level is hard,” Mingway answered. “I’d advise you not to think about it. There were once inheriting pilots that tried to train in it but that pilot did not even achieve Level Four.”

“I choose the previous Crouched Eagle Talon plus this Glowing Radiance, how about it?” Garen thought for a bit and simply said.

“No problem, the robot will take you to the stash. I have to deal with something now, so I’ll come back later,” Mingway readily agreed; these two were useless to him anyway. His own training method was the cutting-edge enhancement training method. In the beginning, there was not much difference between the training methods but later, the difference would become more obvious.

The voice went away and the ball also returned to its original state.

Garen waited for a while in the hall. Soon, a silvery white robot with wheels on its bottom half rolled over and led him to the right where an elevator slowly descended.

After getting into the elevator which went upwards for more than ten seconds, turned into another passage and moved forward for another ten seconds, it soon came to a halt.

“Destination arrived, please enter, this is the third stash of His Highness Mingway. You can choose any two things inside and no more,” the robot’s mechanical voice sounded. “Please transmit the cooperation agreement to me, I will check it and pass it on to His Highness.”

Garen lifted his Watch Terminal and transmitted the agreement that had been prepared earlier to the robot. At the same time, he transferred the first earnings over to it.

The robot’s red electronic eyes flashed a few times as it completed the transmission. It moved aside and it seemed as though it was checking the agreement.

Garen walked into the small black hall before him.

Inside, it was pitch black, but the moment he stepped into the small hall, lots of yellowish light brightened up his surroundings.

The small hall was circular in shape and a large stone-gray bird statue stood in the middle. This large bird’s posture was weird. Its wings were unfolded with one foot raised as though it was about to step forward. Its height was more than five meters, which was equivalent to that of a Mech.

He did not know whether it was an illusion, but from the moment Garen walked into the small hall, the large bird statue’s eyes seemed like they were staring at him.

Ignoring the large bird statue, Garen began to walk around the small hall.

The small hall was filled with icy-blue light balls the size of a human head. There were two white rings that were constantly circling around a sphere like satellite rings. Inside the rings were the so-called treasures.

Walking around, Garen took a look at every single one of them. Some were seemingly ordinary hats, some were small bottles holding transparent liquid, there were also some swimwear and underwear that had been worn by women. There were ancient-looking black metallic helmets, ancient knight’s armor and so on.

Garen was completely unclear of the value of these things. He only observed them along his way, intending to get a general idea of Honorable Noble Mingway’s collection. As for his choice, picking any two things would do.

When he walked until the back of the large bird, a strange cane suddenly caught Garen’s eye. The cane was very long and its upper half was capped by a ball of light. It was long, dark and smooth, seemingly made out of wood. The top was set with silver ornaments, and its white silver was carved into the shape of many thin roots that clutched an ovular crimson jewel.

“This cane…” a ripple occurred within Garen’s heart. A feeling that seemed familiar yet foreign slowly emerged inside his heart. He gently picked up the cane and savored the mysterious feeling inside his heart.

“That is Staff of Absolute Yin. Since you have picked it up, then it’s counted as the first thing you’ve chosen,” Honorable Noble Mingway’s voice sounded again. “What do you choose as the second item?”

“Staff of Absolute Yin? Can you explain what it does?”

“It’s an antique with a long history, and the material it’s made of is somewhat special. It was said that only the elders of the Mother Planet Federation are eligible to use it, but the federation had been divided for such a long time that this thing has already lost its symbolic identity. Now it’s just a pretty ornament with some collectible value,” Mingway laughed scornfully. “By the way, this thing’s value is only twenty million at most.”

Chapter 840: Mingway 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“It’s fine, as long as I like it,” Garen smiled, watching as the ball of light atop the staff scattered by itself. He spun the staff gracefully in his hand, it felt good.

“Alright, seeing as you chose wrong with the first item, I’ll recommend you something you can use.” Mingway seemed slightly apologetic. “In the corner to your right, there’s a small silver-white box, do you see it? That’s called the Instantaneous Paper Box, it’s a single-use item. When you open it, there will be an explosive field of repulsion, it’s as powerful as an inheriting pilot’s single use of his Willpower force field. It only works once, and it cannot kill or injure your opponent. The most it can do is push away the opponent, for a range of fifteen meters, it’s something that can save your life at a crucial moment.”

“Alright, I’ll take it.” Garen took his advice and chose the Instantaneous Paper Box. Now he had two items, the Staff of Absolute Yin and the Instantaneous Paper Box.

“Right, you can go rest for a bit in the Flying Saucer Room, I’ll send you straight to the edge of the Radiation Area, to the legal entrance into the Blackboard Region, so that it’ll save you some trouble.

“Thank you, Your Highness,” said Garen politely.

“By helping you, aren’t I also helping myself?” Mingway was very open about it.

Garen was in a good mood. Led by the robot, he left the small hall, and began to unlock and demagnetize the items. Everything in the vault was fortified with powerful magnetism, in order to prevent them from emitting any force fields that might be noticed by outsiders.

A white pillar of light was suspended from the ceiling above. Garen put the Staff of Absolute Yin inside first, and let it float in the pillar of light.

Smack!

Garen’s expression changed immediately. Nobody noticed, Mingway had already left, and the robot was also still controlling the light pillar so it could demagnetize the items. No one noticed that Garen’s gaze had become extremely, extremely strange, his expression changing for a moment before quickly returning to normal. Still, he could not suppress that hint of surprise and joy deep in his eyes.

After a clear sound, wisps of black air flashed around the staff, and then quickly vanished.

Garen reached his hand inside to grab the staff, and pulled it out lightly. Then he put the Instantaneous Paper Box inside, and let it float there.

No one saw that he held the staff tightly, very tightly…

**********************

The room where the Flying Saucers rested were many spherical rooms, and each sphere was hanging on so many silver racks, that it looked from afar as though the hall was lined with two rows of World Cup trophies…

The living area was cold and empty. Led by the robot, Garen entered a bedroom, and checked the surveillance situation around it. The room was very safe, the walls were all made of very high-quality alloys, so normal explosives would not even make a mark on them.

As soon as he closed the door, he grasped the Staff of Absolute Yin.

The thing felt strangely smooth and round, like human skin.

Closing his eyes lightly, Garen took a deep breath.

He began to softly rub the red ruby on the tip of the staff, the surface of the ruby had many black cracks, like melted lava. It was strangely beautiful.

Wisps of an indescribable cool air flowed into his body through his fingers, and that long-awaited feeling made Garen sink into it for a moment.

“I found them at last… potential points…”

After observing his surroundings carefully for a moment, Garen got up and turned on the computer in the room. Sitting there, he quickly checked the situation after he had left, acting as though he was surfing the Internet out of boredom.

As he clicked the mouse, large amounts of screens and images flashed through his eyes. He had filtered out a vast amount of information and sites out of the countless information given to him, and collected them in his mind.

“The Blackboard and other regions are all currently embroiled in the whirlpool that is the White Light Organization… This seems to relate to a bigger picture… There’s something impressive in the Blackboard Region, it’s the center of everything.”

Long ago he had already noticed it, but he did not pay too much attention to it. More and more outsiders were appearing in Blackboard City, that could not be a coincidence. Through all this information, he could only grasp some rough ideas. So he could use them to figure out what the bigger picture was like.

“But no matter what problems there are in the region, none of it has anything to do with me. I just need to take it step by step, and proceed according to plan, then nothing will go wrong.” Garen quickly clicked a couple of pages, his fingers brushing past the keyboard with a whoosh.

He gathered all the serious incidents that had happened in the region recently and put them together in a file. By listing them all down from the top, he could see that it was not just the Blackboard Region, but even the Polar Region and the Maria Region, as well as others, were beginning to make their moves.

Garen’s intelligence was twice that of a normal person, his reflex speed and logical thinking skills abnormally fast. Soon enough, he had more or less figured out that something major was happening in the Blackboard Region.

It was highly likely that the strange actions from the White Light Organization and other main regions were also as a result of this.

“The elite students and the higher-ups are mostly in charge of the serious incidents outside, most students remain unaffected, so I can ignore this. The Blackboard Region has caught everyone’s attention, but on the other hand the Polar Region’s battle for territory is not really in the spotlight now… Maybe I could give it a try.” Garen’s thoughts jumped over all this, and landed on the territory he had decided on. He could use this chance to ask Mingway about it, Mingway was also a rich noble from the Polar Region, so he would probably have influence in that sense.

The battle in the Blackboard Region was too far away from him, what he needed to do now was to increase his own powers as soon as possible.

Ever since he reincarnated here, his recovery speed had been too slow.

“Last time I absorbed the White Peacock Stones and increased my limit, but I had always been holding it back, so that I could wait for a good enough training method and increase them together.”

With his bare hands, Garen picked up two stacks of printed information on the table next to the computer in the room. These were the two stacks of training information that Mingway had asked someone to put in the room beforehand.

He flipped through them. Glowing Radiance was his main focus, Crouched Eagle Talon was only a generalized training method, like Galaxy Glow, they could be bought on the market. Or rather, out of any people on the street who were currently practicing training methods, a couple of them would use this Crouched Eagle Talon. But most people could only reach Level Three at the most, while this version was Level Five, so it was much better. Garen had seen them on the market before, but they were too average so he never really considered them.

“Alright, this is the one, this is the highest level training method I’ve come into contact with. If I couldn’t reach Mingway, perhaps I could only buy this at a high price from Blue Narcissus.”

Garen flipped open the Crouched Eagle Talon, and began to read it carefully, page by page. It was relatively easy for him to switch from training with the Galaxy Glow to this one, because he did not go deep with that one, and his Willpower had yet to fully reach that special state.

The training method was very simple, Garen just read it once and he could already completely understand its secret. Unlike the previous training method, the Crouching Eagle Talon first activated the arms, activating the Willpower in the arms. Since this one was the most-used part, so it was very easy for regular people to do that as long as their Willpower was strong enough.

Following the steps stated there, he just had to move his current Willpower into forming two imprints. After they stayed in each of his arms for a short while, when he could feel that the imprints had fully formed and were sealed into his arms, that would be proof that he succeeded with the first grade.

Garen’s Willpower had already reached Level One anyway, so he could just ignore the basics. He flipped to the second grade, second level content.

Feeling the impulse to level up that was being suppressed inside him by the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, Garen let his Willpower relax slightly, releasing the suppression.

Woo… Woo…

Suddenly there was a sound by his ear that sounded like a child’s cry, it was the cry of the peacock.

Just like that, sitting in front of the computer, Garen turned his body around, and let his leather chair spin with his momentum. His skin began to turn faintly blue, a mild ice-blue color.

A hint of a warm touch spread from the right side of his face. Without him noticing, an icy-blue peacock, slender and beautiful, had appeared behind him. It stretched out its neck, lightly caressing the side of Garen’s face.

The peacock was translucent, softly making its faint cry.

Whoosh…!

All of a sudden, Garen opened his eyes, but he saw nothing beside him. There was no peacock at all. He touched his right cheek lightly, there seemed to be something more there.

Turning off the computer screen, he used the half-transparent screen as a mirror.

Garen abruptly found that there was a new, mysterious icy-blue mark on his right cheek. It was an image like that of a flying bird, covering half of his face. Most strangely, the mark seemed to have been embedded into his skin, it did not look like it was drawn on at all.

“Did I just completely step over the Basic Level, just like that?” He did not feel like he had changed a lot.

He checked the attribute pane in his vision.

‘Nonosiva Lin – Strength 3.1, Agility 3.0, Vitality 4.7, Intelligence 2.1, Potential 0%. Soul limit 40.’

‘Willpower – Lower Second Level, (Obtained a certain degree of strengthening from the Living Secret Technique)

(Training Method: Crouching Eagle Talon Level Two.’

‘Potential Quality — Void Pursuer’

‘Soul Seed – Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, Holy Phoenix Demonic Book.’

‘Secret Technique – Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Living Secret Technique, Level Five. Completion rate of Level Five is at 100%.

‘Natural Ability Obtained — Devour (Devours various living things to restore body)’

‘Natural Ability Obtained — Distorted Seed (Creating chaos is the Hellfrost Peacock’s favorite pastime)’

‘Natural Ability Obtained — Cold Chaos (Causes fluctuations in time and space naturally and releases cold air naturally within an area of twenty meters to create a chaotic low-temperature area with the lowest point at zero degrees. Simultaneously, there is a low probability that it will trigger confusion within the minds of its enemies, causing them to attack randomly)’

“Overall my attributes increased by more than three points, I’ve improved a lot. The average is about twice what it was, I knew that I would get a big upgrade once I got past the Basic Level.

And then there’s Cold Chaos. Its range was increased to twenty meters, and its temperature reached 0 degrees. I guess I could kinda use it.”

Garen looked at his changes, somewhat satisfied.

“The main point is that my Willpower has finally reached Level Two. I knew that increasing Living Secret Techniques would strengthen my whole body, that little bit of additional effect would also allow my Willpower to increase as well. As expected of the powerful secret technique that can be used all over the universes.”

“Now, let’s take a look at the only item with potential power that I’ve found since coming to this world…”

Garen moved his gaze to the Staff of Absolute Yin, his gaze burning hot. If he could obtain potential points, then his speed of improvement would increase tremendously.

Chapter 841: Fog 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Potential points could rapidly reduce the time needed, as long as he had a strong enough spirit, he could improve in the shortest time with no side effects. Some weaker, lower level techniques could even be forcefully upgraded using potential points.

Garen’s eyes flashed slightly, as though he was holding the staff and examining it carefully, but in truth, he was feeling the constant flow of that refreshing air into his body.

Only when he caressed the gem on the staff slightly would that refreshing air appear, this is how it was different from the Antique of Tragedy from before.

Looking at his attribute pane, he saw that after such a long time, the potential power pane finally began to move slowly.

‘Nonosiva Lin – Strength 3.1, Agility 3.0, Vitality 4.7, Intelligence 2.1, Potential 10%. Soul limit 40.’

Just a few seconds of caressing gave him 10% potential value. Although it was not fast, it was still better than nothing. He had used up a lot of potential value and potential points when he was drifting in the Mother Stream, if he could have kept some of it, he would not have been so lost in this world for so long.

Carefully examining his skill pane, Garen chose the skills that could be upgraded with potential points. Unsurprisingly, the low-level Willpower training method, Crouching Eagle Talon, just happened to be forcefully upgradable using the potential points.

“Is it equal to a middle-level secret technique, huh? Two points to increase one level. Looks like it’s not too low-level once it’s related to supernatural powers.”

Garen calculated how many potential points he needed, and came up with a comparison.

In the Secret Technique World, low-level secret techniques needed 1 point to upgrade by one level, middle-level ones needed 2, and high-level ones needed 5. High-level ones also needed to fulfill certain special secret technique training requirements. The Crouching Eagle Talon needed two points to level up once, so it seemed to belong to the same level as middle-level secret techniques.

Finding the hope to leveling up quickly, Garen began to investigate the staff in his hand meticulously, trying to find the source of the emission of potential power.

When he just grabbed the gem, there was no power coming out. But he just had to caress the gem lightly, and a few refreshing wisps would appear. It would not work if he rubbed it too hard either, so it looked like he needed to use the right amount of force to touch and caress it, so that the potential power would reach its maximum value.

He stopped caressing it and found a small knife instead, trying to scratch the red gem on the tip of the staff lightly.

Amidst the scratching sounds, he actually managed to scratch off tiny bits of powder. He did not know what the gem was made of, it was not very hard, and seemed instead like a normal piece of concrete.

After he scratched off a bit of the surface, Garen used his finger to lightly rub the place that was shaved off.

Psst…

A large gust of potential energy surged into his body abruptly, as endless as a river And strangely, this surge was slowly weakening as time passed by.

“I knew it! This thing has a self-regenerating ingredient.” Garen noticed that the surface of the crystal had somehow become smooth again, the scratches he had made with the knife disappearing in a flash.

His potential value shot up from 20% to 83%, and then it started to slow down.

102%… 111%… 137%… 144%… 150%… Finally, it stopped at 153%.

“Why has it stopped?”

Garen used the knife to scratch the crystal again, and then touched the place that was shaved with his finger. However, there was no longer a huge surge like before, the speed of increase just sped up ever so slightly.

After that, he constantly tried many other ways, shaving off a lot more powder from the crystal gem. These powders would naturally evaporate and disappear into the air, while the gem on the tip of the staff no longer exploded with power like the first time. Every time he scratched it, the flow would only grow slightly bigger, and then it would not really move anymore.

His initial hypothesis was that the gem on the Staff of Ultimate Yin was probably a treasure that could generate potential power on its own. This treasure would gather some potential power inside it, but it could not store much, and the power would also be slowly released and wasted. That was why there would be a small surge like before.

Garen quickly found details about the Staff of Ultimate Yin from the Internet.

He discovered that the staff had always represented life, reproduction and activeness, it was the symbol of the Mother Planet Federation’s Tree Root Elder. No one knew how many there were, but they were extremely rare and valuable.

Within two hours, Garen had finally collected 200% in potential value, meaning he had two potential points.

Without hesitation, he poured the potential points into the Crouching Eagle Talon.

The moment the potential points took effect, his arms made a cracking sound, as though there was a rope or something tying Garen’s arms up tightly. Round and round, they seemed to suffocate him.

“It’s so tight…”

Garen raised his arms, feeling like back then when he cultivated his Golden Statue Technique. His arms were very tight.

“Too bad I’m not in the same universe so I can’t cultivate the Golden Statue Technique, but I can make up for it by training the basics of the Crouching Eagle Talon.” Garen could feel his Willpower increasing again slowly. Under the effect of the potential points, it was moving towards Level Three. Relaxing in his heart, Garen began to wonder how he could strengthen this training method.

Based on his martial arts that had once reached the top and approached Army Level, and his experience with secret techniques, it was very easy for him to patch up a low-level training method like this, and reach the point where his body and Willpower were in sync.

Soon enough Garen modeled an easier path in his heart, taking apart everything he could use from the Divine Statue Technique that was once his strongest, and melding it with the Crouching Eagle Talon. Without changing the part of the Crouching Eagle Talon that cultivated the Willpower, he made up for its shortcomings in upgrading his arms instead.

Secret techniques trained the general qualities, such as the resilience of the body cells, wheres Willpower was a deep-level living force generated from the cells, the two of them should work together pretty well.

Garen checked a lot of information, and it was because the strength of the body had an effect on Willpower, so that there even used to be a school of pilots who trained their bodies to the extreme. Eventually, however, it was lost because it could not spread far enough.

“Since I’ve found a direction, I can try to merge it for a bit.”

With the effect of the potential points, Garen was no longer worried about his improvement speed, but rather about the direction he should advance in. His own level was enough to reach a very high level, but if he did not grasp the direction right, he might restrict his own development, or end up in a dead-end, delaying himself.

***************

Blackboard Region, Blackboard Academy

Under the quiet tree, Vera slowly walked up to the boys’ dormitory building.

It had been a few days since Nonosiva left, and his student card was getting slightly magnetized, so the school issued him a new one. Instructor Hamm noticed that Nono and Vera were close, so he passed it to her to pass to him.

Along with that girl from before, Vera kept sticking to Nonosiva like glue recently. She used to be just a very normal pretty girl in the class who just happened to be slightly more innocent-looking, but after approaching Nono, even if he was not very close to her, she had still earned the respect of many of her classmates. Some students from the other classes even treat her as though she was Nono’s girlfriend.

Vera particularly enjoyed the feeling of kowtowing and envy from among girls, she believed that she was naturally meant to enjoy life.

Holding the student card, Vera openly walked into the dorm building. Some of the students who were familiar with her greeted her with smiles.

Vera walked to Nono’s dorm door, and hesitated for a while, before lightly inserting the student card into the scanning machine at the door.

Boop-boop.

The scanner lock made a few sounds, and then there was the smack of the door opening automatically.

“I’ll leave after I put this student card down, when Nono comes back, he’ll renew the information and change out the old ones,” she thought, walking inside and placing the student card on the table in the room.

She turned around and was about to leave, but there was an unbearable itch in her heart, and she just could not take that step.

“Nono’s not here anyway, so I might as well see what secrets he’s hiding… How could he get those princes from the Blue Narcissus to place so much emphasis on him…”

Vera’s heart was slowly starting to burn.

Closing the door lightly, she looked around her, and then drew the blinds.

First, she looked in the bedside drawers, after flipping through them, she found just plain clean underwear, socks, and the like. There was nothing really else.

Then came the desk, she opened each of the drawers that were lined up. The first held study notes and materials, the second electronic components, chargers, and so on. As for the third drawer, Vera yanked it hard, but somehow could not open it.

“Could it be the secret in this drawer?” Her heart burned, and she looked around the room, but she could not find a key. Finally, she tried waving the student card at the lock.

Boop-boop… smack!

It was unlocked.

Vera was instantly overjoyed, and she pulled open the drawer quickly.

Inside, there was a thick stack of white documents.

“What’s this!?” She picked them up and flipped through them casually. “Contract for high-energy fuel powder…? Signed by…Nonosiva… Vivienne… Celine…”

Hiss… Suddenly she took a sharp intake of breath. On the document, she saw a large string of numbers spelling out a gargantuan sum.

That was almost a million Universal Units! And that was just for one month!

“The document says that all the contractees will earn according to these percentages… Nono himself will get this much! That’s… that’s practically free money!” Vera was in complete shock, feeling as though her eyes were sparkling with gold.

She took out all the documents quickly, and found large stacks of cash at the very bottom. The pale green notes were all the largest denominator, a thousand units, and such a thick pile would probably mean several hundred thousand units.

“So much money…!” Although Vera’s family was very rich, they were also rather strict with how much pocket money they gave their kids. The children would not get more than ten thousand a month, and her family was only average compared to others in the school. Outside, she might be considered a princess or a rich young miss, but here, she was completely unassuming.

Under these circumstances, the power relations and money struggles between girls became the way to measure the standard worth of the pretty girls.

Vera often found herself with less than enough money every month, after going to so many of those high-end consumer places, she always ended up with nothing. But compared to some other girls, some of them may not even be able to buy a bag.

She had secretly looked for ways to earn money everywhere, but unfortunately, she did not meet with much luck. Several times, she had to resist the urge to find a sugar daddy. She held back in the end, though, because she believed that with her conditions, she would surely be able to find a rich and powerful guy someday.

Chapter 842: Fog 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“So much money…” Now there was so much cash right in front of Vera’s eyes. Looking at the messy bundles of cash, it was obvious to her that their owner did not take them seriously. He had just tossed them in carelessly, and there was even a smattering of smaller change underneath the huge notes.

“Nono would surely not care about the money in this drawer, he gets a cut of more than two million every month… This tiny sum must surely just be a pittance for him…” Vera gulped. “If I take a bit… just a bit… Surely he would not notice…”

Greed surged in her heart. Such a thick wad of cash, if she simply pulled out a dozen or so notes, that would surely not make an impact at all, surely she would not be noticed…

Such thoughts kept echoing inside her mind.

After hesitating for a while, Vera finally reached out her hand, and expertly pulled seven or eight thousand-unit notes from the stack.

“Just this… Nono wouldn’t notice, for sure.” She closed the drawer with a whoosh, feeling her heart pound extremely quickly.

Stuffing the notes into her wallet anxiously, she got up and arranged her hair.

She put everything back the way it was, opened the blinds, and opened the door. But Vera’s heart kept replaying that terrifying sum on that document.

She paused for a moment, but in the end, she still turned around quickly. Closing the door, she found that document again, and she quickly took several pictures of it with her Watch Terminal.

“I might be able to sell this for a pretty sum…”

She smiled, satisfied, and finally closed the drawer again, leaving the room reluctantly.

***************

In the Blackboard Region, Caesura City

The huge cylindrical chimneys were dyed a yellow-red by the twilight rays.

There were many skyscrapers and streets between the chimneys, but compared to the size of the chimneys, these buildings were as small as toys, like the uneven grass on a lawn.

Between the streets, there was a constant flow of levitating cars, as though they were the pulse of a city that flowed with fresh metallic blood.

Boom!

Suddenly, there was a large explosion of crimson flames at the bottom of the largest chimney. It was a high-end residential area that was lavishly decorated, and the two mansions in the very center were completely engulfed in flames, turning into black scraps in an instant.

Thick black smoke floated out from the burning remains, and soon enough, the sirens of ambulances, police cars, and fire engines arrived at the scene. A large crowd of people alighted from the cars, and quickly began to secure the area.

Beside the burning remains, the crimson firelight dyed everything within a ten-meter radius bright red.

Ker-chak! Ker-chak, ker-chak…

Buddy quickly took a few close-range shots with his high-quality camera, his expression somewhat somber.

There were a few more reporters from the news agency behind him, but unlike him, they looked extremely excited.

“Hehe, this is big news!” said someone in a soft voice.

“We’re lucky, we got here at the first opportunity, and go first-hand information,” the other person said excitedly. “My aunt’s husband just happens to be the inspector in charge of maintaining order here, otherwise we would still need about ten minutes of source investigation.”

Buddy was not in as good as the mood as the two of them, though.

“Such an explosion could instantly override all the defense systems, and destroy all the Energy Barriers. Only a strong enough pulse wave bomb can do that…”

“Isn’t that perfect? We can just call this explosion the Pulse Wave Incident.” The reporter behind him hurriedly noted down the headline.

“But very few people know that one of the previous Three Black Rain Generals, the strongest veteran pilot under the last generation’s Black Star, Bordo Miserman lives here,” said Buddy in a somber voice.

“The Three Black Rain Generals?! Buddy, are you kidding me? The Three Black Rain Generals are the three strongest pilots under Black Star, even if they have retired, they still enjoy the privileges of Great Generals here in our Blackboard Region!” The reporters’ expression changed immediately, a regular terrorist attack and a pointed attack were two completely different things.

“I’m sure of it, I came here for a special interview before, interviewing General Bordo’s grandson.” Buddy looked at the fire quietly. The fire brigade sprayed pillars of water at the fire hurriedly, and the smell of dry fire-extinguishing powder, as well as oxygen-absorbing liquid, proliferated everywhere.

“No way, the Black Rain Generals should be enjoying their retirement in Blackboard Academy!”

“Very few people know that Bordo didn’t actually enter the academy, and instead he lived alone as a normal person, with his family. It’s not just him, several other important officials did the same,” said Buddy quietly.

Instantly, their hearts began to feel heavy.

“So you’re saying… this explosion, it was aimed for General Bordo?” someone asked.

“It’s very likely,” Buddy nodded. “If it really was an attack aimed at him, with General Bordo’s skills, to think that he could still be destroyed so calmly…Then the enemy’s powers must be…” Suddenly, he felt a chill down his spine.

***********************

“This just in, there was a terrorist attack in the city of Caesura yesterday. A pulse wave bomb blew through two houses in a high-end residential area. Fortunately, because of the peak-hour traffic from the end of office hours, there were very few people in the buildings. The number of casualties and fatalities were few, including about a dozen members of the elderly and children…”

Accompanied by the sound of the television news, Clint was sprawled onto the table in his room, wolfing down his food. There was a plate with an entire kilogram of seafood fried rice, with some octopus, lots of shrimp shells, chunks of fish, strands of seaweed. He poured all of it into his mouth, as though that mouth was an endless abyss.

“One more portion!”

Smack!

Clint smashed the empty plate onto the table and yelled.

“You’ve already eaten three portions…” Baylon said helplessly beside him, wearing an apron. She was the one who made the fried rice, having rushed out to buy ingredients and trying it out blindly after some studying. Personally, he(1) felt the taste was so-so, but Clint ate it like it was a delicacy.

“He’s a pig, ignore him, and fill your own stomach first,” Red Moon’s voice rang out slowly.

“I can’t help it either!! I just never feel full, there must be something wrong with that training method you gave me! I didn’t use to be like this!” Clint cried out in defense.

“Sure, the Nine Mega Cannon training method increases your appetite, but not to this extent. The more you eat, the more that means your energy efficiency is low, you waste too much, so you need to absorb a lot more energy to make up for your Willpower consumption.”

“What’s that mean? I don’t get it…” Clint asked honestly.

“It means you’re too stupid, that’s why you eat so much,” Red Moon stated mercilessly.

“Oh! Don’t blame me, there must be something wrong with your training method!” Clint finally knew how to resist, after accepting a brand new plate of fried rice from Baylon, he continued to dig in.

“That idiot.” Red Moon was utterly speechless, and turned his attention instead to Baylon, dressed in a white apron.

After this kid’s Willpower was activated, perhaps as a result of the training method, but mostly because of his own body, Baylon had somehow quickly become such a sweet, pure, and pretty figure.

Slender, weak, tall and long, curves in all the right places, large watery eyes that looked like they were about to cry at any moment. Long hair hanging loose, matched with fair and supple skin, gave off a gently beautiful impression that just begged for love and pity.

“As expected, you fail as a boy, it’s better to be a girl and find someone to take care of you,” Red Moon said exasperatedly. “It’s unnatural. Tsk-tsk…”

“The more I train with that Bright Queen Jisaiya method, the more I feel my body change. What’s up with that…?” asked Baylon, embarrassed.

“It’s normal, that’s the training method inherited from the legendary Bright Queen, it’s a Three-Only type, and it can evolve, allowing the pilot’s body to advance together with it from the very beginning,” Red Moon explained.

“What do you mean by Three-Only attributes?”

“It means what it says, in the whole world, only three people can practice this training method, because the Bright Queen Jisaiya only left behind three imprints. If you have the chance to reach the peak, you’ll enter a race to obtain the imprints, and achieve the actual, complete main imprint. But it’s still far, far too early. That woman, the Bright Queen, died too soon, and she was a picky one too. If it weren’t for the fact that her training method was still kinda decent, I wouldn’t wanna get close to her.”

Red Moon seemed to have a very bad impression of the Bright Queen.

“Lon! One more bowl!!”

Beside them, Clint had somehow finished a large plate of rice in such a short time, slamming the plate onto the table and yelling again.

“There’s… There’s no more…” Baylon was utterly shocked, seeing how Clint still looked unsatisfied, she began to panic… “You ate it all…” She was about to cry. She had made seven people’s worth of food, and this guy finished it all, even she had not gotten a chance to eat yet.

“Urk…” Clint noticed that he had eaten too much as well, and scratched his head awkwardly. “Um… Uh… Ah!!” Suddenly, he screamed.

“Careful! Something’s coming!” In an instant, Red Moon hit Clint hard with a bolt of electricity, making him cry out in pain.

“Everyone, hold your breaths!”

Suddenly, the lights in the room went off, and everything was plunged into darkness. There was only the faint smell of fried rice lingering in the air.

Outside the room, in the garden, a tattered tall black shadow slowly appeared outside the wall.

“The Forbidden…” A deep male voice came from within the shadow. “Found it, right here…”

Smack!

Suddenly, a beacon of light was turned on, shining onto the shadow and revealing most of its body. It was a tattered and broken-up white-and-red mech, six meters tall!

“Do it!!”

Amidst the shouts, a similarly huge humanoid shadow jumped out from the house, crashing straight for the Red-White Mech. Underneath the illumination of the light, they saw that this black shadow was actually just a broken trash mech made up of assorted parts.

“Fool!”

The Red-White Mech did not give way at all, crashing its arms forward.

Bam!!!

The two crashed into each other.

“Eh? What tremendous strength!” A surprised voice came from inside the Red-White Mech. “But if all you have is strength, you’re still just a piece of trash.”

Waving him away, the Red-White Mech swept with its leg, and hit the opponent’s waist with a clang, sending him flying out and crashing into a large portion of the wall at the side.

“Clint!!” cried Baylon worriedly from inside the room.

“Hand over the Forbidden Core, and I will spare your life,” the Red-White Mech chuckled, stamping on his body so that he could not get up.

Clint felt weak all over, he could not use any strength at all.

“Idiot! I let you drive mechs so that you could run errands, not to fight! You idiotic moron, don’t you understand human speak!!” Red Moon scolded madly beside his ear.

“What to do…?”

“What to do my ass! Run!!”

All of a sudden, Clint’s mech found a huge burst of energy. He stood up abruptly and ran away as fast as his legs could take him. When he passed Baylon, he picked up Baylon lightly, and then ran into the distance even more madly.

After this full-strength crash, the Red-White Mech’s engine nearly exploded. He was already at the end of his rope, his mech was nearly collapsing after his battle with Red-Eyed Medero, so he did not dare to exert too much force at all.

And now a tiny Level One minnow had managed to escape from him, that really pissed him off.

Amidst the roar of the engine, he quickly gave chase. The two mechs, one after the other, soon disappeared into the night.

Chapter 843: Eagle’s Nest 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was not easy, switching to the Crouched Eagle Talon training method. After Garen was sent straight to the borders of the Blackboard Region by the Flying Saucer, he came down using one of the single-person flying machines His Highness Mingway gave him. Without much delay, he arrived back inside the Blackboard Region directly.

Just as Garen expected, the security and scanning were the same level as they were back in the Blackboard Academy. So he had been scared for nothing, he could cheat his way through with just that little Moonfang.

The whole Blackboard Region was currently in chaos thanks to the White Light, it had been proven that the Pulse Wave Incident was the terrorist organization White Light’s doing. The policemen and army squads from all over began to move out in earnest, and for a moment there the whole region was being rocked by the reaction.

On the way back to the Academy’s Blackboard City, Garen could see new notices and declarations by the police all over the place, such as how to save oneself in the face of a terrorist attack.

After two days on the road, he finally returned to Blackboard Academy. Upon replying to the greetings from his friends and fellow students one by one, he went straight back to his dorm.

Ker-chak!

The door opened, and the first thing Garen saw was the student card on the table.

“A new card? Someone’s been in my room.” He reacted quickly, and looked around to see if he could find any clues.

The position of the curtain was not right, that was probably tampered with before. There was a slight mark on the thin layer of dust on his desk, that someone must have messed with it.

Garen bent down and wiped the handles of the drawers lightly, then he brought it to his nose and sniffed it. All three handles had a faint smell of perfume.

“It’s a woman. Perfume like this must be a fairly young woman.”

His expression was calm.

“It should be the girl who brought the student card here, seeing as there was no one here, she could not help but mess around a bit. If the higher-ups let her bring the student card here, she must be someone who seems to be closer to me in the eyes of the public, and a member of the school as well. And in this school, the ones who seem to be closer to me are the likes of Vivienne, Celine and the rest.”

Garen’s brain turned slightly, and he quickly came to a conclusion.

“Celine does not like perfume, and Vivienne always uses the most expensive and trendiest brands. This perfume smells like the type those innocent-looking girls like, but it’s not too expensive. If it’s not that valuable, it can’t be Vivienne. In that case, it has to be those people, Kell or Vera.”

“I just have to ask who helped to send me my student card, and I’ll know.”

He pulled open the last drawer. The notes and documents were exactly as he left them, but the wad of notes seemed to be slightly thinner.

“As I thought, I need a more private room.”

Standing up, Garen shook out his joints.

Now that he had reached Level Three Willpower, he felt as though his base was not too steady, and his Willpower was not solid enough. It was evidently because he progressed too quickly.

After the Willpower in his arms was activated, before he even learned to control them properly, he had already reached the next level, Level Three.

The Level Three Crouched Eagle Talon had very powerful malleability and general accessibility, but Garen had advanced too quickly. As soon as he reached Level Two, he went straight into Level Three. He did not have time to get used to controlling it at Level Two at all.

“I need to spend some time on stabilizing my power.” Garen was aware of this problem as well.

After washing up, he began to spend time in his room training his body in correspondence with the Divine Statue Technique. Adapting it with his battle experience that went even beyond King of the Century, he began to slowly create an even more perfect version of the Crouched Eagle Talon. Most importantly, the Crouched Eagle Talon used to be a very normal Level Five training method, one that could not reach Level Six inheritance. Under Garen’s changes, however, it seemed to be moving to a new level. He could not be sure if he was right about the deductions regarding the training method after this, but it was vaguely moving away from the original path.

He trained and tweaked it a bit in his room, and then he practiced the Waterbird Fist that he was most familiar with in the previous world. Due to the difference in universe and space, the Waterbird Fist required a makeover before it could be used again. Out of the Waterbird Fist Profounds, only the purest and most powerful Profounds could be isolated away. Using his Willpower as well as his body, he could use the Final Profound, Flight, with up to 90% of its original power.

Garen rearranged the pure combat techniques from the Totem World. Other than the Living Secret Techniques, the only things he could still use from the Totem World were the Ten Thousand Mammoth Battle Skills. The Ten Thousand Mammoths Battle Skills were actually a complete set of fighting skills that he crafted from his foundations in the Secret Technique World, and it was basically a head-on fighting style.

Meanwhile, Flight used the pinnacle of skill, so the two were completely different.

Combat skills were combat skills, the purest combat skills had nothing to do with secret techniques or methods, but certain combat skills had different methods at the core driving them, so naturally, they would have wildly different powers and styles.

Garen figured out everything he could use in this world, and spent three days in his room, completely isolated. He even turned off his Watch Terminal, so that he could concentrate properly on perfecting it. From his own martial arts, from the Demonic Book martial arts, from the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point, he collected and gathered them all.

He cut out all the parts that could not be used due to the different world setting. Vaguely, he noticed that after his Willpower grew stronger, the ideas his mind came up with also seemed to be more perfect, as though there was a second brain helping him out with thoughts and calculations. For many questions, as soon as he started thinking about it, he could instantly and clearly get his intended answer. The simple logical processes in the meanwhile were all solved in an instant.

He brought out all the pure combat skills, the things he could use in this world. He filtered them through these past three worlds, assessing them with different rules. Many of them looked strong, but Garen threw away the parts with many limitations.

Three days later…

A brand new form of martial arts finally began to take shape in his hands.

Garen renamed these martial arts the Ten Thousand True Technique. It was a very simple and very plain name. Ten Thousand meant many, and True meant true nature and thusness(1), it could mostly be used limitlessly even across universes.

Actually, the Ten Thousand True Technique was not just a normal external martial arts technique, it was also a method that could temporarily stimulate his body’s explosive power.

Garen used all the secret methods he knew, taking away the limited parts and then continuing to model and derive the usable parts, finally forming the Ten Thousand True Technique’s Nine Level Body System.

This Nine Level Body System was related to the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point, but it was not as ridiculously powerful. Instead, it was gentler. According to Garen’s calculations, this would be more adaptable to other universes as well.

After running his techniques past so many rules from so many worlds, it was equal to him straining the impurities off his martial arts, revealing the smooth surface underneath.

The Ten Thousand True Technique represented Garen’s aim for his future position.

No matter what power system it was, as long as he was in human shape, as long as he had his basic organs, the Ten Thousand True Technique would work.

After melding his own fighting techniques into one, Garen began to train the Ten Thousand True Technique anew. His roots were strong, and he had long achieved the nine levels of state of mind required, so he very easily reached Level Three. After that, he needed to constantly train his own body.

***************

The Academy’s physical fighting training area was a special place that the Blackboard Academy had designed especially for students who liked to practice their actual combat. It was as large as five football fields, and there was a transparent ceiling of reinforced glass above them. The sunlight came shining down, and the high-powered air ventilation machines around them kept buzzing lightly.

There were rows of punching bags and alloy pillars lined up closely, and every so often there were even cube-shaped three-story buildings. The buildings were made completely of glass walls, so everything outside could be seen clearly.

In the afternoon, there were still many people sweating it out in the training arena, training relentlessly. They trained in alone, in pairs, even in groups surrounding one person. There were also those doing health exercises… boys and girls as well, including some middle-aged people or members of the elderly.

There were also some professional athletes. Track, endurance, sprint, hurdles, they were all there. Many people came here every day to train their bodies, all the equipment was free to use, and it was very close to the canteen as well, so it was very convenient.

Garen changed into some black gym clothes, wearing a black belt around his waist. Walking into the training field, he heard the yells of a group of people playing football in the distance, while on the other side, there was also a group of girls practicing aerobics. Other than the mech course, there were also many other students in the other courses.

Although piloting was indeed a very important and prized profession, that did not mean everyone wanted to be a pilot. There were students majoring in battleship command, or art, or languages, or engineering.

On the field, there was an uproar of shouts. In the large area in the center, there were several dozen students dressed in different clothes and running sparsely from each other, while two coaches count the time at the side.

Alone, Garen walked to a row of training equipment that no one was using. The equipment was very old, and there were even some sweat stains left over on them. Evidently, someone had just finished using them.

The area in front of this was a small plastic training field. Several boys and girls were gathered in front of a female teacher as she taught them to dance, while there were things like double or single bars beside them.

From here, he could just see the situation on the running track diagonally ahead. The athletes were all running round and round at even speeds. Although they looked to be sweating a lot, their breathing was still even and rhythmic, clearly showing that they were very experienced runners.

Garen pulled back his inquisitive gaze, and walked up to the heaviest black sandbag.

Bam!!

The heavy black metal sandbag was hit by Garen’s forearm, and was sent rocking wildly out.

Garen took off his shirt, revealing his well-defined muscles. He put black gloves on his hands, and all his skin was slightly dark. Among those on the training field, he was considered average.

He came here just to get used to the changes in his body, in his Willpower, and to sort out the conglomeration of his martial arts. By going into the Third Level Ten Thousand True Technique straight away, his body had improved by three times that of others. This was also the change brought by the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, but this change was not something he had controlled and built up over time. So if he wanted to utilize his most powerful potential smoothly, he needed to get used to his own level.

Bang bang! Bang!

Garen began to punch the target again and again. He did not put a lot of force into every punch, but he tried to keep it in a very small and precise area, carefully sensing the waves and tremors in his body.

Using tremors to understand his own body, that was a special martial arts that only Garen had, it was one of the training methods from the Secret Technique World.

There were no special movements, he just let loose punch after punch, occasionally unleashing a side-kick, knocking the heavy sandbag into swinging back and forth, as though it was going to snap and fall at any moment. It whooshed loudly, the giant swinging metal sandbag giving off a very unstable and dangerous feeling.

After showcasing all of his basic fist techniques, Garen carefully felt his own power level, and the minute changes in his body. At the same time, he used the Ten Thousand True Technique to use the different levels of vibrations from all over his body to strengthen and open up his body from a very deep level. Unlike training methods, this started from the outside and worked inwards. In some manner of speaking, the Ten Thousand True Technique was one of the most balanced external techniques. Especially after merging with Garen’s Seven Star Life’s Secret Point secret method, each level had some of the power as though he had permanently opened one of the secret points, hence permanently activating his body’s potential and increasing his body’s quality. It was not by much, not too exaggerated, but it had also lost the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point secret method’s terrifying backlash effect, becoming gentler and safe.

The Divine Statue Technique trained one’s body, but merging the Divine Statue Technique with the Crouched Eagle Talon, he could strengthen his Willpower, and he could strengthen his arms and body to a certain degree as well.

Together, the two of them trained his body and his Willpower at the same time, balancing it out as they progressed together.

Chapter 844: Eagle’s Nest 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After completing his set of fist techniques, Garen was starting to sweat slightly as well. It was not tiring to practice his punches, but it took quite a lot of mental energy to slowly adjust the vibrations. Different areas required different frequencies of vibrations so that they could be unearthed properly, these were the Ten Thousand True Technique’s strict requirements. To the outsider’s eye, it looked like a very simple, very standard fighting method, but only Garen knew that the various vibrations inside were the truly difficult part.

With a smack, he steadied the sandbag that swung at him. Only then did Garen notice that someone had been standing next to him and watching him. He looked like a well-mannered, fair and clean boy. He did not say anything, just smiling at Garen, then he walked to the side and started taking off his clothes. This revealed the tight white singlet underneath, followed by the fair but powerful and well-defined muscles. It looked like he was here to train as well.

The boy shook out his joints a little on the spot, and then found another sandbag and started practicing as well.

Garen watched him nonchalantly. This person had very good basics, and was very serious in his training, his attention fully focused on one point.

He could not be too bothered with others as well, so Garen rested for a while and then began his next round of training.

Time ticked by, and Garen took another short break. He picked up the saltwater he brought and drank a few sips from it, wiping the sweat from his body.

All the students were gathered on these large drill grounds, there were too many students from the other courses, so not many people noticed that he, the mech genius, was training his body here in the corner. It ended up being pretty quiet.

He used the heaviest metal sandbag, so the boy training next to him gave him occasional glances of envy. He was evidently very surprised at Garen’s strength. To think Garen could move several hundred kilos worth of a metal sandbag.

Soon enough, it seemed to be time for group training. More and more people arrived to train hitting and punching with their arms.

Garen sensed that one small team was here specifically to train the Crouched Eagle Talon training method. The Crouched Eagle Talon was a very accessible training method, like Outbreak of Rain and Wind Words, it was a Level Three version of the training method that was available in the market. These few types of training methods were very popular in the academy, because they had higher worth for the money. So out of the mech school students, 90%n of them used one of these training methods.

After that, only the poorer students used the Blackboard training method, that was something only students who could not afford any of the other training methods at all used. Any students with just a little bit of fortune would choose training methods like Outbreak of Rain, Wind Words or Crouched Eagle Talon. Compared to the free Blackboard training method, these training methods were slightly better, and had that slight edge when it came to building foundations. As their levels increased, the difference would become huge by the end.

This was the reason you must not fall behind at the starting line.

Garen himself cultivated the Crouched Eagle Talon, so he quickly noticed that group of people among all the students, because they were all cultivating the Crouched Eagle Talon. There were other teams who all practiced Wind Words, or Outbreak of Rain. Students who used the same training method would instinctively gather together, so that they could discuss their problems.

These students were mostly all just Basic Level, the slightly better ones were only Upper Level One. But there were many older students who looked like they were in their third or fourth year, leading the team as they answered the others’ questions.

Garen had experience with aura, so it was very easy for him to sense their level through their spirits.

Since they all trained with the Crouched Eagle Talon, Garen was very intrigued by this world’s own matter of cultivation. Everything he learned was from the Internet. The textbooks only spoke about the Blackboard training method.

Wiping the sweat from his body, Garen picked up his clothes and bottle, walking towards that group.

The small group was standing in the middle of the large field, forming their own little circle like everyone else. Every so often, some people would leave, but others would join.

“…When you enter Level One from the Basic Level, there would be a small leap. Your Willpower would make a small leap. It sounds very abstract, but in truth, that feeling is like going up a step. After taking one step upwards, if you turn around and look back again, you’ll be seeing a world from a higher perspective. Following the same logic, the Crouched Eagle Talon is better than most training methods at training the arms, and this shows in your control of the mech…” The only older girl was explaining the basics of training to her juniors and freshmen, dressed in a white blouse with puffy sleeves, and dark blue faded long jeans. She looked simple, clean, and professional.

Garen walked over and looked at the circle of juniors, sighing slightly in his heart. Not long ago he had been one of the freshmen as well, but now he was a senior to these students.

This group of students all had young and innocent faces, their eyes full of curiosity and patience. Evidently, they had full confidence in their training method paths.

“Before coming into contact with training methods, everyone dreams that they might be that prodigy, one in ten thousand, but reality is cruel…” Garen shook his head slightly. Standing at the side quietly, he listened to that senior explain the process of training, and compared each step to his own process. He also noticed a lot of things he had missed out, as this senior mentioned some little ways to use the Crouched Eagle Talon in battle that also opened Garen’s eyes. He was pretty impressed, these were evidently the special tricks passed down through generations of students, so they were naturally unique in their own ways.

“Hey, handsome, do you practice the Crouched Eagle Talon as well?” A young girl with curly black hair patted Garen’s back lightly. “What bulging muscles…!” she exclaimed.

“They’re okay, my basics aren’t that strong,” Garen nodded. “What’s that senior sister’s name? I didn’t know so many girls liked the Crouched Eagle Talon.”

“She’s Sofia, a fourth-year senior in the mech course. Her Crouched Eagle Talon is really powerful, and she’s in the top ten of the Eagle’s Nest in her grade. She and Senior Soron take time out of their schedules every two days to teach everyone here on this field,” explained the girl softly.

“What’s the Eagle’s Nest?”

“It’s the group society formed by all the students in the academy who cultivate the Crouched Eagle Talon. The Wind Words, the Outbreak of Rain Club, they’re all like that. You actually don’t know?” The girl seemed slightly shocked. “No wonder your basics aren’t good, we need to communicate with our fellow students a lot if we want to progress together. If you’re free, come attend class from now on, or you can join our Eagle’s Nest too.”

“Are there a lot of strong fighters in there?” asked Garen.

“Of course, I hear that a Level Five instructor would occasionally come and teach the inner members and higher-ups too. No one else gets this treatment outside,” said the girl dreamily.

“Level Five instructor…” Garen’s heart twinged. He had risen too quickly, so his roots were not strong. This might just be his chance to learn from everyone’s experience and skills.

“Whaddaya say, tempted, right? I’ll talk to them for you,” said the girl without waiting for a response, hurriedly dragging Garen into the crowd.

Soon enough, the two of them reached a table that was set up inside.

“I brought a newbie for registration! Hurry, hurry, don’t delay!” the little girl yelled, smacking the table.

The table was placed inside the crowd, and when everyone was blocking it, even Garen did not notice it. Only when he walked in did he see that there were two young people sitting behind it. It was one boy and one girl, the boy was handsome and gentle, while the girl was pretty and cute. They were clearly walking ads here to recruit newbies.

“Come, my friend, register your name, class, and Willpower level.” Seeing that it was a boy who arrived, the cute girl stood up and began to greet him, handing Garen a form.

“This is so…” Garen felt something in his heart. In the previous world, he had joined the combat club, but now he was joining the Eagle’s nest in this world instead. It gave him a strange sense of familiarity.

Filling up the form quickly, he handed it over.

The girl glanced at it, and her eyes immediately lit up.

“Oh, so it’s Nonosiva. I never thought that you would switch to the Crouched Eagle Talon. You’re the First Seat prodigy from the freshmen ranking competition!” The girl was slightly excited. “Come, come, let me introduce you to Senior Sofia!”

The little girl who brought Garen here was slightly surprised as well, she did not think that the person she just randomly dragged here would be the First Seat of the freshmen last year.

The boy who had been sitting got up as well, smiling.

“Welcome, Nono, to the Eagle’s Nest. We’re one of the most populated clubs in the academy, because a lot of people chose the Crouched Eagle Talon. I didn’t think that you would choose the Eagle Talon too.”

The two of them shook hands, both very friendly.

Garen could sense that this guy was a fourth-year senior as well. His Willpower was slightly hidden, as though something was blocking it, so he could not tell what level the boy was just based on his spirit. But Garen could tell that he was at least Level Two.

The Crouched Eagle Talon advanced very quickly, and was very easy to learn. The first few levels were all relatively doable, so it was the most normal and commonly-used among the accessible training methods. It was equivalent to the Iron Skin technique or the Tongbeiquan from martial arts novels, the skills everyone knew. Since it had a naturally low level, it would always be slightly weaker than other training methods that were slightly stronger, even at the same level of Willpower.

“It’s last year’s First Seat of the freshmen, Nonosiva!”

“Even he’s chosen our Eagle’s Nest, the Crouched Eagle Talon must have its strengths!”

“Yeah, it must be good since the most people chose it, otherwise why would so many people choose it?”

The students around him were getting excited. Nono’s reputation was considerably widespread, even those who did not watch the competition felt as though they had to look up at him once they heard the title of Freshmen’s First Seat. Instantly, Nono’s image was rapidly magnified. Once they heard Nono’s level, they were even more shocked.

He was only in second-year, but he had already reached Level One, the standard people achieved at or after the fourth year. Level One was already the minimum requirement for graduation, but of course Blackboard Academy’s students all had more ambition than that, so most of them aimed for a higher level. This was equivalent to normal undergraduates and Masters students or Ph.D. students. The higher you studied, the stronger you were, and naturally the treatment you received after graduating was vastly different.

In academies, it was very common for first-years to be at the Basic level, most of them studied and trained properly. A majority of the students studied just so that they could pass the semester exams. Only a few of them really pushed hard, and never stopped working. Just imagine, how many people could earn enough credits to graduate within the first year? It was practically a miracle.

There were very few Levels Ones in second year as well, but by then there would be individual elites. Still, they would rarely even reach Level One. Even now, Garen did not actually meet the graduation requirements. Even if his Willpower was at a high enough level, he still needed to meet the mark with many other subjects.

Only in third year would you find some students who had accumulated enough credits. Garen had also planned to complete all his exams and subjects by third year. Students studied at Blackboard Academy for eight years in total, and to obtain enough credits by third year, you needed to take many, many subjects. It would total up to more than a hundred and ten subjects, and you had to reach Level One in all of them. Many subjects had overlapping study hours, which was also why it was very hard to gather enough credits.

Chapter 845: Actual Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The group of people parted like the red sea, revealing Sofia, who was giving a lecture at the front.

She raised her head and looked over in his direction.

“I’ve heard everything, Mr. Nono, last cohort’s freshmen’s First Seat. I never thought that you would’ve improved the Crouched Eagle Talon Technique as well,” Sofia’s voice was soft and gentle and it had a mesmerizing effect.

“The reason I joined the Eagle’s Nest was that I hoped to learn more from stronger fellow practitioners. Of course, I also wanted to exchange knowledge with my fellow practitioners regarding the theories and concepts behind the Crouched Eagle Talon Technique,” Garen sincerely expressed his intents.

“That is to be expected. Everyone who joins the Eagle’s Nest has the same intentions. Only through these sorts of exchanges there would there be clashes in schools of thought, and only then can we see improvement. As compared to the mindset of those who have just enrolled in the school, having access to the combined experience and abilities of everyone here from both the present and the past will allow us to make the most out of our training methods,” Sofia articulated.

“If you don’t mind, I would like to go and view the Eagle’s Nest immediately,” Garen said. He started to feel that his foundation for this technique was not concrete enough and this Eagle’s Nest might be able to solve his concerns.

If he did not have a concrete foundation, it would make it harder for him to progress to the next level. It may even lead to him facing more trouble when up against an opponent of the same level, especially when it comes to a battle of Willpower.

“Sounds like a plan,” Sofia was also a very straight-forward person. Despite her gentle appearance, she was actually exceptionally fervent in her interests. Seeing how direct Garen was, she too loosened up.

“Peach, bring Mr. Nono to the headquarters and give him a tour of the place. There are many seniors stationed at the headquarters, feel free to direct any questions you have to them.”

When facing a genius, naturally he was allowed some form of special treatment. Furthermore, the method of choice for the Eagle’s Nest was to allow everyone to progress at their own pace and not interfere too much with the students. This did not apply only to Nono; it was also the case for the genius from last year, Klaibe, who has since been promoted into a senior of the elite Black-Clothed Generals, with the title of Demonic Shadow Duncan. This was all part of their tradition.

“Since this is your first time in the headquarters, I should tell you this. If you’re interested in challenging any seniors over here, you can select one senior to challenge daily. Take note that this refers to Close Quarters Combat and not a mech battle,” it was almost as if Sofia had already seen through Garen’s character, and not wanting to beat around the bush, she went straight to the point.

“Alright.”

Garen nodded.

The surrounding students started to mumble aloud, challenging seniors was everyone’s right after all. Once you’ve entered the Eagle’s Nest, your ranking here is determined by your actual potential and abilities. Challenging stronger opponents was key in this type of ranking system.

However, these ranks would not give you too much of an advantage, it mainly allows you to access journals and notes on the Crouched Eagle Talon Technique left behind by seniors of the past. These archives of information were all from the masters who had trained in the Crouched Eagle Talon Technique in the past and contained information from the various methods and the different aspects of mastering this technique. However, if you failed to reach a certain level with these techniques, it would have adverse side effects on your body, so it’s better not to fly too close to the sun.

The two’s conversation was short and concise with no small talk in between. Just by looking at Garen, she knew that he would be interested in these challenges and archives. Most people would have already understood that Garen was interested in the archived records of the Eagle’s Nest. For a technique to be practiced after such a long time, yet still remain unparalleled in strength, naturally, it must have had its own unique complexities and theories behind it.

The young girl known as Peach, who was also the cute girl that was in charge of the new members earlier, stood up and guided Garen towards a nearby bus station. Following closely behind them was a group of students, all curious about the developments of Garen, leaving only a handful of students in Sofia’s class.

Looking at this situation, Sofia helplessly let out a sigh. She might as well just bring everyone along at this point.

With that, a whole class of students boarded the academy’s bus, leaving the drilling grounds as they headed towards the direction of the Eagle’s Nest.

******

The Eagle’s Nest was a medium-sized den-like structure in the Blackboard Academy. It looked like a gigantic eagle’s nest on the surface, but in actuality, it was constructed from reinforced metal alloys.

The inside of the building was separated into a few different sections, one of which was the training hall.

Above the white ground of the training hall was a transparent glass ceiling. At this moment, the hall was surrounded by various students stationed at the Eagle’s Nest, most of them being second-years and third-years. A lot of them were casually chatting while spectating the two people below.

Following Sofia’s lead, Garen was brought to the side of the hall, looking down at the two below.

“Today’s challenge is between the two below. Katja, who is ranked thirty-second, is challenging Seris, who is ranked twenty-first,” Sofia softly introduced the two to Garen.

“These two look like they’re quite strong, otherwise, the people who followed us just now wouldn’t have left their positions to observe the battle themselves,” Garen nodded.

“That’s no surprise. The Eagle’s Nest serves as a gathering place for all students practicing the Crouched Eagle Talon Technique. Just the Level Five experts would already amount to more than fifty people, with a lot of them being instructors or Black-Clothed Generals. Some even attained high ranks in the military and take up important positions throughout the Blackboard Region. Although our Crouched Eagle Talon is no match for students of the same level practicing other skills, we have the advantage of numbers!” Sofia proudly exclaimed. “We don’t have the strongest technique, but the value of mastering this technique is definitely comparable to even the best techniques, it is one of a kind.”

“That’s true,” Garen nodded once again.

“There are numerous geniuses within the Eagle’s Nest, and some of them were even in a situation like yours; people who just barely missed the opportunity to become elite students. It might be worthwhile for you guys to interact and befriend each other in the future,” Sofia suggested.

Garen agreed and continued to watch the battle happening below him. The two stopped talking and the surrounding spectators also quietened down, closely observing the bout that was about to start.

Ding!

With a loud ring, the two people below sprang into action.

Their movements were almost in sync, making wide hand motions with every step. At the same time, they were rapidly striking at each other. Although it looked like completely normal strikes, it gave off an ever-changing strong aura.

Smack! The two crossed arms. To everyone’s surprise, they were using the exact same move on equal grounds.

“I see that your training on the Eagle Wing Strike has gone well!” the ranked twenty-first Seris said loudly.

“I’ll definitely defeat you this time!” Katja loudly roared as he lunged forward. His arms were like sharp blades, slicing towards the opponent repeatedly. The action was almost on par with an actual completed Secret Technique, with very few flaws when it came to both attacking and defending.

This sent a shiver down Garen’s spine.

“Their actions are all meticulously calculated and simulated with a quantum calculator, down to every slightest movement. Every possible flaw that they find will be countered with intense training for the scenario. This is the greatest advantage of combining technology with traditional training. In the Eagle’s Nest, you also have access to a huge bonus. You can use the Martial Arts Servers passed down from the seniors to undergo countless simulations to improve your own martial arts,” Sofia explained to Garen. “These simulations will use countless variables to intricately calculate and pinpoint the biggest flaws that your techniques and errors may present within the shortest amount of time. With proper utilization of this, it would produce results equal to ten years of personal training.”

“With these forms of strict training, there shouldn’t be many people who managed to achieve it, right?” Garen asked softly.

“Of course not. There were only three people in the entire history of the Eagle’s Nest who managed to complete the Martial Arts Server’s training fully. The best possible combat style for the Crouched Eagle Talon is not something that can be easily achieved,” Sofia looked at Garen in amazement; she didn’t think he would be able to understand this much just from her brief introductions.

“The Martial Arts Simulation Servers have every noteworthy technique, experience, and information since the creation of the Eagle’s Nest up till now saved in its memory bank. It can calculate the best way to maximize one’s potential through an analysis of one’s physical and mental capabilities. Of course, this requires some authorization. We call this the ‘Flawless Martial Arts’ technique, and it requires a higher level of authorization for the members to access this technology.”

“That’s understandable,” Garen nodded.

The two stopped talking once again, closely observing the battle occurring right below them.

In the training hall below, Katja was starting to get pushed back by Seris, forcing him into a corner. The two were both using Flawless Martial Arts, but he obviously had more flaws than his opponent. In a battle with both sides having equal speed and strength, he would undoubtedly be in a disadvantageous position.

Almost as if he was dissatisfied with himself being forced into a disadvantageous position, Katja turned around, his arms suddenly turned completely red. It wasn’t the red you saw from swellings, but rather a red comparable to the color of fresh blood.

“Don’t get too cocky! Swooping Eagle Slaughter!!” a twisted form of Willpower started to boil from Katja’s body, creating vortex-like cones of wind that wrapped around his arms. It almost looked like two electric drills was attached to Katja’s arms as he lunged towards Seris.

“A Willpower secret skill? Do you think you’re the only one who can use something like that?” Seris laughed. “Extreme Pierce!”

He pointed out his index fingers, each finger pointing at one of Katja’s arms. The fingers rapidly turned black as they swelled with blood, to the point where they looked like they had become gigantic blood clots. The air surrounding him started to whirl up like a hurricane.

“Katja has lost,” Looking at the stage, Garen exclaimed.

“Oh?” Sofia looked at him curiously. “You have really great eyesight huh?”

“Is going down for the challenges the fastest way to raise your rank and gain authorization?” Garen wanted to experience what this Flawless Martial Arts simulation room feels like. After all, it was his first time seeing such high-tech martial arts training.

“The Flawless Martial Arts system is most effectively utilized for finding your own flaws, but only the top fifty in the ranks are authorized to access this technology. Don’t look down on this ranking,” Sofia reminded, “The three geniuses I’ve trained in the past, they all started off arrogant just like you, challenging the seniors immediately after they entered. However, none of them managed to win their first two battles.”

“It’s fine,” Garen shook his head as he started walking towards the stage. “I’ll give it a shot.”

He wasn’t just interested in the Flawless Martial Arts, but also the Willpower secret skills the two had used just now. The feeling those skills gave off, it felt like they were using their Willpower in similar manners to how people use their internal energy in wuxia novels.

Moves utilizing Willpower would be much faster and stronger, and they could even enter the opponent’s body and cause pure physical damage to the body. Through his observations, he noticed that the two had the capabilities to release their Willpower from long ranges, but they did not attempt to do so. This meant that the techniques they used weren’t that high leveled.

Katja was knocked down on the floor, his face completely flushed red. Other than that, he seemed to be fine. Seris walked up to him and helped him up.

At this moment, Garen had entered the training hall from one of the entrances, closely assessing the two from a closer distance.

He didn’t feel anything from afar, but with a closer look at this distance, he realized that these two were both Level Three experts! No wonder they were in the top fifty of the Eagle’s Nest, they weren’t just some random characters.

However, after pondering for a bit, There were hundreds of Level Five professors and instructors within the whole Blackboard Academy, it wasn’t surprising that there were even more Level Three or Four reserves present. After all, this was the place with the strongest people in the Blackboard Region.

This two seemed to already be at the level of the fifth-years, having already gone through half of the eight-year education system of the Blackboard Academy. However, being able to attain Level Three at this stage was still a great feat.

No longer paying attention to the interactions between the two, Garen walked towards the white stone plaque erected at the side of the hall. The plaque displayed the rankings of the members of the Eagle’s Nest, listing everyone in the top fifty.

The first person on the list was someone called Sajeena, with Level Five Willpower. This was recorded two years ago, when she was a sixth-year, it should be nearing her graduation soon.

At this point, Sofia had finally caught up to him. Following behind her were a group of youths that seemed interested in what was happening over here. They all gave off a strong aura with their Willpower; it seemed that all of them were very skilled students.

“You want to challenge someone now?” Sofia looked at this genius who had just joined this group. Geniuses were all the same after all; he had the same mentality as the other two geniuses she brought in before. When they saw someone who was stronger than them, they were unable to resist the urge to challenge them, hoping to become stronger.

“The students of our Blackboard Academy take pride in their strengths, and wanting to take on challenges is only natural. Take your pick; if the name is glowing, it means that they are currently present in the Eagle’s Nest. Of course, those selected have the right to reject three challenges a day. Furthermore, no grudges should be held if anyone is injured in the battle,” a proper-looking bespectacled young lad next to Sofia said in a soft voice.

“My name is Anjay Terin, ranked fifteenth. I heard the freshmen’s First Seat had just joined us, so I came over to have a look.”

“Nice to meet you,” Garen shook his hand. “What’s the minimum authorization required to use the Flawless Martial Arts simulations?” Garen was no longer overly prideful. This world was not one where he could simply mess around in. These Willpower experts were quick-thinkers, had amazing battle senses, had more experience in the mysterious power form manipulating their Willpower, and could often have a terrifying explosiveness when it comes to their strengths. Seeing as his own Willpower manipulation was still very limited, he felt that it was best not to be too full of himself.

“Everyone within the top fifty will receive authorization to access it, but the amount of time allocated to you would also vary with rank. Those at the top ranks are even authorized to organize competitions and tournaments with the other clubs. So what do you think? Want to give it a shot?” this guy had a gentle and polite tone, but he seemed to be a battle-loving individual underneath the surface.

Interestingly, it seemed that everyone Garen had come across in the Eagle’s Nest seemed to have this sort of personality. They all seemed to be very passionate about battles and have a strong desire to improve themselves.

Chapter 846: Actual Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Why not?” Garen replied with a cheeky grin, revealing his pearly whites.

He turned his head towards the plaque and looked at the glowing names on the list. Randomly, he picked the guy at the forty-eighth rank.

The light flashed momentarily, symbolizing that the fellow had rejected his challenge.

Picking another person, he selected the one at rank forty-two this time. Once again, the light flashed briefly, showing that his challenge was rejected.

“At this rate, it seems like no one would want to face me. I guess it’s because I’m still a nobody who has no rank, so they probably see me as just a small fry,” Garen frowned at Sofia and Anjay Terin.

“I have an idea,” Anjay smiled, his smile gave off a sly vibe. “I haven’t pwned noobs [1] in a long time. How about I personally come on to let you try?”

“You?” Garen calmly looked him in the eye. His heart was starting to fill up with a sense of adrenaline, it was the feeling of his Willpower flowing through his arms as if the Crouched Eagle Talons itself had the “battle-loving” attribute.

“Senior, are you not afraid of being overthrown?”

“It all depends on the person claiming they can overthrow me,” Anjay Terin started to chuckle as shapeless waves started to ripple from his body. It turned out that he was a level four expert.

This sent a chill up Garen’s spine.

“Get onto the stage! Newbies tend to have an air of arrogance when they first join. I still remember the first day where I was dissatisfied just like you when I was being wrecked by my seniors. If you’re dissatisfied, then get up on the stage and give it your all!” Anjay Terin took off his clothes and walked up to the stage. The other two from earlier had already left the stage and the surrounding spectators also prepared to take their leave. However, as they saw the ranked fifteenth Anjay Terin walking up to the stage preparing to fight, most people stopped and turned back. A few people started asking around about what’s going to happen. Meanwhile, Sofia and company, who were the only ones who knew about the situation, started receiving countless notifications from their watches.

Garen’s vision flashed for a moment as he also walked up to the stage. Stripping off his clothes he threw it down the stage, miraculously hanging it onto the clothes rack at below the stage.

He had already adapted to the basics of the Crouched Eagle Talon technique. Along with his training for the basic Divine Statue Technique, he had managed to vastly increase the hardness of his two arms. Although he hadn’t faced off against a Crouched Eagle Talon user of the same level yet, he was confident that he wouldn’t be weaker than someone of the same level.

Garen felt that he was like a new expert who had just started training his Internal Energy, whilst the Eagle’s Nest was a large established Martial Arts Sect that was filled with countless skilled elders, all with their own experiences and battle capabilities.

As the two got onto the stage, the surrounding chatter got louder and louder. More and more people learned about the identities of the two on stage right now. One was a veteran expert, whilst the other was the debuting freshmen First Seat who had just started training in the Crouched Eagle Talon Technique.

Just based on the difference in Willpower, most people wouldn’t even blink an eye at Garen. Although the entire academic break has passed, approximately 6 months have passed since the tournament, but at the time of the tournament, Garen had only displayed a Level One Willpower. He did not engage in any Willpower counterattacks, so at best, he would only be at a Level Two.

At this Level of Willpower, going up against a Level Four Willpower expert, undoubtedly he would be utterly destroyed.

Of course, as he stepped onto the stage, he started to feel something awry. The man standing on the opposite end, Anjay Terin, had almost no weak spots on his body, and the only two points that seemed flawed looked like a bait for the enemy. This would’ve lured in the average youth, but for someone like Garen, he could easily detect the legitimacy of the weak spots.

“Ranked fifteenth… so this is what Level Four Willpower feels like? The Eagle’s Nest is amazing!” Garen exclaimed in excitement.

“Come! The strong shall stand tall! Let’s start!” Anjay Terin seemed to be hyped up by the momentum of going onto the stage, his eyes were opened wide as his body slowly emitted a strong energy field.

“Alright!”

Garen felt as if he was back in the Secret Technique World where his aura had been unparalleled, and he started to feel his passion rising up within him.

In his first step, he chained a few stomps off the stage, propelling him towards his opponent. It wasn’t any special technique, it was just a simple strike. He was not using the Ten Thousand True Technique, he even suppressed his own body’s abilities, reverting himself into the level of an average human being, all of this just to fully experience the true potential and ability of the Crouched Eagle Talon Technique.

“You’ve got guts!” Anjay Terin laughed out loud, his right arm transforming into a claw in response to the incoming attack.

Without any fancy tricks, the two clashed.

Clunk!!

The two of them were both knocked back by two steps, both glaring at each other with a sense of amazement.

“Great Eagle Claw! Once more!” Garen coldly huffed, his two arms smoothly raised up like a giant eagle, lunging fiercely at his opponent. Strangely, his feet were repeatedly kicking as he was in the air, these kicks seemed to cause a small gust, allowing him to manipulate his direction in the air. The two claws were slashing through the air, creating a loud screech. If these were real claws, they would be able to easily slice through even the hardest metal boards.

The spectating students were completely stunned, and those who had originally looked down on Garen started to change their impression on him. This freshmen First Seat had far exceeded their imaginations.

“It’s Level three! This degree of strength and hardness is at the very least Level three. Look at the color of his skin, it has a glow unlike other people, it’s obviously strengthened using some form of genetic potion, or else there’s no way it could have this sort of change. However, what sort of genetic potion did he use to be able to increase the hardness of his flesh to such an absurd level?”

Sofia could tell just with a glance that Garen’s arms were not normal, this was not something that could be achieved purely through the use of one’s Willpower.

“What a fearsome strike, Anjay Terin might have to use his full potential,” another boy started to nod in agreement.

“That might be true, but I can’t help but feel that there’s still something up that Nono’s sleeve,” Sofia shook her head.

At this point, the tides of the battle had started to change.

Garen had already changed his direction mid-air thrice now, and even Anjay Terin was taken aback by this strange move, though he still managed to immediately respond to it. Without a second thought, he stretched out his arms, creating two black slashes through the air, almost like an eagle’s claws awaiting the incoming attack.

“You think I’d be afraid of you!?” he roared loudly. Using his Willpower, he increased his movement speed to the extreme, to the point where a trail of his silhouette was visible, lunging straight towards Garen.

“Eagle Dragon!!”

With a loud pant, Anjay Terin’s claws made contact with Garen’s palms.

The two collided briefly, creating a huge crash. Garen was flung back, furiously stomping on the ground to stop the momentum and leaving countless deep footprints on the ground.

What was weird was that his palms had started to emit some white smoke as if he had just been scorched by something, and his skin was still red hot.

“Nono isn’t the only one who can strengthen himself with a genetic potion,” a few of the students at the side of the hall started laughing.

“It’s Anjay Terin’s Fire Snake Strengthening Potion! So that’s the awesomeness of a potion that can only be obtained with a huge sum of cash!”

“That Nono isn’t bad himself, if it was just another Level three, he would have been critically wounded by that one strike just now!”

The surrounding crowd started to make more noise.

Garen remained expressionless as he moved his palms around for a bit. The white smoke from his palms started to dissipate, the high temperature leaving no damage on his palms at all. This left the opposing Anjay Terin completely stunned.

“Was that a Willpower secret skill?” Garen asked.

“Of course not! This was just a gene strengthening potion, if I use my Willpower secret technique, it would cause a huge mess, you’re just a newbie after…”

“It’s fine,” Garen interrupted. “Your other moves shouldn’t have any effects, I’m only interested in your Willpower secret skills.”

Being interrupted was supposed to be something rude, but Anjay Terin seemed to reveal a hungry smile. Although he looked like a gentle person, in actuality, he was someone who loved to battle and fight. Seeing someone like Garen who liked to talk with his fists, he felt completely refreshed.

“I’ll let you have a taste of my Willpower secret skill then!”

Just as he finished his sentence, he raised his arms up high, leaving a silhouette in front of his body.

“Blink!!!”

In an instant, Anjay Terin seemed to have disappeared into thin air, leaving an ear-piercing boom in the air. In that instance, his speed was raised to an extreme degree.

At this speed, almost within a blink of an eye, he could leap a few meters in distance. Even with Garen’s amazing reflexes, he wouldn’t be able to respond in time. It felt like his opponent had disregarded air resistance and his entire body was engulfed and supported purely with Willpower. In a blink of an eye, he had already been hit.

At that moment, Garen felt the same feeling that he had felt when he fought with the Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia.

With a loud bang, Garen was sent flying. Even though his arms had reflexively put up a guard and blocked the blow in front of him, it still connected. With this hit, he flew through the air as if he was a human cannonball, crashing into the wall surrounding the stage.

This was the fearsomeness of a high-level Willpower, it could largely strengthen and support the pilot’s physical body, and in the process, create terrifying explosive power. The strength of the Crouched Eagle Talon Technique lay within this terrifying explosive speed and the strength and sturdiness of the arms. For an expert who was ranked fifteenth, this used up almost half of Anjay Terin’s power.

“It’s the end.”

That was the one notion all the spectators had in their heads.

After being hit by a direct hit from Anjay Terin’s Willpower secret skill, even just the impact from the Willpower was enough to have Nonosiva kick the bucket, but now with his arms under influence of the genetic strengthening potion, he wouldn’t even stand a chance.

However, to everyone’s surprise, a low laugh started ringing from inside the walls.

“Heh… Hehehehe…” Garen couldn’t help but laugh, “Not bad… this type of enemy… This era…”

The fearsomeness and explosiveness of Willpower attacks, this let Garen finally understand why there were no secret techniques being developed in this era.

The reason was that the humans of this world have already found another path that led them to a similar strength.

If one were to see secret techniques as a way of enhancing oneself with the goal of evolution, then Willpower secret skills would be creating a whole new power with the goal of changing oneself.

If the two were compared, it would be like the contrast between a warrior and a wizard. A warrior would be able to maintain his strength at all times while having a strong aura, while a wizard could obtain an explosive strength for a short period of time, having an immensely high offensive output, but low vitality.

If this hit had landed on any other Level Three Willpower student, he would undoubtedly be severely wounded. However, Garen was different; he had 3 times the vitality of a normal person in addition to the amazing regenerative properties of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique. This strike was merely a scratch on someone like him.

However, judging from this strike, this Anjay Terin had at least half the level of his actual offensive prowess.

Licking his lips, Garen felt a sense of passion and excitement he had never felt since he had entered this world. In his last world, he had no worthy opponent; he had already been unparalleled in strength from the moment he was born, and standing at the top without a rival was an exceptionally boring feeling. However, in this world, there were existences which could destroy even stars, and he had also experienced the potential power of a Willpower secret skill.

Garen could finally afford to be serious…

Looking at Anjay Terin who seemingly started to tremble slightly, Garen let out a smile. His body started to emit a monstrous beast-like aura.

Crack… As he walked out from the dent of the wall, rubble started to fall off from behind him. Amazingly, there wasn’t any sign of wounds on his body, and even that light wound from earlier had already completely recovered.

“Be careful,” before he even finished the sentence, Garen had completely vanished. “Ten Thousand True Technique, Destruction!”

A clear white airwave sliced through the air, heading towards Anjay Terin.

Anjay Terin steeled himself, his body once again bursting with the strong shapeless energy field from earlier.

“Blink!!”

With a loud roar, he aimed his claws as he lunged towards his opponent.

Chapter 847: Difference 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Their arms clashed and created a shockwave that rippled through the hall, sending the surrounding dust flying all over the place.

Garen and Anjay Terin were having a fierce bout. As their arms collided at high speeds, they gave out loud clunks as if two pieces of metal were hitting against each other.

Without using any other techniques and purely the abilities within his arms, Garen managed to force Anjay Terin into a corner within just a few seconds. Using only just one arm, he could block his opponent’s two-handed attacks. With each swipe, he could completely parry his opponent’s attacks.

His other hand reached into the space between them and his palm struck Anjay Terin directly in the chest.

Bam!

With a strike on Anjay Terin’s chest, his face immediately turned pale. Backing up a few steps to regain his stability, he looked at this freshmen First Seat. At that moment, he had no idea what to say as his pale face had patches of red. Seeing this sight, the whole training hall fell silent.

Bit-by-bit, Anjay Terin started to feel that this freshman Nonosiva’s martial arts were almost as flawless as his. More importantly, his every action and skill gave off an indescribable sense of suppression. This type of feeling wasn’t the bloodlust you felt from the top-ranked students who were experts in actual battles, it felt more like… an indescribable fear-inducing feeling.

“For you to reach this Level at this age… I’ve underestimated you,” Anjay Terin clutched at his chest as his face turned even paler.

“You’re not bad yourself,” Garen shook his head slightly. “Continue?”

“I…” Anjay Terin wanted to say something, but he was interrupted by another voice.

“Leave this to me, Anjay.”

Nearby, a man with long black hair jumped up to the stage with a flip. Taking off his black jacket, he threw it towards his friend.

“Barry?” Anjay Terin stopped talking and he opted to leave the stage as instructed. Right before he left, he gave Garen a word of caution, “Be careful, this is fellow is ranked seventh, and he has a bad temper.”

Garen nodded, accepting his opponent’s good intentions. He shifted his sight towards the man who had just arrived on the stage. This Barry guy seemed to be surrounded by a black mist, giving off a mysterious vibe.

“Rank seven… He looks different from the others,” he felt that his opponent’s mental will was almost like it’s not from just one person, but rather, a culmination of two people’s wills.

“Level 3 Willpower. To be able to utilize it to this level was solely due to your physical body’s capabilities,” Barry’s line of sight seemed as if it could scan through everything, almost as if his eyes were faintly flashing with a white dot of light.

Garen felt a chill in his heart. He remained silent, glaring at his new opponent.

“Your vitality is terrifying. It should either be from being submerged in a strengthening potion or from some genetic altering ray. However, that doesn’t matter,” Barry smiled. “All of these are irrelevant. Although your vitality can increase your body’s defense and speed, only pure Willpower suppression stands above all.”

“Pure Willpower suppression?” Garen raised his guard, as he was still not very familiar with the true Willpower secret skills and he could only base his reactions on his observations. His opponent was an expert who was ranked seventh. Out of all the people practicing the Crouched Eagle Talon in Blackboard Academy, he was among the top ranks of the pyramid. Looking at his age and aura, he didn’t seem like a rookie when it came to actual killing. This kind of opponent was enough for him to actually fight with full seriousness.

“As a fellow genius from the Eagle’s Nest, let me show you some pointers…!!” before the word “pointers” even finished, Barry waved his right arm. His arm was like a sharp blade, slicing through the air, shooting forth a bloody and sweet aura. A shadow of an arm started forming in the air, almost like a snake, slithering towards Garen.

On the ground, all things touched by the arm’s shadow started losing their color as if they were starting to rot. This displayed the terrifying power of the shadow’s toxicity, as something as durable as the alloy ground had started to rot just within an instant, if it was human skin, the person would be instantly disintegrated.

“Poison!” Garen frowned as he immediately jumped back, dodging the shadow’s pursuit. However, a poisonous mist had started to engulf the opponent in a few meters’ radius, and there was no way for Garen to enter.

Barry stood at the center of the stage like a curled up porcupine; there was no way to get close to him.

Bam!

The shadow of another arm struck Garen from behind. Although Garen managed to dodge in time, there was still some black mist sticking onto him. This black mist felt as if it has a mind of their own, slowly moving around on Garen’s skin as it pleased. With a shake, Garen managed to get it off of him.

The two continued on in this cat and mouse battle, with one on the offensive while the other remaining on the defensive. Unconsciously, Garen was completely suppressed.

Even though he had not released the restraints of he placed on his body, his opponent still managed to suppress him using Willpower secret skills. This gave Garen a sense of excitement; if a rank seven fellow was able to unleash this amount of battle potential without a mech, it showed how fearsome Willpower support could be.

For a pilot with a strong Willpower, even without his mech, he would still have the battle prowess of an expert in internal energy, and so defeating an average person would be completely effortless. The development of their own cells had reached an absurd level.

Thinking of this, Garen finally started to loosen the restraints on his body. At the end of the day, these people had a stronger Willpower than him, but their vitality was not that much different from an average person’s. Take Barry whom he was currently facing for example, based on his reflexes and physical strength, he had at most 1.2 or 1.3 times the vitality of an average person. In other words, he was only that much stronger than the average person. This also displayed how Willpower training could only support your capabilities for a brief moment. Without the support, his capabilities were no different from an average person’s.

After Garen made sure of the difference between secret techniques and Willpower secret skills, without uttering a single word, he lunged forward, straightened his palm as if it was a knife, and fiercely struck forward.

Whoosh!!

With a screech, his palm created a shapeless air flow, dispersing the poison mist in front of him. Taking advantage of the poison mist being dissipated, he immediately charged, throwing a fist at Barry’s direction.

“Poison Pond!” Barry opened his mouth as the Willpower in his body started bursting out. That wasn’t a Level Four Willpower, it was Level Five!

A strong Willpower started to flow out in all directions as a formless energy field, almost like a huge wave, that crashed towards Garen’s body.

He was flung back and his legs skidded along the ground, leaving long black marks; even the soles of his leather shoes had been completely burned through.

Garen’s body was completely engulfed in his own Willpower in order to protect him from the damage caused by the opponent’s poison mist. However, he started to feel a searing pain in his mind; it seemed like his Willpower had been damaged, and it would need some time to heal.

A Level Five against a Level Three, as expected, the difference was still quite a large leap. If not for Garen’s monstrous vitality, he would probably have been knocked out cold.

Silently standing in the same spot, Garen could hear the shouts of amazement from all around him. Most of them were in admiration of Barry’s terrifying poison technique, but there were also a few that were praising him. For someone who had just entered the Eagle’s Nest, even as the freshmen First Seat, he’d managed to hold his own against so many attacks by Barry, who stood at rank seven.

Garen had restrained his own physical capabilities to that of an above average human. Even so, he did not expect that even with his myriad of battle experience, he would be forced into a corner by an opponent to the extent where he had his Willpower damaged. This was obviously the result of his unfamiliarity of his opponent’s abilities. That last Willpower wave was something that could not be dodged. It was a wave that spread in all directions, and the only counter was hard defense.

Squinting his eyes, Garen simulated the battle if he had released all his restraints. The end result would’ve been a tie, leaving both parties heavily damaged. His opponent’s poison techniques were dangerous, but he could still take on the poison damage if he dealt a Hail Mary attack, heavily damaging his opponent.

This gave Garen a sense of exhilaration; he had almost reached the epitome of power in the Secret Techniques World, but here, he was already being suppressed by a pilot without his mech. Although he no longer had the monstrous Divine Statue Technique, just with his body’s diverse battle experiences, he could only reach such a level. If that was the case, how strong would the pilots of an even higher rank be?

However, his current physical capabilities were still small, it was only 3 times the average person, and he was still far from his actual level back in that world, much less his level in the Totem World. This result was expected.

Garen was in shock on this end, not knowing that Barry on the other end was even more shocked.

“This bastard… This bastard is a bloody monster!!” although Barry remained calm on the surface, he was trembling on the inside.

“Out of all the Level Five pilots, I have the best physical capabilities! From reflexes, vitality, strength, to speed, all of it had been strengthened using special potions, and I’d even been through multiple genetic alteration rays. My physical capabilities should have far exceeded the average human’s! I can unleash my body’s full potential up to 100%! Even those military experts who had undergone special training shouldn’t even be a match for me!”

Barry’s mind was in complete turmoil.

“Only those martial artists who have spent their lives practicing purely martial arts should have better physical capabilities than me! How can this freshman…” Barry’s pursuit to strengthen his physical capabilities was something that even most traditional Level Five pilots could not attain.

There weren’t many pilots who would focus so much on training their physical bodies because their strength lay within their mechs. No matter how strong their physical body was, when up against even the weakest mechs, they would still be completely destroyed. Rather than spending time on their physical bodies, most people would spend more time training in their respective mechs.

This had caused most people to pursue strength by focusing solely on their Willpower. When it came to physical capabilities, Barry was already considered among the cream of the crop.

Barry was someone who had participated in countless combat tournaments in the Blackboard Region, even winning two gold medals and a silver medal! He had also worked part-time as a tutor for a few generals and their combat training before. He was someone who had crawled back from the depths of hell itself.

Suppressing his trembling heart, he cleared his throat.

“How long have you trained in combat?”

The two were no longer in battle, they just stood opposite each other. Hearing his opponent’s question, Garen felt that both sides had no intent to continue.

“I started when I was young. Why do you ask?”

This opponent’s reflexes were even faster that Anjay Terin’s from earlier. He also had great battle senses, and he’d chosen an extremely appropriate timing to activate his explosive Willpower. He was a worthy opponent.

The white dots in Barry’s eyes started to light up once more. He carefully scanned Garen once more and started to frown.

“You chose a wrong path… No matter how strong your body is, you still stand no chance against a mech. A pilot’s path relies on Willpower, over-strengthening one’s body is a waste of time and energy and will cause one to lose focus. You should have been able to progress even faster.”

“My Willpower is already fast enough…” Garen lightly shook his head.

Barry let out a sigh.

“How meaningless. Your physical capabilities are strong, and you are able to stand on equal grounds with me in this current situation. But, once we step into a mech, believe me when I say I will be able to destroy you in one hit,” he calmly said while pointing his index finger at him.

Garen’s heart trembled slightly. His sharp five senses could tell that everything his opponent said was the truth. There was no sign of any joking or mockery, it was a sincere statement.

Chapter 848: Difference 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Barry shook his head.

“No matter how amazing your martial arts are, you will never be comparable to even the weakest Mech. The legendary strongest martial artist Cheng Xingyao from the Mother Planet Federation two centuries ago was rumored to have been able to break a boulder with a strike and kill a rhinoceros or an elephant with a fist. However, his body was barely on par with a Level Two radioactive mutated creature. That is the extent of the human body, regardless of any trick you use. On the other hand, a Level Two creature can easily be defeated by a Level Two pilot in a Mech. Two Level Two Mechs will be able to defeat a Level Three creature, while Mater Cheng Xingyao died in the claws of a level Three creature.”

His speech was extremely blunt as there was nothing for him to hide. Countless Eagle’s Nest students around them also nodded in agreement with his statement. All of a sudden, the chattering of discussions filled the hall; this topic that Barry had brought up had sparked the conversation between students about the topic of what was the healthy balance between Mech training and physical training.

Barry sincerely looked at Garen.

“Let me give you a word of advice, a pilot’s strength lies in his Mech. A high Leveled Mech can destroy the world, as such, only a high leveled pilot can reach the piloting requirements. With every level, the increase in strength of the Mech is something that far exceeds what a human alone can achieve. On the other hand, even if you forgo training for just a day, your body will start to become weaker. Think about that!”

He turned around and jumped off the stage. Grabbing his jacket, he walked out of the training hall with his friends who were accompanying him from earlier.

Garen had not uttered a word since the very beginning; he was listening silently to him.

He understood that his opponent had good intentions, they were fellow Eagle’s Nest students after all. They were both Crouched Eagle Talon practitioners and, in the eyes of outsiders, from the same group. His opponent honestly hoped that he could carefully think about this problem.

However, what they didn’t know was that his Willpower was raised solely just by having the Life Secret Technique. Giving up his pursuit of secret techniques would mean giving up his own growth, causing the growth of his Willpower to come to an abrupt halt. Even the slightest improvements would take a minimum of 10 years.

“Unless you can hold your own against a Mech, a human’s strength alone is nothing but an illusion,” as Garen jumped down, Sofia too gave him some advice.

Anjay Terin also nodded in agreement,

Garen became silent.

“Can you show me the actual difference?”

The two looked at each other.

“Allow me,” Sofia nodded. His performance on stage earlier had already fully displayed Nonosiva’s innate talent as a genius, surpassing even the likes of other Elite Students. Managing to reach a Level Three Willpower when he was still a second-year, it was enough for her to invest her attention in him.

“Follow me.”

******

Half an hour later…

The three of them, followed by a group of curious students, arrived at the simulation battle area.

Countless Battlenet stations were neatly arranged in this area. Every pair of stations were placed opposing each other as if symbolizing a duel between the two.

“This is where most duels take place. Go on, battle simulations don’t cost anything, and it’s the safest method,” Sofia explained as she entered the cockpit on the right and laid back.

Garen followed suit and entered the left cockpit.

Closing his eyes, the Nerve Link Equipment connected itself to his head.

Shooop!

He opened his eyes to a pitch black scene. Suddenly, a line of text flashed in front of his eyes.

‘Welcome to Eagle’s Nest Battlegrounds. Please enter your name.’

“Nonosiva,” Garen answered softly.

‘Name verified. Ranking unknown. Please wait shortly while initializing background…’ the text changed and disappeared after a brief moment.

After a while, a bright light flashed in front of Garen’s eyes. After his eyes adjusted to the sudden change in brightness, he observed his surroundings.

He was standing in the middle of a wide silver and white hall with a floor that was smooth and flat and seemingly made entirely from alloyed metal. On his right was a black wall with a metal emblem of a black sword and shield embedded at the center. On his right was a huge glass window pane, revealing a beautiful sunset. There were even a couple of airships and battleships slowly drifting through the sky.

‘Virtual background initialization complete. Please select your Mech,’ an electronic voice rang in his ears.

Garen moved his body around and noticed a rectangular screen that had appeared in front of him. The screen displayed the silhouettes of the different Mechs available.

There were Mechs ranging from Level One all the way to Level Five, but due to his Willpower Level, he was limited to only Level Three and lower Mechs. Directly tapping on the image of the Level Three Mech, Garen started to read the details of each of the Mechs.

After perusing for a moment, Garen selected the Mech that he liked the most.

‘Wings of Freedom: Level Three Strength-Type Mech. A standard issue Mech used by the Erlan military. Firepower Level Three, Speed Level Three, Defense Level Two, Strength Level Two. Special Equipment Skill: Heart of Freedom. Gains explosive speed for a short period of time. Increase the user’s speed by one level. When this skill ends, decreases the user’s strength by one level for ten seconds.’

This Mech was completely blue, and it seemed to be a Dragonlance wielding slender knight. It had a pointy helmet, revealing only the nose and the mouth below the eyes. It gave off a mysterious charm.

He tapped on the image of the WIngs of Freedom. Immediately, Garen felt his surroundings shift. In the blink of an eye, he was now seated inside a blue cockpit, and there was a bright circular screen in front of him, displaying the situation outside.

On the surrounding blue walls, there were countless lines connected to the various controls and lights.

“You’ve finished selecting your Mech? The Wings of Freedom, huh?” on the opposite side of the hall, a dark red Mech appeared out of nowhere. It was also a humanoid form, but it was dual wielding a pair of rapiers and lightly tapping them together to create a crisp clanking sound. That Mech didn’t have any outstanding features, giving off a very plain vibe.

“My Mech is the lowest tier Level Five Mech, the Red Fish,” Sofia introduced. “I purposely selected the worst Level five Mech to demonstrate how the difference in Willpower levels can have a terrifying difference in strength when it comes to manipulating a Mech.”

Garen did not answer. He manipulated the Mech to move its limbs around a bit.

“Ready?” the Red Fish raised one of its rapiers.

“Okay,” Garen responded.

“Be careful. What I’m going to use is the Red Fish Mech’s most basic move, the Rushing Cross Slash. It is a basic move that any Level Five pilot will be able to use,” Sofia responsibly explained her next move.

“Understood. Come at me!” Garen readied his Mech. At Level Three Willpower, he could already completely stop relying on the Moonfang, allowing him to freely control the Mech. The agility, speed, reflexes and strength stats of a Level Three Mech shocked him. This Level Three Mech had an equivalent to the combined stats of two Level One Mechs. This was not just a simple equation of “1+1=2”. In an actual battle, one Level Three Mech would be able to defeat ten level One Mechs at once.

“Careful!” Sofia once again warned. “Rushing Cross Slash!”

The lights at the Red Fish’s feet started flashing red, and its two rapiers were held close to the two sides of its body, their tips before the Mech’s face.

.

Vroom!!

A loud engine ignition sound rang loudly as the Red Fish Mech suddenly had an explosive burst of speed, moving hundreds of meters with just a leap. Thrusting the two rapiers forwards, it left a trail resembling a red cross in the air.

This speed had far exceeded that of the Level Three Mech. Leaping hundreds of meters in an instant and charging straight towards Garen’s Mech, this kind of explosiveness didn’t even allow room for Garen’s Willpower to react and maneuver the Mech away. He had no choice but to forcefully raise his lance up, attempting to use the opponent’s momentum to pierce through it.

Within that short time, it was the best he could do.

However, what exceeded Garen’s expectations was that even at that explosive speed, the Red Fish could still manage to make adjustments to its movements. Leaning the Mech slightly to the right, she managed to catch the Dragonlance right below the Mech’s armpit, allowing her to continue charging forward. As she made contact, the rapiers in her hands fiercely slashed through the body of the Wings of Freedom Mech.

Despite Garen already using the skill Heart of Freedom to momentarily increase his speed, he was still far slower than his opponent. In an instant, the chest region of his Mech was slashed through by the rapiers.

His vision suddenly turned to black. Whoosh! Everything surrounding him disappeared, leaving him in a pitch darkness.

‘Pilot Sofia Wins!’ the electronic voice rang out loud once more.

Pshhhh…

The cockpit automatically opened up.

Garen slowly stood up and walked out of the cockpit. Sofia was already a step ahead of him, silently looking at him. The surrounding students who followed him here, including Anjay Terin, were all here. The students started chattering amongst themselves, but Anjay Terin showed an unsurprised look.

“How was it? Were you able to feel the difference now?” Sofia softly asked. “My actual Willpower is only at Level Three, but I was able to use my authorization to alter it and pilot a Level Five Mech. Even though it was the weakest Level Five Mech, you should be able to understand the difference in strength between the levels of the Mechs now. I was also once like you, and I got completely thrashed by a Level four Mech in the past as well.”

“Why is the difference so big?” Garen thought back to the scene at the battlegrounds just now. He now understood that the difference between Mechs had far exceeded his imaginations.

“This is the strongest point of a will-powered Mech – the internal speed-change system. It allows the nerves of the pilot themselves to speed up, and this speed boost will increase based on the Level of the pilot’s Willpower. In the eyes of a pilot, the world after the speed boost will become an extremely slow world, and every action, if not above a certain speed, would be seen as a normal person’s slow movement, almost like the slow-motion effects from movies,” Sofia explained.

“Furthermore, this was only an average level. A high-leveled pilot would even be able to manipulate the Mech to emit an energy field. If the opposing Mech is not at a high enough level, it wouldn’t even be able to get close to it,” Anjay Terin continued solemnly. “For example, the Magnetized Energy Field can create a strong magnetic field that can affect the balance of both the pilot and the Mech. Unless you’re piloting a non-metal Mech, you’d have no hope of even getting remotely close to the opponent’s Mech. You would then be at the mercy of your opponent’s long-range attacks. There’s also the Reflective Energy Field, this is the forte of the White Light Organization. According to the information we have, apparently all Mechs of a lower level than the user, no matter how strong their attacks, would have it reflected right back at them. It’s straight up an unbeatable noob pwning [1] machine!”

Garen started to frown even more. The difference between the Level of Willpower could be greatly amplified by the Mech, increasing it to such a degree. Needless to say, he had underestimated the terror of the will-powered Mechs by a longshot.

“Looks like only a Mech can defeat a Mech… Unless he has an army of people who have mastered secret techniques, or if he reaches the level of a demon lord, he would still be no match for the destructive prowess of a Mech,” Garen finally understood the different levels of the Mechs in this world.

He did use its full potential in that bout just now, but even if his physical capabilities were stronger, against that Mech’s attacks, unless he has reached an impossibly high level, the human body could never withstand the impact of that strike. That strike packed at least a few hundred tonnes of force, and that was only taking into account the physical impact of the strike; it did not factor in the damage from the opponent’s Willpower.

Chapter 849: Investigation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The difference caused by Mechs.

After leaving the Eagle’s Nest, this was the only thing on Garen’s mind.

The entire atmosphere of the Eagle’s Nest had a very upbeat and crazed feeling to it as the members inside were all extremely passionate, though albeit prone to violence. Garen started to faintly feel that this had something to do with the Crouched Eagle Talon training method.

It was even the same for him; he too was starting to be slightly affected after starting to train this technique.

According to Sofia’s description, other training methods would also bear similar side effects. For example, for the Trails of the Wind technique, regardless of the practitioner’s temper, as they mastered the technique, their attitude would have a certain degree of change. They would become more adaptable, agile, varied and quick-thinking.

Another example would be the Brutal Hammer; its practitioners seemed to develop a certain type of attitude. They would become more inclined to use violence and torture, have bad tempers and were overall maniacal.

In comparison, the practitioners of the Crouched Eagle Talon would only become stronger and be more prideful of their strengths.

In the upcoming days, he went to the Eagle’s Nest daily and trained with the experts there. With the help of the Staff of Absolute Yin, he also managed to accumulate more and more potential points. However, before completely mastering his foundations, Garen decided to hold back from using these potential points. There was no meaning in increasing his strength that way; as someone who had trained in secret techniques before, he fully understood the importance of establishing a strong foundation. If the foundation was not stable, even when facing an opponent at the same level, one’s weak point could be easily exploited into an effortless defeat.

In lethal combat, every flaw could be a fatal one. As such, if one did not have a strong foundation, it would cause one to have numerous flaws.

As the days flew by, half a month had passed in a blink of an eye.

In the canteen, at the noisy dining hall.

“What? Baylon is missing?” Garen exclaimed as he looked at his watch.

“Yeah. We had always thought he was working as a live-in full-time worker at that bakery. He would usually contact us every fortnight. This time, when we called over, they said he had left for home a long time ago. But we haven’t even seen Lon in ages!” from the watch screen, he could see that his mother Amy had a worried look on her face. “We’ve tried everything we could, but there were no results. It’s all up to you now!”

Garen reminisced about his impression on Lon. He was a bashful, gentle, introverted fellow, always had long hair, and was the type who didn’t dare to raise his voice. This type of person wouldn’t intentionally cut off all contact with his family. Judging by his personality, something must have happened that prevented him from contacting home.

“What about dad?”

“He’s still busy working on some stuff at his office, and he also has an urgent meeting this afternoon. He is probably preparing for it now,” Amy looked extremely fatigued. “Recently, your grandma fell sick again and she also has some problems with her leg, so your dad is also busy taking care of her. Furthermore…” at this point, Amy’s face was once again filled with concern.

“Furthermore what?”

“Furthermore, the police came by this morning for some investigation. They say your brother, he’s… somehow related to the terrorist attack case, so they needed to come in to do some investigations.” Within one day, his mother Amy had gone through so much bad news, it was surely extremely taxing on her body.

“Terrorist?” did they mean White Light?

Garen frowned. Ever since he had received Blue Narcissus’ endorsement, his family’s financial status had become much better, but new problems had started to pop up one after another. At first, when he had selected Nonosiva, it was because the Soul Seed felt that he had a different aura from others. However, after such a long time, there still weren’t any major changes. On the contrary, now his brother Baylon had such a problem befalling him…

“Apparently it also had something to do with the younger brother of the bakery owner. Now that the warrants are out, what should we do? Your younger brother had to live a bitter life alone ever since he was young… If something were to happen to him…” as she spoke, his mother Amy started to sob intermittently.

“Don’t worry mom, I’ll try to use my connections over here to do some investigations on the issue,” Garen comforted her. “Alright, I’ll go get some people to help, I’ll report back to you tonight.”

“Okay, try to be as fast as possible! If something were to happen to your brother…”

Hanging up, Garen took a deep breath. The soul seed started to have a slight movement; it seemed like it was possibly something big this time.

After thinking for a bit, he started calling up people from his network.

“Is this Celine? I need a favor, my brother might be in trouble. I’ve no idea of the circumstances, so can you help me dig up some info? Alright alright, I’ll treat you to dinner sometime soon, bye.”

“Vivienne, I have something I’d like you to help me investigate. My brother is in some sort of trouble, he went missing around half a month ago, okay, alright, thanks!”

“Kendall, is the Charm Mercenary Troop available? Can you get them to investigate what’s going on at my brother’s side? Give them the mission to protect my little brother at all costs. Of course, I mean now! Why do you think I pay you guys so much every month? Alright, thanks! Buck up! Alright.”

After countless calls, Garen slumped down while deep in thought. The Nutritious Meal in front of him was only half-finished, but his eating speed became slower and slower and suddenly came to a complete stop.

“What’s up? Is there any trouble? I heard you make a few phone calls earlier,” Sofia walked up to his side. She was carrying a tray with a small portion Nutritious Meal and a glass of apple juice.

“Oh, it’s Sofia,” Garen politely gave her a greeting, though he was still frowning. Baylon had always seen him as his idol and aspiration. He was a kind young lad, giving up his opportunity to go to school to Garen, his older brother. Although Garen wasn’t actually his brother, since he was occupying his brother’s body, he had to at least do his part.

“There’s some trouble that popped up back home. My younger brother went missing.”

“Looking for people is my specialty,” Sofia nodded. “If you don’t mind, let me help you out.”

“Then I’ll have no choice but to trouble you, senior,” Garen didn’t hold back; it was only natural to help each other with favors, this was a part of human communication.

“It’s nothing much. Wait for my update, I’ll have a report sent to you latest by tonight,” Sofia smiled.

“Alright, enjoy your meal, I’ll take my leave first. I have to settle some issues at the academy,” Garen stood up.

“The Eagle’s Nest is currently giving out investigation missions, it’s all high-level missions given in the name of the military. All pilots who are Level One and above can take up the missions. Coincidentally, there were a few missions regarding the rumors of terrorist activity within the city. If you don’t mind, you can take those up. Maybe you can get some more information from the military side regarding this situation,” Sofia suggested.

“Oh? I’ll take a look in a bit, thanks for the info,” Garen nodded

Without even slowing down, Garen headed directly towards the Eagle’s Nest. After asking for directions from a few members, he arrived at a small room. One of the walls inside was replaced by a huge display screen. The screen listed the missions given by various parts of the military from all over the region to the Eagle’s Nest and the associated rewards.

Amongst these, were things like investigating the mysterious Mech outside the city, night time security patrol, training accompaniment, fire department support, Mech beta testing, and more.

Tens of missions were listed on the screen, with the list being refreshed every few seconds. Sometimes, new missions would appear, while at other times a mission would be displayed as cleared as the entry slowly faded away.

There were a lot of students here picking their missions. As Garen walked in, he was recognized by many people. Ever since his battle at the training hall last time, he had gained a small amount of fame. For someone at his age to have already attained Level Three Willpower, within the Eagle’s Nest, he was easily ranked within the top three hundred. Furthermore, he had even joined the Blue Narcissus as an elite chosen by Britney. Although he did not become an elite student, if not for his bout with Celine, both of them would have undoubtedly entered the ranks of the elite students without a hitch. In addition, he had managed to improve his Willpower from Level One to Level Three just within the short timespan of half a year. His potential was unmeasurable.

Hence, no one dared to underestimate him. Upon his entrance, they unconsciously parted like the red sea, all greeting him with smiles on their faces.

Garen nodded to them in thanks. This group of people looked to be at least Level One or Two, and those who dared to come view the missions weren’t average students. He proceeded to the spot they created for him and started to look at the missions.

Soon, he found the mission given out by the military, which was a mission of investigating and patrolling around Blackboard City. He immediately called the listed contact number and left his name and student number in the voicemail as identification.

As he was about to leave the room, a muscular man with short blue hair walked in. The two looked at each other face-to-face, noticing the force of the Level Three Willpower engulfing each other.

“Nonosiva?” the guy smiled. “Big Bro Anjay Terin told me all about you, he said you were awesome! I’m Kembe, I guess I’m in luck, to think I would meet the Freshmen’s First Seat in the flesh.”

“I was only lucky, Level Three Willpower is something quite common in the Eagles Nest,” Garen humbly replied.

“This isn’t something you can chalk up to luck,” Kembe shook his head. “Why the rush, did you get an urgent mission? Need any help?”

“Thanks for the offer, but there’s no need. Let’s talk more next time, it’s almost time for my mission to start,” Garen motioned at his watch.

“Ah alright, let’s chat next time, I’m also planning on taking up a mission for fun,” Kembe casually said. “Why don’t we swap our contact info? If you’re free, we can even go grab a drink or two. I heard that even Barry couldn’t defeat you that day at the training hall! That’s awesome!”

“Alright, let’s see when both of us free then,” Garen nodded.

As the two walked past each other, Garen looked at the time once more. While awaiting the confirmation of the mission, he still had a bit of time. After pondering for a moment, he decided to head to class.

The number of familiar faces in the class had decreased by quite a bit. A lot of people had failed to reach the required grades for certain subjects and were forced to retain a year. There were also a few people from other classes that were transferred here to make up the numbers. This was a normal occurrence in Blackboard Academy. Every year, there would be some students dropping out, some students being retained, some successfully being promoted to the next year, and some classes would be merged if they didn’t have enough students left.

Walking into the noisy classroom, he was just in time for the next class. Other than a few elite aces in the class, most of the students went to class as usual, as it was the best way for them to earn academic points. Aces like Garen or Fervale, on the other hand, managed to earn their academic points through attaining the top ranks in various competitions. Even accepting missions from the Eagle’s Nest or taking assessments could grant him academic points, which, needless to say, was completely effortless for Garen.

As Garen walked into the classroom, many students’ gazes shifted towards him. Some went over and gave him a passionate greeting, while others seem to be silently observing him and gossiping about him. Fervale was also not here; his seat was empty.

Vera and Kell were at their seats busy revising for their test, so they haven’t been together with Garen recently. However, upon noticing Garen’s arrival they stood up and walked towards him.

“Nono, what brings you to class today?” Kell asked while holding up her long wavy bangs.

“I came to talk to Vera about some stuff,” Garen’s sight shifted towards Vera, and his calm yet sharp gaze upon her made her shrink away. “C’mon, let’s talk outside.”

Chapter 850: Investigate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“O… Okay,” Vera felt goosebumps appearing all over her body. She followed Garen out of the classroom before standing still at a corner.

“Were you the one who delivered the dorm keys to me previously?” asked Garen directly.

“Yes… You weren’t here so they told me to send them to your dorm,” Vera tried her best to look natural.

“Did you touch the things?”

Vera froze at once.

“What… What things? What are you talking about?”

“The documents in my drawer,” Garen reached his hand out and patted her face. “Didn’t you know that going through other people’s stuff without their permission is actually against the rules…”

“I didn’t! Don’t accuse me!” Vera went to great lengths to plaster an innocent expression on her face but her heartbeat sped up instead.

“Whatever. I don’t have time for silly chats with you. I’m aware of your current situation. You’re not getting enough money from your family, right? Don’t worry, I have money but I’ll need you to help me do some things. As long as you make yourself pretty, I have no qualms about spending tens of thousands on you,” said Garen calmly. “You’re allowed to refuse, of course. But if that happens, I have a recording of you in my hands now and I’ll have no choice but to send it to the Academy for them to screen it publicly.”

He raised his watch. The screen was currently displaying the interior of his dorm room clearly and showed Vera opening his drawers sneakily. She even took some cash from the lowest drawer and stuffed it into her pocket.

“I wonder how the ‘little boys’ who admire you will react once they find out about these recordings. And your best friends as well…” Garen looked on coldly while Vera’s face turned pale instantly. Panicked and helpless looks appeared in her eyes faintly.

“You… I didn’t do it on purpose… I was wrong! Really, it was just a moment of confusion…” Vera was rambling slightly now.

“That’s enough. I don’t care whether it happened in a moment of confusion or not. I’ll look for you when I need you. That’s all.”

Garen pinched her cheeks before turning around and leaving.

*************************

At night

Garen sat leisurely on a bench at the roadside of the Academy and quietly flipped through the related information that was sent through various channels.

The whereabouts of his little brother Baylon remained unclear. He had only discovered that his last appearance was in the One for All Bakery, the little shop where he used to work. After the loud explosion occurred by the river, no one saw him ever again.

It seemed as though all the channels had only received the same information, including Vivienne, Sofia, and the others.

Beep beep, beep beep…

“Hey, Kendall? No news? Alright, okay, yeah,” after disconnecting the call, Garen knitted his eyebrows closely together again. His instincts told him that the case involving his little brother Baylon this time was not a minor issue, unfortunately. His Soul Seeds had been trembling faintly until now. Therefore, this was clearly a serious problem that would affect and change the bigger picture.

His phone rang again immediately. The caller was a middle-aged man who was in charge of issuing tasks in the military headquarters.

“Student Nonosiva, I’m so happy that a Level Three student like yourself chose the task that we issued. We have drafted a small group for this task that will comprise of fifteen members with you as the captain. You will lead the patrol throughout certain territories for a duration of one month. You can choose one of the remaining available regions as the location of your task.”

“Understood. A small group of fifteen people. What kind of patrolling method will we be using? What opponents will we be going up against?” Garen continued asking.

“You will be using the Mechs to patrol and counter a broken red and white-colored Mech. Once you’ve encountered your opponent, please inform the headquarters at the first moment and stall it. If possible, go all-out and kill your opponent,” replied the middle-aged man meticulously.

“This is a map with the regions you may choose from,” He was sent a map that segregated the Blackboard Region into smaller areas.

Garen glanced at the map and noticed that it divided the region into a total of more than thirty pieces. The tasks within almost half of these areas had been accepted. Within the remaining areas, he chose the place that was closest to his home without hesitation. Fortunately, that area had not been chosen yet.

“Your map has been determined. Meet with your team members by tomorrow and set your own meeting point. This is your group number,” a group number was given to him by the person on the other line.

Garen nodded and asked a few more questions about some important matters before disconnecting the call.

Moments after the phone call had been disconnected, he received another phone call from Celine. When he glanced at it, he noticed that there were more than ten unanswered phone calls previously, meaning that she had been calling him much earlier.

Just as he answered, the sound of Celine’s heavy breathing echoed from the other line instantly.

“Nono, guess what I’ve found?!”

His instincts told him that something was amiss. Garen sat up straighter suddenly. “What happened? Don’t tell me you’ve made another great discovery?”

“It’s more than just a great discovery!” said Celine angrily. “I went looking for one of my friends in the higher level intelligence departments of the Academy because of the situation with your little brother. Later, I ended up discovering a shocking secret from him!”

“Tell me!” from Celine’s experience, everything was a shocking secret to her. No one could imagine how astonishing this secret truly was. Garen calmed his own breathing quickly and listened carefully to the voice on the other side of his Watch Terminal.

“Have you heard of the Forbidden Mech?” Celine’s first sentence made Garen’s heart tremble.

“Legend has it that it’s a mythical Mech and a strategic war weapon that can destroy planets. It’s the ultimate and strongest existence in the whole universe!” said Celine immediately without waiting for Garen’s reply.

“So how is it related to the secret you discovered?”

“Three hundred years ago, the Forbidden Mech of our Mother Planet Federation was defeated in a crossfire, causing to collapse into many fragments that were scattered throughout various planets. They were known as Forbidden Parts. Our Mother Planet obtained a few of these fragments,” explained Celine quietly. “Do you know why Blackboard Academy dispatched groups of Black-Clothed Generals and Elite Students in such large scales previously? To find these Forbidden fragments! Furthermore, the information that I obtained stated that the large explosion by the river outside the city recently was very likely to be caused by the core component of the Forbidden Mech– the Forbidden Knowledge Core!”

“Knowledge Core?!” Garen was shocked. His emotions were unconsciously stirred. “Are you certain that the Forbidden Knowledge Core is still intact?!”

“The members of the White Light Organization moved out in great numbers because of this. They are currently clashing with the professionals of the Academy and neither party is giving the other any leeway,” said Celine hurriedly. “I obtained accurate information. That Knowledge Core can summon a temporary projection of the Forbidden Mech that will release its Forbidden Abilities for a short period of time. It cannot do this without an intact core!”

Garen became silent. This information was somewhat serious and he needed to digest it properly for a while. This situation was similar to a regular person encountering a fortunate coincidence suddenly. Now that a fine weapon had seemingly appeared somewhere nearby, he would be able to gain tremendous powers if he was able to practice using it successfully.

The Forbidden Knowledge Core was similar in that sense. Garen was in urgent need of a Training Method. Strong, advanced Training methods were usually considered to have reached their peaks once they had achieved Level Five. Any further and they would have entered the Inherited Mech’s territory, which had its own strengths and weaknesses. Meanwhile, the Forbidden Mech was considered as the pinnacle of the Star Levels and was a first-rate existence even in comparison to the Inherited Mech.

A Knowledge Core like this would definitely have a lot of exceptionally powerful Training Methods and various scientific information recorded inside its databank. If an idiot obtained those things, particularly the Training Methods, they would be able to change their lives and become extremely successful. They could even seek to dominate the region.

“The people in the higher levels of the Academy are participating in this as well. This is an extremely rare chance!” said Celine in a tempting manner.

“We’re too weak. We won’t gain any benefits if we join them now,” said Garen calmly while returning to his normal train of thought. Although his heart was aroused, he knew that he needed to estimate his own strengths accordingly before moving forward.

“That may be true, but we are still students of the Academy. If we can help the Academy obtain the Core… From what I’ve heard, the White and Red Mech that you are looking for comes from one of the terrorists in the White Light Terrorist Organization. He hasn’t retreated despite his heavy injuries and has been constantly pursuing it. It’s very likely that he possesses the Forbidden Core,” said Celine quickly. “If we can help the Academy get the Core, the reward won’t be too bad, don’t you think?”

Garen’s face was expressionless but his mind had already started to stir.

“I will begin my patrolling task tomorrow.”

“I will report the latest information to you constantly. You can pilot the Mechs within the district and that will still be perfectly legitimate. No one will dare to gossip about you. If needed, I will transfer all of my household’s Mech Pilots and get them to move out and help you!” said Celine in a determined tone suddenly.

“Alright.”

“That will be all.”

Garen disconnected the line while his gaze deepened. He stood up from the bench and walked back towards his own dorm room.

********************

The next day

Ten black Mechs descended onto a landing field on the border of Blackboard Region slowly.

On the backs of these black human-shaped Mechs were red disc-shaped shields that made it look like they were carrying red straw hats. Their muscular bodies, red eyes, the standardized doubled edged machetes in their hands and their Swordfish Type A Engines were the standard equipment that was allocated by the city.

The morning sunlight cascaded downwards. Moments later, a larger black Mech flew over and landed in front of these ten Mechs.

“Sir!!”

Suddenly, loud cries echoed from the waiting Mechs simultaneously like thunder. The sound was amplified outside the Mechs and caused surrounding grounds to quake because of the noisy hums.

Garen stood in front of these ten people. All of them were a part of a standard battle team that the military had allocated to him. They were individuals that were tasked and sent from other academies. Moreover, they were students that were educated in the other Mech academies in the region. Some of them were also veterans who had performed such tasks before and were very experienced. They were clearly here to be his deputies and warn him about things.

“Hello everyone. I’m Nonosiva from Blackboard Academy. I’m the standard leader who will be in charge of leading the tasks. I hope that we can work together properly for the following duration.”

From his tone, Garen’s calm and unflurried emotions could be heard clearly.

The few veterans in the crowd were slightly surprised by this. Although he was an Elite Student of Blackboard Academy, it was abnormal for him to behave so calmly during his first military mission.

“Alright, begin reporting your names and levels now!” Garen waved his hand downwards quickly while the whooshing sound of wind echoed instantly as he pointed at the first Mech on the right.

“Sir!” this Mech belonged to one of the veterans who stood forward and replied loudly while using the standard military gestures. “Ansaro! Level One Mech Pilot!!”

“Carrie! Level One Mech Pilot!”

“Sebatton! Level One Mech Pilot!!”

…

…

Within moments, all of the Mech team members had stepped forward and listed themselves one after another. The thing that surprised Garen slightly was that one of them was a Level Two Mech Pilot. That person came from another academy in the city, War Academy, which was one of the three main Elites.

Chapter 851: Patrol 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“War Academy? Is that the academy in the Egret Block?” asked Garen while looking at the Level Two individual.

He had a kind and sincere face, slightly tanned skin, and looked very serious. However, a look of concealed dishonesty was faintly seeping out of his narrow eyes.

“Reporting, sir! My name is Alexander!”

“Regardless of what you were called previously, you will be given new serial numbers and code names now. Choose the name of an animal to be used with your allocated number. Come up with the names on your own,” Garen raised his wristwatch and pressed it gently. A rustling noise could be heard as the serial numbers of the fifteen members and himself were distributed quickly.

Seconds later, the serial numbers were determined and transmitted to them respectively.

His animal prefix was “lion” and his group was known as the lion’s pride while Garen was called Lion No. 1. Meanwhile, the other members arranged themselves according to their power rankings until No. 16.

While looking at the row of soldiers who were standing in front of him, Garen was not completely sure how to arrange them as he had never actually been enlisted in the military before. However, he only needed to achieve his aim and the priority of this task was to complete the patrol and hunt down the enemy that would probably appear. The territory had already been confirmed and this entire area, as well as its surroundings, was their responsibility now.

“Listen up, in busy areas and places where there are endless streams of people, you are not authorized to collide with others carelessly at high speeds in order to avoid accidentally injuring the masses. All of you have Magnetic Cords, so cast them outwards when you encounter the enemy and lock them down while waiting for support. Do all you can to avoid injuring civilians!” Garen followed the first criteria and began assigning the tasks. Although the people before him were aware of this already, he was still obligated to emphasize certain things once again. In the event that an innocent bystander was hurt, he would still be partially responsible even if the damage was not caused by his own actions, but by one of his subordinate members.

The rules comprised of not injuring the common people, not destroying buildings carelessly, and not leaving the patrol grounds without permission. They would also need to report before leaving the group. He was prepared to move the group at any moment when the alarms at various positions sounded.

More than ten minutes had passed before every single rule had been listed out.

“Everyone, assign yourselves to your fixed territories now and report to me immediately if you encounter any situations!”

Garen passed the maps which had been marked with the specific areas to each of his fifteen group members. Other than himself who would be patrolling from place to place, the others would guard a fixed area within a certain range. They would report and communicate with each other after a fixed duration of time to indicate that there were no problems.

On the drill grounds, once the fifteen Mechs were assigned to specific territories, they rose into the sky and dispersed, flying in all four directions.

Garen stood on the drill grounds and single-handedly pulled out a broadsword that he had prepared earlier before waving it around casually.

“Although it’s not that smooth, it was still made with pretty good materials.”

This was his first task. If he completed it successfully, his collaborations with the military would gradually increase in the future. He would even be able to get a job and wages in the military much earlier without even having to graduate. This was also one of the main ways for the military to win over the students of Blackboard Academy.

Although the military and the Academy had a relationship of subordination, the military had actually been under the command of a different ringleader all along. This ringleader represented a large group of Elites that had previously left a specific faction of the academy. Even though their high-end powers were no match for the Academy, their numbers exceeded the Academy’s greatly. Therefore, the military had high hopes for these exceptional individuals.

“The students who practiced the Crouched Eagle Talon would probably be influenced by certain Training Methods, causing them to become belligerent and aggressive. This would be in line with the military’s style. Therefore, both sides would be able to work well with each other. If this task was given to another organization other than Eagle’s Nest, the other groups would not necessarily be able to obtain a patrolling task like this.”

When Garen’s mind finally comprehended everything, he sheathed his broadsword and glanced at his communication device and noticed that his group members had almost arrived at their respective patrolling spots.

He only needed to wait for his team members to report their situations at any time. After that, they would change their patrol areas slightly after a certain period of time.

After resting on the drill grounds for more than ten minutes, Garen piloted his Mech and soared into the sky. He flew towards the area where the first member, No. 2 was currently patrolling.

He passed over a street where there were bustling crowds. He could occasionally see white spider-shaped super-miniature Mech policemen. These human-controlled miniature Mechs were entrusted to solve issues pertaining to public security. Each of these white spiders was more than three meters tall and were Mechs that constantly patrolled at the sides of the streets while moving slowly.

There were two sidewalks closer to the center that were filled with clusters of office workers and vegetable vendors. Elementary and junior high school students on their way to class could occasionally be seen mixed in the crowd. Closer to the middle where the center of the road was located were streams of different types of vehicles. There were little push carts, electric motorcycles, and most of all, bicycles, followed by the scooters that were mostly used by the working class.

The cacophony of beeping and honking noises of car horns filled his ears and students squealed and joked loudly while electric bicycle bells chimed, motorcycle engines roared and vendors argued loudly. The noises mixed with one another and formed a picture of the daily life on this entire street.

Students would occasionally cast gazes of admiration at the Mechs that flew past them. Meanwhile, deep looks that indicated a strong sense of security could be seen in the eyes of the people that were walking down the street whenever they saw a Patrol Mech by the road.

The Black Mech that Garen was piloting flew in front of a building on the right side of the street slowly. His silenced engine would not make awful noises as long as he was not using the highest power output.

Blue flames shot out of the back of the black human-shaped Mech as it moved forward along the street slowly.

There was a stretch of motley people and cars below. Instantly, the Black Mech which was wielding two knives in its hands appeared within Garen’s field of vision. On the custom heavy landing platform at the side of the street, Alexander, who was also known as member No. 2, was placed in a large, chaotic area where the foot traffic was highest because he was a professional whose strength was only second to Garen.

When he saw Garen approaching, Alexander made a deep bow. He straightened the palm of his right hand and placed it sideways against his left shoulder in a brief yet energetic manner.

“Sir!”

“Yes, always guard the Mechs with your full attention. You can relax slightly. Don’t be too anxious because our unit is set to guard this place for an entire day,” Garen reminded him.

“Understood,” Alexander smiled. “Sir, someone came over and gave me some bribes earlier but I don’t know…”

“Bribes?” Garen was shocked but reacted immediately. They were merely the patrol team and the Spider Mechs of the garrison would be here to solve problems that were out of their domain. However, they were nominally at a higher level than the garrison. Therefore, it would be really easy for them to find the instigator who was trying to create trouble for the garrison.

“Did someone from the garrison send it over?”

“They’re local thugs. Unlike us who come here occasionally, they’re always here…” giggled Alexander. “There’s a pretty good massage parlor below. Sir, if you don’t want to…” this fellow began to laugh excessively.

“This…”

“I heard that their pretty boys are not bad…”

Garen’s emotions were slightly aroused at first. He could have gotten a massage and soaked in a warm bath to relax his body for a while. However, the last sentence made him feel cold aversion the moment he heard it.

“You go on your own, I’m going to continue patrolling. Just make sure not to be too presumptuous.”

The probability of them encountering terrorists within the district was extremely low. Individuals who were allowed to accept tasks within the district would not only be physically strong but would also come from pretty good backgrounds. After all, patrolling the busy areas was a lucrative job. Garen did not want to offend these people.

He controlled the Mech and left the busy area. There was a large clear river in front of him that resembled a winding ribbon. White steamboats of various sizes sailing across the glittering surface of the river.

In the morning sunlight, Garen piloted his Mech slowly and flew towards a heavy landing platform by the river before docking there. When he looked over at the opposite side of the river, the Blackboard Region’s symbolic suspended Garden Trade City stood upright on the other side.

The buildings throughout the entire trade city resembled sharp pencils that protruded out of the ground. They were more than a thousand meters tall and fully white. Neons signs and billboards of various colors filled the area while publicity airships flew around and circled the area while scattering advertisements occasionally.

Compared to the liveliness by the river, the trade city was much noisier. It seemed as if an exciting ceremony was being held there as the sound of music and singing would drift over at times.

Garen looked over from afar and saw the crowds who stood shoulder-to-shoulder like a pile of black sesame seeds. He could only see the tops of their dark heads.

Faint morning sunlight cascaded on the surface of the water, appearing like a river of sparkling diamonds.

Garen decided to stop temporarily. He sat cross-legged on the heavy circular spot and rested quietly. Once he had turned the Mech off and pushed the engine button, everything fell into a state of peacefulness.

After all, he was still waiting for Celine’s intelligence reports. The other members would probably be unwilling for him to close in on them while the patrolled the area anyway. Therefore, as long as there were no issues in this area, everything would be fine.

He reached his hand outwards and pressed a button near the lower front part.

Whoosh…

A soft noise could be heard before the Mech’s cockpit raised itself outwards and upwards slowly like an egg with a half-opened shell. Garen, who sat in the driver’s seat, was soon exposed.

He removed his helmet and got up from his seat in the cockpit immediately. He controlled one of the Mech’s arms and lowered it to the ground before walking down that arm and standing at the side of the platform. The pleasantly cool breeze by the river blew at him as he breathed in the fresh air.

The sound of moving cars from the street, conversations of the pedestrians, and noisy chatter of the elementary and junior high schoolers could be vaguely heard behind him.

Garen combed his hand through his hair. Unknowingly, his hair had almost reached his shoulders while the sleek black locks had begun to shine as well. The radiation of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique gave it a faint bluish tint.

He lifted both of his hands and observed his white and blue skin. It had become almost transparent and completely smooth as all of his previous scars and blemishes had disappeared completely.

“Beautification is definitely one of the Living Secret Technique’s best uses,” Garen could not help but laugh at himself while unzipping his piloting uniform. Once the tight black clothes were slightly loosened, his shirt collar became a straight collar that touched both sides of his neck. His strong muscles and contours were soon exposed.

After he had switched bodies and practiced the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, Nonosiva’s previously slender and skinny body was completely gone. It was replaced by a strong and muscular physique instead. He had gained the perfect upside-down-triangle-shaped muscles on his upper body while his arms were taut and strong. He stood on the side of the heavy platform and draped his black clothes over his body.

Perhaps Garen’s soul was another reason why there was a faint glimmer in his eyes despite his seemingly normal external appearance. Even through his hair, his piercing gaze gave him an astute aura.

The corners of Nonosiva’s mouth had already been pointing downwards previously. It gave him a threatening air that made others think that he could flare up at any moment, making it even more difficult for people to approach him throughout his life. People who were the slightest bit weaker than him would not even dare to meet his eye when they stood in front of him.

His imposing physique, cold expression and somewhat glimmering and piercing eyes were features that made him seem like a suppressed volcano that could erupt any moment. However, Garen himself did not even possess those traits…

Nonetheless, these signs caused him to appear as his current state, which also happened to be extremely fierce.

Chapter 852: Patrol 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Pfoo…

Garen took a deep breath before exhaling it slowly.

“Come and look quickly, that’s a Black Cloud Level Advanced Mech!!” the sound of joyful childish squeals echoed behind him suddenly.

“Hmm?”

Garen turned his head and looked at a group of passing school children on the road who were looking fervently at the gigantic Mechs here now. All of them were clearly fanatical Mech enthusiasts.

However, their initially enthusiastic expressions froze instantly when they saw him turn his head suddenly.

A few elementary school students who were carrying their bags took a few steps back when they were scared off by his “fierce” face.

“So… So cool!! No wonder he’s the man who can pilot the Black Cloud!!” said a little boy loudly while pointing at him.

“Little guys…” Garen opened his mouth and smile. However, his smile clearly made him look fiercer, vaguely making it seem as if he was sneering ferociously.

“Run, quick!!” the group of school children scattered and disappeared without a trace instantly.

Garen stroked his face wordlessly. No wonder Vera had shrunk so fearfully even though he had just said a few words to her. Apparently, he had grown an extremely deterrent face without even realizing.

“I should continue patrolling…” Garen exhaled and got into his cockpit again.

Time ticked by slowly. His Potential Points continued to accumulate but Garen did not plan on using them. His greatest problem now was his lack of a solid foundation. After completing his tasks every day, he would hone particular aspects of the Crouched Eagle Talon’s Training Methods as well as the functions and means of response to their various Techniques.

His patrolling days passed day by day. Every day fell into the same old schedule and he would inspect the condition of his team members’ tasks. In reality, Garen would just choose the patrol areas of a random team member to observe. He would be too lazy to visit the others. Therefore, most of his time was spent on the heavy platform by the river where he would rest and enjoy the cool breeze while breathing in the fresh air.

The elementary and junior high school students who passed by when they were either going to or leaving school daily would always give him a calming atmosphere.

As time passed, Garen’s understanding of the Crouched Eagle Talon’s abilities allowed him to catch up to the other advanced students in the Eagle’s Nest quickly. The initial lack of foundation that was caused by his speedy upgrades was offset quickly.

More than ten days passed in the blink of an eye.

The weather gradually turned colder. Although the faint morning sunlight was still present, the temperature had definitely lowered. The sunlight could not be felt even when it was shining down on his body directly.

Garen stood beside the heavy platform as usual and gazed at the faraway scenery.

Beep beep, beep beep…

The noise of a ringing phone call could be sounded from his watch slowly.

He pressed it to answer the call.

“I’ve found some information about your little brother,” Celine’s first words gave Garen a jolt. “Nothing out of the ordinary. He was pulled aside by the big explosion by the river. Also, he may have been involved with the White Light Terrorist Organization so you’ll need to be prepared.”

“In other words, both of these events are actually the same thing?” Garen furrowed his eyebrows.

“That may be the case. Although the superiors have released the ten of your patrol team members all over that region to capture the Red-White Mech, no one is actually expecting you to seize it. From the information I gathered, you just need to find an extremely dilapidated, pieced together black Mech to find the Forbidden Core.”

“Old black-colored Mech?” Garen repeated. “What about my brother?”

“I’m unclear about the full situation, but I can give you an address I obtained from the information at the intelligence department. The other person’s place of refuge is probably there.”

The information was transmitted over quickly. Garen opened it and glanced through while his gaze flickered.

“From the looks of it, it’s very likely that this place is in the area where I’m stationed.”

“That’s true. Although we don’t know the reason behind it, it’s true that the other person is currently fleeing towards your area,” said Celine certainly. “You should be careful of your surrounding situation at all times.”

“Yeah.”

“Then will be all. I’ll be here to assist you at any time. Call this number during critical moments.”

“Got it.”

After ending the call, Garen’s mind became more solemn. He could now confirm that his little brother Baylon was related to this incident.

“If Lon was really involved in this, there should be an important reason why the culprit would be rushing over in this direction. They would probably be coming here to visit their parents or family. This reasoning is somewhat plausible. Except that… How would they be able to escape successfully in the situation that their tracks are exposed?”

Garen concluded that the other party definitely possessed exceptionally strong escape measures that other people did not know of.

He got into the Mech again. There was a sputtering noise before blue flames were released from the back of the Mech and it flew upwards slowly. He began his investigation along the fixed patrolling roadmap.

Time continued to pass slowly from mid-morning to noon. The place remained calm even after he ate his lunch. However, Garen sensed that something was amiss when he patrolled the fifth district.

The fifth district was filled with factories, warehouses, storehouses and the likes. There were few signs of human habitation while the area was full of tall “alleys” that were formed by the spaces between factories. Cars could be seen passing through this area occasionally.

There were even fewer people to be seen during the late afternoon.

Garen landed on the heavy platform slowly. His extremely acute senses allowed him to detect that something was not quite right although he was still inside the Mech.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows slightly and began to use his senses to carefully distinguish the source of the abnormalities.

Tch!

He opened the cockpit and jumped right out before landing on the ground.

“It’s shaking!”

Both of his eyes were narrowed.

“The ground is shaking…”

These tremors were extremely weak as the sensors could not detect them as well. However, Garen’s exceptionally strong five senses allowed him to feel these things clearly. It seemed as if a heavy object was running around underground.

“It’s a Mech!!” he figured out the answer immediately. “The sewers!”

He somersaulted instantly and got into the Mech. He piloted it towards the nearest entrance to the sewers. These few days of patrolling and his prior memories of the map of this area had allowed him to be familiarized with the topography here much earlier on.

He quickly obtained the blueprints of the sewers from their website off the internet and tried to memorize it while flying towards the entrance rapidly.

He could already see the entrance to the sewers moments after he arrived there. The cover that was specially provided for the engineering Mechs had been removed. The insides of the sewers were completely dark while a trail of wet footprints was left at the side of the road. They were clearly Mech footprints.

“It’s really here!!”

Garen picked up the communication device quickly. He was about to call his group members but immediately halted further actions. Instead, he dialed the number that Celine had given him directly.

“How is everything?!”

“Bring your people over here. Determine my location and hurry!”

“Understood!”

Without saying anything else, the phone call was disconnected.

Garen pursued the footprints carefully with his full attention. The factory area was extremely huge, but no one knew where the guard who had been stationed here had run off to. Hardly anybody was here and even the garrison’s Spider Mechs were nowhere to be seen.

Garen piloted his Mech quickly in pursuit before passing through an open area instantly. He made a sharp left turn and entered an alley between factory buildings.

Coincidentally, a damaged black Mech currently had its back to him and was dashing into a different entrance of the alley. Strangely enough, this Mech did not have a flight engine. However, it was almost silent whenever its feet stepped on the ground.

“I’ve caught you!”

Garen’s engine roared suddenly while his Mech charged over at once. Swords appeared in both of its hands instantly.

Clint was scared out of his wits when he noticed the Black Mech charging up behind him through the sensor on his back.

“I’m going to die!!” he yelled loudly.

“I can still help you make a short distance leap! Be careful!” roared Red Moon. “Duck!”

Tch!

The moment Garen sliced at his opponent, the old Black Mech spun and disappeared from its original spot as if it had completely dispersed in thin air. A tornado spun out from its initial position.

Garen’s face remained unchanged as he had expected earlier on that his opponent would have troublesome escape measures like these.

His Mech squatted on the ground and used the sensors on its head to listen carefully after prostrating there.

Moments later, the Mech rose up and flew off speedily in a different direction.

*******************

Clint fled between the warehouses quickly while panting and sweating profusely.

Bang!

An exquisite Black Mech landed in front of him suddenly and obstructed his path. His violent Dual Blades swept over like two shrouds of silvery grey mist.

“Duck!!” without saying another word, Red Moon flickered and leaped away.

Tch!

Clint was blinded before he appeared in a different alley.

“That guy… Too scary… At least I managed to counter a few of that Red-White guy’s moves. How was it impossible that I didn’t have any strength to resist this guy at all?!” said Clint with a confused look on his face.

“It’s different! The White Light’s Mech didn’t even have a solid foundation. Other than its strength, everything else about it was rubbish. It’s obvious that this current Mech has an extremely solid foundation and exceptionally incredible techniques and combat abilities. It’s completely unlike most of the others that only rely on Willpower abilities,” explained Red Moon quickly.

A shroud of silvery grey mist shot over suddenly and appeared in front of his eyes instantly.

“Be careful!!” Red Moon could not even yell in time.

Clint could only feel a tremor running through the body of his Mech suddenly. His shoulder was directly pierced by a long sword that split it open. After that, the sword crashed violently against the ground behind his body and stabbed into it deeply while releasing a brief scratching noise.

Electric sparks illuminated the Mech’s damaged body. Before he could even think, a black Mech descended from the sky and a sword was placed right over his head.

Clang!!

During a moment when his life was in imminent peril, Clint raised his right arm to block the attack while kicking his right leg outwards towards his opponent’s lower body simultaneously.

“Behold my ultimate move!” Bang!!

The leg of Clint’s Mech separated itself automatically at once and turned into a rocket that shot outwards. It flew towards the fork of Garen’s Mech’s legs. Unfortunately, Garen lifted his knee at the key moment and kicked it towards the other side.

“How is that possible?!! Even Red-White fell for this trick!!” Clint yelled in disbelief.

“Escape quickly! This guy isn’t someone you can handle!!” Red Moon moved and flickered again.

During these dangerous instances, the light that reflected off a silvery grey blade only sliced through thin air.

“You fled really quickly,” Garen sheathed his sword and stood still while red light shined out of his Mech’s eyes.

“Has everyone arrived?” he asked softly while raising his watch.

“Yes, sir. Mistress told us to listen to all of your instructions,” answered the man on the other line.

“Be careful when you disperse and separate from one another. Move out within five hundred meters of my surroundings. That guy could not have leaped much further. His energy is depleting too and his distance gets shorter each time,” instructed Garen.

“Understood.”

The Mech Pilots that were sent from Celine’s household operated super-miniature Mechs to avoid bringing attention to themselves. The military and garrison were the only ones who were allowed to operate Mechs in the districts publicly. Therefore, Garen was able to use his status as part of the military to patrol openly.

Chapter 853: Track 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Moving on, let me see your powers… little guy.” Garen lifted the Dual Blade from the ground. A scraping noise could be heard when the two surfaces rubbed against each other. Meanwhile, the red light inside the eyes of Garen’s Mech grew more intense.

Whoosh!

A thunderous noise echoed from the Mech while Garen rose into the sky again and flew towards another location that was resonating.

************

The Mech that Clint was piloting dashed across the ground as if it was flying. The speed of this Mech was extremely fast and it did not look as heavy as its outer shell. There was a faint crack on its arm from blocking Garen’s sword. The leg that it had released earlier for its sneak attack had automatically flown back as well, further proving Red Moon’s adept Mech modification abilities.

Most of the alleys in the factory area were large and broad. They were completely suitable for Mechs to run through at high speeds. Clint’s Mech did not make any footstep noises at all. Its electromagnetic induction was even bound by a specialized Energy Field that prevented it from leaking at all.

“What do we do now?” asked Clint while panting violently. When the Mech ran, the Mech Pilot themselves would bear the exhaustion.

If the mysterious Nine Mega Cannon Training Method had not allowed him to achieve extremely powerful physical qualities, a Mech Pilot unlike himself would have been out of breath long ago. After all, this damaged Mech lacked buffering equipment. Therefore, after engaging in a few highly difficult actions for more than ten seconds, Clint’s entire body would experience disproportionate blood flow and become dizzy because of the inertia when the Mech moved.

“What else can we do? Run!” said Red Moon impatiently. “Look for an opportunity to escape into the sewers below!”

“We’re going there again…”

“What else do you plan on doing?”

“O… Okay…” Clint was helpless. The sewers were excruciatingly smelly and if he had a choice, he would not go down there a second time. Unfortunately, the current situation left him no other option.

The damaged black Mech resembled an abnormally nimble disabled person who could run and jump down the entrance of the nearest sewer instantly.

“Look out behind you!!” yelled Red Moon suddenly.

Clint rolled forward quickly. This move had allowed him to escape from the Red-White Mech many times. He used the strength of the Nine Mega Cannon to roll forward quickly while exerting a large amount of force. The further he traveled, the faster he moved. This move was truly worthy to be an ultimate move for escaping and saving one’s life during a battle.

Bang!

A deep sword mark appeared on the ground suddenly where Clint had been earlier.

A Blackboard Mech descended from the sky behind him and stood there with one knee on the ground. This Mech was actually the one that Garen was using previously.

“He’s here again! Damn it! Go as fast as you can!!” panic filled Red Moon’s mind. Every Jump would deplete his energy sources that had been accumulated over many years. “Curses! If only I hadn’t consumed so much energy during the explosion previously…”

Clint took a big step and leaped forward after hearing those words. He had barely dodged the blade that had come at him directly from behind.

“Still thinking of rolling away?” a cold voice echoed behind him while another gust of chilly wind blew over. At this moment, a second blade came flying at him again.

“This speed is amazing!!” yelled Red Moon while summoning his last bouts of strength. “Blink!!”

Tch!

Clint moved instantly and was blinded suddenly. He did not know where he had landed in the blink of an eye. However, it was clear that he had not entered the sewer successfully.

“Ugh… Blegh!!!” When he was finally unable to hold himself back, Clint sat in the cockpit and barfed violently. These continuous Jumps and Blinks had finally taken their toll on his body. It seemed as though the gates to the dam that was his stomach had finally opened, causing him to vomit everything out messily. Yellow, white, and brown substances blended with one another like sticky Chinese congee.

The cockpit was instantly filled with a disgusting sour stench.

“Don’t get it on my body, you disgusting smelly kid!” yelled Red Moon furiously.

willpower

The Mech continued to roll forward. It got up and took big steps before running forward again. Clint was unable to tell which direction he was going in anymore and just ran around carelessly.

“Found you! Bastard!” a terribly battered Red-White Mech appeared behind him suddenly. The Mech’s entire body was thrashed and seemed to be in even worse conditions than Clint’s Mech. More than half of the light green crystal that was embedded in its chest was broken, making it seem dim and lustreless.

“It’s that Red-White guy! We’re dead!” Clint was exhausted from puking and could barely run forward while the distance between Red-White and himself grew closer.

“Don’t be afraid, I’ve prepared a secret weapon for you!” said Red Moon hurriedly.

“What secret weapon?!”

“Touch the small of your back for a bit!”

Clint followed his instructions and immediately touched that area.

Shh…

A large object that was thick, huge and dark bounced out and landed in Clint’s hands suddenly.

“So… So huge…!” while looking at the large item in his hands, Clint could not help but exclaim in shock.

“Like hell it’s huge! Hurry up! Turn around and hit him!” Red Moon roared.

Clint held the Gigantic Club in his hands tightly. This club was almost half as thick as his body and he did not know how it had been stuffed there. Clint did not think twice and rolled on the ground instead. He was looking upwards initially but when he rolled backward suddenly, he ended up colliding directly into Red-White who was behind him.

Windy, whooshing noises could be heard suddenly when he smashed the Gigantic Club in his hand towards his opponent. Instantly, the tip of the club twinkled for awhile and appeared behind Red-White’s body immediately.

“You’re asking to die!” the Red-White Mech sneered coldly and tried to seize the Gigantic Club single-handedly. Although its Level Five Willpower had sustained serious injuries, it did not have to exert much strength on a Level One small fry. He would exceed the Level One greatly even if they were fighting recklessly.

Bang!! Caught off guard, he ended up grasping at thin air instead as the tip of the club had apparently disappeared a meter in front of him. Next, Red-White could only feel pain in the back of his head. His sensors became fuzzy instantly.

A brief hissing noise could be heard as Clint disappeared before his eyes again.

“Oh… Sh*t!!!” Red-White flared up.

******************

“Just now… What was that? It was awesome!” asked Clint as he ran frantically while enduring the pain with great difficulty.

“It was the Gigantic Magnetic Club and Small Area Spatial Extension Technique. They are fatal moves that are used during critical moments! If you had not destroyed the skin of my Mech, we would have gotten rid of that Red-White who’s hot on our heels earlier on,” replied Red Moon furiously.

“In front!” Clint stopped in his tracks suddenly when a few super-miniature Mechs with Blackboard symbols appeared in front of him. These super-miniature Mechs were only the height of an average person and wore fitted uniforms on their bodies like steel soldiers.

The one similarity between them was the Willpower forces that lingered on their bodies, which were all much stronger than Clint’s.

“You could escape for such a long time despite the captain’s pursuit of you? Stop right there!”

The leading soldier outstretched both of his arms before vibrating Willpower forces shot out of its body suddenly and crashed towards Clint.

Hum…

The distorted Willpower forces resembled a comet. It was colorless and scentless but moved extremely quickly. Three consecutive waves of these forces connected and formed a line that rushed towards him. The floors and walls seemed distorted by the forces as they turned into soft substances that vibrated constantly.

“It’s that guy’s subordinates! Retreat!!” a hint of tiredness could be heard in Red Moon’s voice. “Duck!”

Clint felt as if his body had turned numb to these illusions that were happening now. He was already immune to the strong distortions caused by Dimensional Jumps.

When his vision was blinded suddenly, he appeared in front of the gigantic Black Mech again.

“Eh… What a coincidence…” Clint’s face was deathly pale. He smiled and opened his mouth to speak. “Blegh!!”

He vomited violently again suddenly. The rest of his breakfast came tumbling out, mixed with his yellow bile juices. He remained slumped in the cockpit seat while his entire outfit from the chest downwards was covered in a layer of vomit.

Whoosh!!

A ray of silvery grey light that was reflected off his blade slashed downwards from above.

Clint reacted by swinging the Gigantic Club in front and smashing it this way instantly. The tip of the Gigantic Club disappeared within moments as if it had pierced through thin air before it appeared at the back of the Black Mech’s head.

Clang!

Moments later, a silvery grey machete appeared in front of the Gigantic Club and blocked it. It was barely able to deflect this sneak attack.

“This move is useless against that guy! Damn! Move!” roared Red Moon angrily while Clint was blinded again.

Whoosh whoosh! Two rays of light that were reflected off the blade illuminated Clint’s initial position and left two bright scratch marks there. It was only a moment too slow.

Garen stood on his initial spot quietly while sheathing his sword slowly.

“He can’t run far. Keep pursuing him.”

“Yes,” a few replies echoed from his communication Terminal.

While glancing at the sensory map inside the Mech, he noticed that the red dot was now nearby. Garen continued to breathe more steadily.

“This is your final struggle against death.”

He sat down in the alley while sticking his Dual Blades into both sides of the ground.

**************

“Oh… Blegh…” Clint puked up more large mouthfuls of vomit. There were obvious traces of blood floating around in the rancid puddle. They were signs that the inside of his stomach was bleeding. “I… I can’t do this anymore…”

“How dare you, as a man, admit that something is impossible!! You stupid kid, you never listen when I tell you to practice more often and now you think you know everything! Hurry up and run! You can’t stay here!” yelled Red Moon.

“I can’t… I really can’t…” Clint felt as if his surroundings were spinning. He could not handle these many Jumps despite the foundation of his Nine Mega Cannon Training Method. His body collapsed limply while his eyesight had become slightly fuzzy, making everything look blurry.

“What’s wrong? Did it not work just now…?” Clint could barely run while asking about the previous situation.

“That guy’s reaction speed is way too fast and his basic combat skills are terrifying. People like these are typical cases of exceptionally talented fighters! Most people have secret moves and can attack sneakily but things like that are completely useless against professionals like this!” explained Red Moon quickly. “I’m going to prepare an ultimate move with the last third of my remaining energy.Hopefully, it’ll help us overcome this hurdle. If we’re unsuccessful, we’ll be truly dead this time. With less than two-thirds of my energy left, I will fall into a coma. If that happens, you’ll lose all hope of fleeing and staying alive if you’re left with nothing but your own powers!”

“How much… Time… Do you need?” asked Clint with great difficulty. He did not continue Jumping to allow his body to recuperate slightly. “I can’t do this anymore. I’ll really die if I keep Jumping!”

“I know, your bodily systems and cycles will collapse instantly if you Jump another two times. There won’t be any way for you to survive if you can’t find a way to heal yourself!” replied Red Moon. “Escape this way! The last entrance into the sewers is in front. We will win have the battle once you enter the sewers!”

“I feel like I’m about to die…” Clint was unbearably weak.

“Little Lon is waiting for you at home!! If you don’t want to die just fight for my damn sake!!”

“I…”

“Move!!” Red Moon Blinked immediately before the Mech charged forwards instantly. It leaped across a distance of a few dozen meters before appearing in another alley where the entrance to the sewers lay in front.

The dark black drain cover was like a dreamlike angel now. Through Clint’s eyes, it resembled the most beautiful and perfect bride in the world. He outstretched his arms while hot tears flooded his eyes and charged towards it.

“Ahh~~~ Drain cover!!!” right now, his eyes were brimming with tears.

It seemed as though time had slowed down instantly. This beautiful moment became slower and slower.

Suddenly, a Black Mech walked over slowly and used its strong, tall body to block the drain cover completely while obstructing the path in front of him.

At this moment, the happiness and joyful tears in Clint’s eyes dried up and vanished.

“No~~~!!!”

Chapter 854: Track 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“This is the fugitive that our captain has been pursuing for half a day?” a male voice filled with disdain echoed from the Black Mech. This Mech was slighter smaller than Garen’s Mech and did not look as strong or powerful as Garen’s. Its body was muscular but clearly slimmer and slightly weaker. It held the exact same long silvery grey swords in both of its hands tightly.

If Garen’s Mech resembled a typically powerful and threatening swordsman, this other Mech was simply an unconventional boorish knife wielder.

“This isn’t the previous guy! You have a chance!” yelled Red Moon. “Bl… ink!!”

Shh!!

Clint’s vision became blurry while his own Mech appeared behind the Black Mech. The perfect drain cover appeared in front of him again.

Alexander was both angry and shocked. His opponent had actually disappeared in front of his eyes instantly. When he had just stopped belittling him, he heard an alarm behind himself. He turned around quickly but noticed that Clint was now by the drain cover that was more than ten meters away from him. Clint was currently reaching towards the drain cover.

“You!!”

A ray of white light shot towards him suddenly and struck the waist of Clint’s Mech. The banging noise made him somersault before he was sent flying for quite a distance.

Soon after, a ray of white light that was as thick as a water pipe shot over and hit the cockpit of Alexander’s Mech accurately. Boom!!!

The Mech exploded at once and turned into a fireball from which countless metal fragments burst open.

Alexander catapulted himself out of the cockpit during this moment of imminent danger.

“A Willpower-amplified exploding particle bomb!! He actually dared to use such a dangerous plaything in the district!!” beads of cold sweat had formed on his body while he was flying through the air in a frightened state.

At this moment, Clint was still fine enough to flip himself over and start running immediately. The Red-White Mech continued pursuing him and prepared to open fire. However, it was obstructed by the forces of a shapeless magnetic field instantly.

With Clint as the center, numerous shapeless magnetic field ripples were distributed throughout the surroundings of the Mech suddenly.

“I’m going to lose everything this time!!!” roared Red Moon. “Strong Magnetic Field Shock, Glow!!!”

Screech!!

The magnetic fields around Clint’s Mech were instantly amplified greatly while the range of ripples spread towards all four directions quickly like the waves in the sea. It restrained the Red-White Mech behind it forcefully, making it temporarily unable to move.

The intense magnetic fields caused temporary magnetization to appear throughout more than half of his Mech’s components, seemingly paralyzing his Mech.

Strangely enough, although Clint’s body was in the center of the magnetic field, he was not affected by it at all.

“Run!!” before Red Moon could even finish speaking, Clint lowered his head and ran frantically as if it was a conditioned reflex.

He collided with the wall of a factory with a ‘bang’ and passed through an empty warehouse. He burst out of another wall and crashed into a different alley after that.

“Oh, sh*t!!!”

While Red Moon cursed angrily, Clint stopped suddenly. He froze on his initial spot at the center of the alley.

A drain cover appeared within less than a hundred meters in front of him. Unfortunately, a Blackboard Mech was quietly sitting in front of the drain cover with its legs crossed.

Garen sat inside the Mech quietly in the alley and glared at the damaged Black Mech that Clint was piloting. Red light illuminated both of his Mech’s eyes while he remained unmoving like a sleeping lion.

Kachak.

The Mech stood up slowly. An indescribably oppressive feeling drifted out of its body and spread towards his surroundings faintly.

Clint stood in the alley as well but did not dare to move. Droplets of cold sweat dripped down his temples and the tip of his nose. The frightening aura that this Mech was emitting was much more intense than the damaged Red-White Mech that he had encountered earlier.

“This guy again… He’s part of Blackboard Academy’s patrol squad and at least Level Three!” Red Moon’s tone was both serious and angry. “This is troublesome. Get ready to Blink for a short distance. Can you take it, Clint?”

“…!!”

Clint wanted to cry but did not have any tears left and wanted to vomit but could not do that either. He looked at the magnificent and strong black outer shell of the other person’s Mech that had detailed and exquisite silver patterns. When it stood there, he knew that it was a superior product at first glance. However, he looked at his own Mech and saw a body that was filled with dirty stains and four legs that had missing chunks in some places and numerous dents in others. When he compared both of them, his own Mech merely comprised of odds and ends.

He glanced at the exquisite shiny silvery grey Dual Blades in his opponent’s hands and looked at the dark club that he held. The feelings that were felt by a poor dwarf when he encountered a tall, rich, handsome man resonated within his heart clearly.

“Give me the Forbidden Core and I’ll let you live,” Garen held the Dual Blades and crossed them in front of his chest calmly while making crisp clinking noises.

“Blink!!” hollered Red Moon suddenly. The crippled Mech became distorted suddenly and disappeared on the spot instantly. When it appeared again, it was already more than ten meters behind Garen’s Mech.

Garen remained silent and leaped backward instantly. He flipped around while swinging his machete outwards. He had managed to catch up to Clint within a short period of time.

Bang!!

Moments later, a silvery grey machete cut through the air and stabbed the back of Clint’s Mech’s head violently. The attack caused him to stagger before he took a few quick steps forward suddenly. His head crashed into the side of the wall and formed a large hole in the cement.

“What’s going on? Didn’t I transmit it already?” yelled Clint. Electric sparks glimmered and filled the cockpit. The Mech had suffered serious injuries while the sensors had been sliced through and damaged instantly.

“That guy… isn’t an average Level Three!!” said Red Moon seriously.

“Then what do we do now?!” Clint could hear the heavy footsteps echoing behind him now. The crippled Red-White Mech from the White Light Organization was catching up to him again.

“Don’t panic, just wait for a while first. Things will definitely turn out for the better…” Red Moon lowered his voice. His mind was anxious as well as his initial surefire escape plan was suddenly stopped by a team captain from Blackboard Academy. Numerous fatal flaws had appeared now and he needed to find a way to fix them!

“Where’s the Forbidden Core?” Garen’s voice rang out again. “For a weakling like yourself, possessing treasures that exceed your abilities is an omen of death.”

He took a step forward. “Come, give it to me.”

Clint’s Mech took an involuntary step backward. One hit had fully damaged the sensors in his head. Would he be completely dead after another attack?

Sweat continued to bead on his forehead and drip down his cheeks before falling on his collar and chest. Some of the vomit that had dried up earlier had become moist and sticky again.

“What do I do? What do I do? What do I do….!!!” his mind was a chaotic mess. Clint did not know what to do at all. Red Moon had formed a link with him, but once he was gone, Clint would lose his own life as well. This link was formed by a complete fusion in his body’s genetic level and was not the usual Mech contract.

“Turn left!!” Red Moon’s thunderous roars echoed beside his ears immediately.

Clint operated his Mech and made a left turn by using his conditioned reflexes.

Tch!!

A beam of pure white light swept past the side of his Mech’s body. The laser beam that was initially shooting towards his back hit Garen who was in front of Clint by accident.

Puff!

The laser beam did not hit him but collided with his silvery grey long sword instead and formed shrouds of green smoke there.

During this life-threatening moment, Garen raised his machete and used it to blocked the area in front of him. He was able to accurately deflect the laser beams that were passing through and coming towards him.

“Who!” Garen lifted his eyes and glanced at the other side of the alley behind Clint.

Pfoo… Pfoo… Pfoo…

The sound of violent exhausted panting echoed from there. A Red-White Mech stood on the other side of the white light and held a white Laser Gun that was more than two meters long in its hand. White smoke was faintly wafting out of the barrel.

“I’ve got you… Stupid kid! Let’s see where you’ll run this time!” the Red-White Mech sneered. “The Forbidden Core is mine…!”

“The Red-White Mech? You’ve arrived at such a good time!” Garen crossed his Dual Blades and moved his feet slightly while a fearsome and offensive aura dispersed from his body faintly. The engine at the back of his mech revved slightly and spat out small blue flames. These flames seemed delicate but could actually explode in a terrifying manner at any time.

A crashing noise rang out when he charged forward suddenly. He soared high up into the sky and swung his blades over while the incredibly sharp swords formed ear-piercing shrieks when they tore through the air. Most of the air currents rolled around the alley endlessly as piles of dust were blown around by the blades, forming a strange scene. It seemed as if the empty space within the entire alley had been frozen by the movements of his blades.

Bang!!!

Both of the Mechs collided harshly. The guns in the hands of the Red-White Mech were instantly split into two halves while the Mech stumbled a few steps back and could barely stand up steadily.

“You?!!” only then did the Red-White Mech look towards Garen’s Black Mech. “The team from Blackboard Academy? You’re just a Level Three…”

He dared to taunt him but remained frozen on his initial spot as he was too afraid to make any rash movements. He had been in a good state initially and perhaps had previously assumed that a Level Three individual was not a threat. However, things were different now. Almost eighty percent of his Mech had sustained damage while he was gravely injured as well. A mere Level Three was standing in front of him, but he gave off a threatening air faintly for unknown reasons.

“True Technique — Destruction!!” roared Garen softly. The frequency of his explosions increased within a short span of time and his Mech charged forward suddenly again. Its speed had almost doubled.

Clang!!!

His Dual Blades split into two waterfall-like parts suddenly and sliced towards both sides of the Red-White Mech separately. The light from the blades resembled two muddled ribbons that flitted through the alley and cut the Red-White Mech’s chest and head accurately.

“What the hell?!” the Red-White Mech could only take a step back as thin ripples appeared throughout its body. It managed to slow down the piercing light slightly, allowing its body to barely evade the two blades. However, the cockpit at the front of its chest was still inflicted with a cut that was a few centimeters thick. The cracking sound of damaged electric circuits could be heard, filing the area with the sound of static.

“You bastard…!!!”

It seemed as though the two Mechs had switched places when Garen turned around quickly. He glanced at his own right thigh where a deep cut wound had appeared there suddenly.

“External manifestations in the Mech Energy Fields? As expected of a Level Five expert of White Light.”

When he crossed his Dual Blades, Garen could feel the distorted Willpower Energy Fields that were flowing in his surroundings and wrapping themselves around him. These Energy Fields slowed the movements of his whole body down constantly. It felt as if his entire body was trapped in mud, forcing him to deplete a lot of energy whenever he moved.

“Get lost if you don’t want to die!!” roared the Red-White Mech angrily.

The corners of Garen’s mouth curled and he laughed. The body of his Mech bowed slightly as if he was a tightly-coiled spring that was brimming with a strength that kept growing more frightening.

The Dual Blades were held parallel to both of his arms while the Black Mech itself resembled a crouching male eagle with wings that were slowly being spread.

A bluish-white aura rose from Garen’s body slowly.

Pfoo!!!

The aura dispersed suddenly and caused everything around it to freeze slowly. White frost began forming on the ground while intricate ice crystals appeared on the walls gradually.

Clint stood on the side and shivered from the chill.

“Retreat quickly! It’s Frost Radiation!!” Red Moon reminded him loudly while hints of shock could be heard in his voice. “How is this possible?! Frost Radiation should only appear at the Frozen Lake, so why would it occur here?!”

Clint piloted the Mech backward by several steps for more than ten meters before feeling slightly warmer. However, a thin layer of ice had formed on his body. It was suffocatingly cold.

“No… I can’t do this… I’m going to die…” the vomit that covered his body had frozen and stuck to his body. It seemed as if illusions were appearing in front of his eyes.

“You…??!!” the Red-White Mech was pushed backward by the cold Energy Fields while he looked at Garen in shock.

Garen stood up slowly as bluish-white cold air dispersed throughout the area with him at the center. It seemed as though the cries of a small child were trapped in the cold air. It was strangely horrifying.

Chapter 855: Turning Point 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The battlefield was in a frozen state as the Hellfrost Peacock Technique finally revealed its true strength for the very first time in public.

With Garen’s Mech as the epicenter, a thin layer of frost was created within the radius of at least ten meters. The air turned cool and the strange cry of a kid could be heard everywhere as if it had appeared out of thin air.

“What sorcery is this!!” the Red-White Mech immediately took a few steps back. Although the Mech would be able to maintain its core temperature, the strange child’s cry couldn’t be avoided.

Garen stretched the Mech body as if he was one with the Mech.

“Now that your Energy Field’s been deactivated, what else can you do?’

Before he even finished his sentence, he’d pounced forward and attacked with two slashes which formed blades of light.

Boom!!

The two Mechs collided with each other together as both swords clashed against the spear, leaving two markings that were at least ten centimeters deep.

A huge amount of frost started to propagate from the spear towards the Red-White Mech.

“Go to hell!!” the Red-White Mech shouted as it released all of its Energy Field at full force while retreating at full speed. The Advanced Mech had finally revealed its terrifying potential as its speed was so fast that even Garen wasn’t able to see its afterimage.

What could only be seen were red and white shadows moving about and in that instance, the dagger in its hand was speeding towards Garen’s cockpit. Strangely, it took three turns to actually inflict a blow; it avoided Garen’s block twice before it pierced into Garen’s left shoulder with great precision on its third swing.

Thud!

The dagger pierced deep into Garen’s left Mech shoulder, snapping off one of the most crucial joints.

Gared scoffed as he moved his knee forward, snapping the cracked spear into half and throwing it towards the cockpit in front of him.

The Red-White Mech attempted to evade his attack only to realize that its hand which was holding onto the dagger was grabbed tightly by Garen and he couldn’t move at all. If its body were in a good condition, perhaps it could overcome him with its Mech’s strength which was higher than Garen, but that was not the case here.

Boom!!

A huge amount of Mech debris in white and black spread everywhere. The debris spread everywhere between the two Mechs as both of them suffered serious damage.

Garen couldn’t care less as he released his opponent with his only functional hand. As he attempted to elbow him, he grabbed his blade in reverse and manipulated the edge of the blade with five of his extremely agile Mech fingers and pierced it into the opponent’s cockpit.

With these two unavoidable attacks, both Mechs were glued to each other once more.

Debris started flying everywhere once more as the Red-White mech managed to marginally avoid the attack. However, its waist was seriously damaged

Both Mechs were in a seriously damaged condition and the icy blue frost had already spread out so much that the Red-White Mech’s legs were already frozen, seriously affecting its movement.

For the second time, the Red-White Mech’s pilot felt that death was knocking on his door. He had experienced this when he fought against Red Eye Medero, where he could do nothing but run for his life. However, it was different this time.

“You’re merely a Level Three Mech….!!” he sat inside the Mech with his face blocked by his hair as he raged and trembled. “Just a mere Level Three…!!”

Garen’s expression remained the same as red alarms and sirens kept ringing in his ears while his Mech’s condition worsened by the second.

The red lights flashed directly onto his face but he was completely unaffected by it.

“The last hit.”

Willpower started rippling around his body.

“Crouched Eagle Talon… I’m going all out…”

Bursts of Willpower kept gathering in both his hands and the Mech’s hands at the same time. As one of its arms were already damaged to the point where it could no longer move, the invisible wave only appeared in one of his hands.

Hah!!

As the light flashed, his black arm immediately raised up and the machete in his hand looked like a silver line slashing down from above.

“Reflect!!!”

The Red-White Mech shouted as loud as it could.

As the tip of the machete came in contact with the Red-White Mech, the tremendous amount of energy was instantly absorbed by the Mech in an instant, as if the surface of the Red-White Mech was an endless abyss that took in all of the energy.

At the same time, a huge force bounded out from the Red-White Mech that closely resembled the afterimage of the machete. It was a half transparent afterimage that was made out of pure Willpower!

Garen’s pupils shrunk in that instant as the Willpower surrounding him was dispersed while a stronger Willpower overwhelmed him. However, he was fast enough to evade the speed of the incoming Machete’s afterimage as the afterimage hit onto his right leg.

Clank!!

The afterimage cut off the Black Mech’s leg, and after piercing through its leg, it slammed into the wall just beside Clint’s Mech. Its force was so strong that the wall sunk in, leaving behind a deep indentation.

This made Clint, who was completely worn out, started sweating all over his body.

“This is the infamous Reflect?!” Red Moon was able to understand the ability’s theory clearly. As a fellow Mech, even he couldn’t help but squeal at such a unique ability.

“The Dimensional Reflection Technique. I can’t believe it has been made possible on a non-Inherited Mech… What kind of…” Red Moon didn’t know what word he should use to describe the genius who had invented this ability.

“We should leave as soon as possible… while these two crazies are fighting to their deaths…” Clint who was placed in a series of shock was so mentally exhausted that even his words felt weak.

As Red Moon was about to speak up, he suddenly felt a new wave of energy from the battlefield.

“Fuck me! A Level Four!! A Level Four’s signal!!”

“What Level Four?” Clint asked weakly.

“That Blackboard’s Captain had an unexpected breakthrough during this deathmatch and he is now a Level Four elite!” Red Moon had the urge to spew vulgarities out of his mouth. Upon closer observation, “We’re good. He’s using a training method called the Crouched Eagle Talon that is easy to advance further. I’ve heard of this training method before, where its increment for each level up isn’t huge and can only be considered a below average training method. It’s only advantage is that it’s easy to level up.”

“Does the training method play such a big role?” Clint could barely hold the Mech up as he started walking away slowly from the battlefield.

“It plays a very big role. A Top Inherited training method, such as the Nine Mega Cannon’s one level up can allow you to reach a Mech Level of Three. Every Mech is categorized into its standard Level by its worst condition to the limits that can be theoretically achieved. The categorization would be fixed to the standard and this is the most crucial information that needs to be published the moment a Mech has been announced.” Red Moon explained quickly. “On the other hand, the difference in training methods will show itself by using a Mech of the same Level. You’re Nine Mega Cannon is currently Level One, which increases your strength by about three levels. On the other hand where your opponent uses a typical training method, its typical level up would increase its strength by one level or slightly more. In comparison, there would be a two-level difference in each level up, a four-level difference in two level up, and if you level up three times, the difference would be six levels apart. The further you level up, the more drastic the difference. This is just based on simple calculation without any change in factors. Realistically speaking, the Top Inherited training method would improve in all aspects instead of just one.”

Red Moon was very wary of the condition of the battle.

“That Captain operating the Mech should be using the Crouched Eagle Talon. Hence a level Four increment would equal to a Level Four power, which was used on the Mech’s arm to instantly increase its power. This gives a huge boost in hardening its arm, which is his training method’s effect.”

“What about that Red-White guy?”

“He should be using a slightly better training method. Judging from the looks of it, it should be an above-average tier. With one level up, it is able to increase its speed and duration of the power source by one level. This is also the reason why even though his Mech is eighty to ninety percent damaged, he could still chase him for a long period of time. If it were a typical Mech, it’d been no longer operational a long time ago,” Red Moon stared at it closely. “The Red-White is a Level five pilot, so his increment, by right, should be at Level five as well. However, with the pilot seriously injured, the Mech is unable to perform at its full potential. Since he has exhausted his Willpower as well, his current Level is at most Level Four. In addition to all of these, his opponent’s melee combat skill is extraordinarily good to the point where he can predict his moves and attack or defend in advance, resulting in the current stalemate situation…”

“Be careful!!” he started shouting.

Clint paused instantly and a thud could be heard as a huge stone slammed into the wall in front of him like a cannon, indenting the wall by a considerable amount of depth. It was a stone that had been sent flying from the battle behind.

He was so shocked that cold sweat leaked from his body profusely. With his Mech’s current condition, this huge boulder would’ve taken away his puny life if not for Red Moon’s Protection Field.

“Alright, let’s keep moving,” Red Moon ordered.

Clint turned his head back to look at the battlefield.

Two Mechs, one black and the other white, were entangled together as waves of powerful Energy Field and cool air spread out, distorting the environment and air in the surrounding. It was so great that even light waves were started to distort faintly and he could only see two Mech silhouettes fighting against each other.

Both Garen and Red-White were fighting to their deaths.

Although Garen’s fighting instincts were very overwhelming, the opponent was stronger with his short bursts of Level five Willpower. In combination with the difference in Levels between their Mechs, he could only match the opponent’s strength even though he had used his potential points to attain the power of a Level Four.

It was especially true towards the reflective technique which he couldn’t understand, as he’d finally experienced the trouble in dealing with these White Light Mechs firsthand. He truly was an elite that could avoid being caught within Blackboard Region for such a long time.

However, even though his opponent was strong and had a powerful Level five Willpower Reflection technique, he was able to see through his opponent’s intention with his Ten Thousand True Technique Battle Skills so that he could defend himself beforehand while attacking his weak points. He was able to fight toe to toe with him even though the opponent’s Mech was stronger than his in every aspect.

The Hellfrost Peacock Technique was barely able to cancel out the opponent’s Level five Willpower’s Deceleration Force Field as both Mechs’ reaction speeds were lowered down to an observable level. However as the Cold Chaos’s level was slightly lower, he was slowly being restrained by the opponent’s Energy Field.

Garen could feel that the strain towards the Mech and his body was stronger over time.

As he had a very strong body, he wasn’t really affected by it, but it was not the case for his Mech as it was a standard Level Three model of the Academy. In addition to this, his Mech was far inferior as compared to the Level five Mech and the strain was worse with the interference of the Energy Field, to the point where moving had started to prove difficult. The chances of him winning were fluctuating up and down.

The person inside the Red-White Mech was worse off as the strange cry of a child kept echoing in his ears. No matter how much he tried to filter out the noise, it kept disrupting his thoughts and mentality. It was so annoying to the point where he started to feel uncomfortable and his consciousness started turning muddled.

Deep down inside him, he had an urge to release all of the stress that was welling up inside him.

However, he controlled himself from doing so as he knew very well that if he were to act impulsively and go all out without caution in this deathmatch between two Level Four’s, he would be, without a doubt, the one that would be instantly killed!

However, the more he tried to control himself, the stronger his urge became.

He started to feel annoyed as he couldn’t find his opponent’s weakness even after fighting with him for so long, as he seemed to be extremely experienced in melee combat. It was as if he was a veteran that had just come out from a dead volcano. He had even used a few techniques in order to trick his opponent, but the opponent seemed to see through his intention in an instant and countered him. Even his most confident Duplicate Chain had been seen through, and he had no choice but to fight against him without any tricks.

Chapter 856: Turning Point 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Damn it!!!”

A typical Level Three or Four would have made a mistake within ten moves and he would have used the opportunity to finish him off, unlike the current situation. While he still had the upper hand in terms of speed, he had no choice but to fight the opponent without any tricks, especially against that hardened arm that had obviously been enhanced through a training method to the point where it rivaled his Level Five body. Both Mechs’ conditions worsened as their battle continued.

With his Mech that was on the verge of breaking, if this continued…

Both of them were fighting to their deaths, and at this point of the battle, the two things that would change the tide of the battle were stronger will and Willpower.

Garen remained expressionless even though one of his Mech’s legs and arms had been torn off and he could only fight with his remaining hand and shield himself with his crippled hand. With his sword-wielding hand, he was able to set up a layer of defense in front of him. Although he was a master in fist technique, he also had some experience in sword techniques. With a sword as an extension of his arm, he could still fight on the same level.

One could say that Willpower resembled the Mech’s internal energy. As both Mechs fought against each other, it increased the hardness Garen’s arm and strength for a short amount of time whereas it increased the Red-White’s speed and stamina.

While it increased their physical capabilities, both of their Willpowers were clashing against each other in its most primitive form.

As Garen’s Willpower was weaker by a Level and didn’t possess the same quality as his opponent, he had to deactivate it within two seconds or else his WIllpower would gradually be reduced. Once his opponent had infiltrated his body, it would spell his defeat.

Clank!!

The dagger and machete from both Mechs clashed against each other as the blades started to chip away slowly. In this high-level battle, even their weapons were unable to withstand the impacts and had started to break down even though they were enhanced with Willpower.

As the Willpower’s Energy Field clashed with radioactive coolness, it formed an absolute isolation barrier within an area of several tens of meters. The frost that had just formed on the ground immediately shattered and the flow of the frost was slowed down by the Energy Field as it was gradually overpowered by it. However, the strange cry of a child wasn’t affected at all.

One of the Red-White Mech’s leg and two of its hands had been unevenly damaged. As it separated from Garen’s Mech, it leaned its back against the wall as panting could be heard from the cockpit.

The Red-White pilot was started seeing illusions as he kept seeing spots of red light resembling Mars moving about in front of him and obstructing his vision. He rubbed at his eyes in an attempt to clear his vision, but the number of red spots was increasing, to the point that it was starting to affect his vision.

After all, he was a Level Four pilot that was boosted to Level Five too quickly. His foundation wasn’t solid enough due to the sudden level up. In addition to that, his Willpower wasn’t strong enough as well. As he was had lived and worked under oppression and fear within White Light, the Cold Chaos had finally found its way into affecting his spirit in this hopeless situation.

“Hehe… Mother… I see you, mother… Where are you? Don’t go…” his consciousness was starting to become muddy as saliva started dripping out of his mouth while it was wide open. Hallucinations started to visualize in front of him as well.

He opened his arms wide as he attempted to hug something though there was nothing there.

Garen walked towards him and stared at the Red-White Mech which had already slumped onto the ground.

“Mother… Don’t leave me behind… Don’t throw me away…” the effect of the Cold Chaos became stronger as the Red-White pilot’s consciousness was thrown into utter chaos. He seemed to have submerged himself into his deepest memories.

“Sob… It’s hot… so hot…”

Garen raised his long sword.

Chop!!

**********

Clint leaped as he maneuvered the Mech to avoid a chain of cannons. Under Red Moon’s instructions, he had managed to escape from a group of Miniature Mechs with his agile mobility.

“Quickly!!!”

Red Moon kept urging him.

“I’m doing my best!!” blood started trickling out from Clint’s eyes, ears and nose as he evaded a sudden ambush with a high-difficulty maneuver. As he kept jumping to run for his life earlier, it had put a serious strain on his body over time. Although his internal organs were protected by a top class training method, Willpower Protection, large areas of his organs had started bleeding profusely after so much exertion.

“I…” as he tried to open his mouth to speak up, a mouthful of blood obstructed his throat and he couldn’t voice out at all.

“You!!” Red Moon could sense how serious the situation was.

Sizzle!!!

The Mech stopped moving abruptly.

The Blackboard Mech eventually caught up to him in front of the alley in front. He stood at the entrance of the alley as he waited for Clint.

Compared to Clint who didn’t have a suspension system, Garen basically flew instead of running on the ground as it was much faster this way.

“It’s over,” Garen threw the head of the Red-White Mech which he was holding onto the ground, and it rolled solidly to the side of Clint’s Mech.

The Miniature Mech’s Pilots slowly stepped back as they only attacked within the shadows. They couldn’t be discovered by everyone else. They had given a valid excuse to the other households that they were helping the Blackboard Region with its public order. They had achieved their objective, which was to delay the pace of Clint’s Mech so that he would slow down. Their objective was never to destroy him as that mission should be completed by Nonosiva himself.

Gradually, signs of activities around the alley cease to exist, leaving only Garen and Clint facing each other.

“The Forbidden Core,” Garen reached out his hand. “Give it to me. You’re still a child, and you shouldn’t be living a life of fleeing every day. You should be in school enjoying your youth, friends, and romance. You’re not supposed to run for your life in a dirty sewer.”

He tried to use his words to affect Clint’s mentality.

He, too, was afraid that Clint would destroy the core out of determination. No one knew if the forbidden core was solid or fragile because no one had really seen the item before. It could be of any shape and state.

However, he knew that his opponent was just a kid as he didn’t cover up his voice while speaking.

“I…” Clint took a step back as the horrifying battle between the Black and Red-White Mech kept replaying in his mind. The opposing party had managed to win against the Red-White Mech and he knew that he couldn’t defend himself against him.

Kachak…

Garen’s Mech moved towards him slowly as he managed to temporarily fix the broken parts with his backup supply to the point where it didn’t affect the Mech’s normal activity. With it functioning perfectly, this had increased the fear and pressure in Clint’s mind so much so that he started shivering.

“Your heart is seriously damaged. You’ll die within two hours if you don’t accept any treatment,” Garen applied more mental pressure to his opponent. He was able to clearly sense the opponent’s concealed heart with his extremely strong senses.

Clint was on the verge of crying… It wasn’t that he didn’t want to hand it over to him, it’s that he would die too if he handed it over.

“Between death and your treasure, are you still confused as to which one is more important? Perhaps the forbidden core had formed a connection with you to the point that you were unable to hand it over to me?” Garen guessed calmly.

Clint shivered as Garen was able to come to a logical conclusion that was closest to the truth by just observing his actions. This terrifying manifestation…

“Is this the strength of a Level Four and Level Five pilot??” he was traumatized.

Boom!!

Within the loud explosion, Garen pounced towards him and punched Clint’s cockpit on the left which sent the Mech flying away. The Mech crashed into the wall on the side. Garen followed tightly and stepped onto Clint’s chest with his foot. He then raised his machete up high as the tip of the blade glistened.

His action was so fast that Clint had not been able to react in time at all. He was still in a mentally shaken state and in addition to that, his body was so seriously injured that he didn’t have any energy left to evade. He could only tell that his vision had immediately turned muddy and the sky had started spinning about. The next thing he knew, he was already down on the ground and the Machete which was held high up and about to pierce down.

His mind was totally blank, as he stared at the sharp edge of the knife.

Tsk!!!

“Brother! No!!”

In that exact moment, a familiar voice shouted at Garen from his side.

However, the sword had already pierced into the cockpit.

Blood was slowly flowing out from the cracks of the cockpit.

A similar Black Pieced-together Mech entered the alley, appearing beside Garen. The cockpit cover opened up slowly, revealing an elegant girl sitting inside it.

Garen looked over. Although he was sure that he heard his brother’s voice…

He moved his lips as he looked at the elegant girl whose face was stained with tears. Although her hair was black and she had a pair of almond-shaped eyes and small lips with a pale skin tone, the mental state was clearly…

“Brother…” the woman cried hysterically as she shouted.

Garen pondered for a while as he finally put together the beautiful girl in front of him and the man he recalled in his memory.

“You… You’re Lon?!”

Baylon bit her lips as she nodded her head.

“Clint, he’s my friend…” for the very first time, she dared to look at Nono in the eye. She had never dared to look her brother in the eyes since young.

However, this time could be the only time in her entire life she had ever done so. Perhaps it was the training method that had changed her, or perhaps it was because she was worried about Clint.

Even Garen didn’t know what to do in this situation.

Clint’s Mech made a ruckus as it rolled about after pulling the sword out of itself. He rolled to the other side of the wall, leaning against it as Clint panted loudly inside the cockpit.

His left thumb had been chopped off and his left leg was almost completely amputated by the machete. He was very fortunate that Red Moon had twisted the trajectory of the machete with his Manipulation Field at the very last second. If he had not done so, he surely would have died to this attack.

However, every sacrifice came with a price; Red Moon had exhausted the very last bit of his energy and had fallen into a coma.

“It’s fortunate that I called Lon here. Don’t worry, you’ll be fine. Lon’s Willpower is best at healing wounds… I will need about ten days to replenish my energy, so if you don’t have anything to do, go sunbathe or something…” Red Moon parted with his final words as he went into a comatose state.

Garen was still looking at Baylon as she struggled.

Baylon immediately pulled Clint up as she stared at Garen sorrowfully while holding Clint up. She then brought him along and disappeared into the entrance of the sewer with her face dripping with tears.

Garen moved the Machete in his hand but didn’t pursue them any further. The Mech standing still within the shadows was like a sculpture.

A Black Mech then landed just beside Garen.

“Captain! Are you just going to let them go like this? Even if she’s your sister, you…”

Clank!! Buzz…!!

Garen immediately cut the Black Mech in half as he slashed his blade downwards.

Boom!!

The Black Mech immediately exploded and turned into a ball of flame.

The fire bathed Garen’s Mech in red light as he put his blade away. He stared in the direction which Baylon had left and walked away in the opposite direction.

Chapter 857: Clue 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What’re you going to do?”

Inside a silence room within Celine’s household, Garen and Celine were sitting facing each other as they casually ate deer jerky as snacks.

“To think that you’d kill one of your patrols, isn’t it hard to explain it to the higher-ups?” Celine looked at Garen lazily who sat opposite her.

“Indole died while on duty as he fought bravely against the terrorist. It was unfortunate that he died as he attempted to protect me,” Garen casually responded.

“Do you really think the higher levels will believe you?” Celine curled her lips.

“Does it matter whether they do or don’t?” Garen couldn’t care less. “Regardless, we have sacrificed a lot in the battlefield. One of my men died in the line of duty, a Mech was destroyed and I myself have suffered serious injuries. Ultimately we still managed to detain the terrorist of the White Light. The result is more than enough. Furthermore, the majority of the people do not know about the Forbidden Mech, so the outsiders would only view this as a battle between the terrorist group and the patrol team.”

“How do you plan to deceive your way out of this?” Celine wasn’t convinced at all.

“What do you mean deceive?” Garen frowned as he picked up a glass of red fruit wine and lightly sipped it. “I did my best and defeated a Level Five Red-White Mech. Although the enemy was seriously injured, it’is still a feat that could only be done by a few. Furthermore, didn’t your men handle the rest while I took care of most of the small fries?”

“You can’t deceive the higher levels with such an excuse. It’s still acceptable if you plan to deceive them in the short term, however, the beans will spill in the long term. Even I can’t guarantee that things won’t leak out even though I’ve gathered so many men,” Celine glanced at Garen and felt that this man was cruel to the core as he was able to kill his partner that he’d just teamed up with. He was completely different from the typical student and was the type of person who would not stop at anything once he had snapped.

“Don’t worry about it,” Garen smiled. “The most important thing is that I won by a slight margin, the Forbidden Core had escaped and is not in my hand. Everyone will definitely set their eyes on the Forbidden Core. Furthermore, the White Light’s Mech definitely has a technological instrument that is able to track the Forbidden Core. As long as we have that instrument, the most they would do is to not credit the whole thing to me.”

“Seriously?” Celine didn’t think of this at all. “As long as we have the tracking device, we will definitely be able to track the location of the Forbidden Core and you’ll definitely be cleared of suspicion. If that’s the case, then the most dangerous period is the buffer period we’re in right now. Even so, with your identity, Britney and a bunch of us around you, and that man from the Polar Region, the higher levels will definitely have second thoughts about killing you.”

As her thought process chained up to this point, she finally let out a sigh of relief.

“Since you know about this, wouldn’t it be the same if you let the core escape? The moment the higher ups get their hands on the Red-White Mech’s tracking device, they would mobilize the majority of Blackboard Region’s power and then finding these few people won’t be too hard of a task,” Celine puzzled.

“Does that matter? If they can’t survive this little obstacle, it’s better for them to just die,” Garen shrugged nonchalantly.

“Seriously…” Celine was hopeless. “Whatever, whatever. Thinking of all these is give me headaches. Let’s go! Let’s have a match!” she immediately stood up. “If you make me worry again, I will beat you up for real!!” She raised her fist and said angrily.

“That’s fine since you can’t beat me, to begin with,” Garen continued sipping his drink slowly without any change in expression as if he was asking for a beating.

“You…!”

***********

In the warehouse area.

It was the battlefield where Garen and the Red-White had fought to the death. A man and a woman had come to the area with a mechanical arm-like instrument. The police force had already locked the entire place down; the police car’s lights kept spinning and as it shone onto the people within the area, it revealed their strange expressions.

Both of them walked through the blockade and as they arrived at the barrier, they gently placed their hand on the barrier.

“Beep… Verification of the Special Detectives is complete. Please enter.”

A beautiful woman’s voice rang out of nowhere.

The officers inside the area turned their heads around and looked at the newcomers. The bystanders too turned their attention towards them.

“Special Detectives?”

Among the crowd, a middle-aged man who had a mottled beard tipped his hat and looked at them through the gap as well.

“Even the Special Detectives have arrived for this terrorist attack. I heard that the government would only send these officers to the scene if the situation is extremely serious,” a civilian whispered.

“What actually happened here to the point where they had to make a huge scene and lock down the whole warehouse area?”

“I heard that there was an intense battle between the terrorist and the patrol team. Ultimately, the patrol team won by a slight margin but they had lost three Mechs and one of the academy students died in the line of duty”

An uncle laughed, “It looks like a scandal. This has never happened in the past. However, ever since the assassination of that military officer, trouble started to appear everywhere.”

“What trouble?”

The bearded man questioned him, acting as if he was a bystander as well, “Do you mean the assassination of one of the Three Black Rain Generals?”

“I’m afraid not, as that incident had already spread out. The assassin has yet to be caught and is on the wanted list everywhere. The higher-ups have tried to suppress the incident multiple times but to no avail, and it has been spread about everywhere. Perhaps the Pilots from the White Light Group have infiltrated everywhere in this region and have been carrying out their activities in the dark,” The uncle continued chuckling. “I migrated here as I heard that it would be safer here in the Blackboard Region, but…” he shook his head.

The bearded man pondered for a while and quietly left the crowd after listening to them for a while. He then took out his Watch Terminal, called a number and reported the news over.

Inside the alley.

Two Special Detectives were squatting down at the center of the alley as they examined the area thoroughly.

“There’re traces of strong Willpower in the area and it’s obvious that it’s a Level Five Energy Field,” the male Special Detective murmured. “It should be from the White Light Group’s Mech of the report. Have you discovered anything over there?”

The female Special Detective frowned as she reached out her finger and touched the layer of white stains on the wall. Her blue irises started rotating as if her eyeballs were rotating together and it looked very inhuman. However, it only lasted for a moment before it returned back to their normal state.

“Surprisingly, there’s a trace of Cold Radiation… Although someone tried to eliminate it on purpose, I could still sense a slight trace of radiation left behind.”

“Cold Radiation? Is it from the Quick Frost Grenade?” the man asked softly.

“I’m afraid… According to the report, this is the location where the Blackboard’s top student fought with the terrorist. One of them most likely possessed a secret weapon,” the woman shook her head.

“Officer, we’ve found something! Come take a look!” the police force’s captain called as he walked towards them.

As both of them walked over to him, they saw that the captain was holding a small exquisite white stone sculpture in his Traceless Glove. The stone looked like a man was squatting down or sitting on his knees, and its face and attire were unclear to the point where it looked like a stone that was shaped naturally. As to why it was exquisite, the back of the stone’s head was etched with a detailed and complicated circular texture which looked to be a magical formation of overlapping circles.

“What’s this?”

“I’ve found it on the body of the terrorist. I can’t believe this thing is still intact after that explosion. Even our researcher isn’t able to detect what this item is made from,” the police captain said as he walked towards them. This man, who was known for his sharp observation, was a muscular man who had climbed up from the bottom of the ladder to become an elite pilot.

“This is…” the female detective took the item and examined it closely. “This is an ancient tracking device…”

“Perhaps…?” the male detective seemed to have recalled something.

At the same time, the female detective had thought of something as well and they exchanged glances with each other.

“Let’s report it immediately!”

“What about the remaining traces of radiation?”

“Ignore it. The most important thing now is that we need to find out is if this is what we think it is!”

**********

In the sewers.

It was dark, cold and smelly.

Two scraped-together black Mechs walked slowly as they moved forward.

Clint’s wound had been healed by Baylon’s Willpower. Although it wasn’t a complete heal, it was able to prevent his injury from worsening.

Time passed by.

After running for a considerable amount of time, both of them felt safer when they arrived at a place deep the sewers, which Red Moon had arranged earlier. This place was narrow but it was big enough to fit two Mechs.

“Sigh…” Clint opened up the cockpit and walked out from it. He was extremely dirty as he laid on the ground. He was fortunate that Baylon didn’t mind how dirty he was at all as she carried him along.

“Your injury is very serious, so stop moving about!!” Baylon felt relieved when she saw Clint’s wound; her Willpower was able to release a Life Field that would supply life force to Clint. At the same time, it would cast a layer of absolute protection which prevented bacteria from invading his body.

“Lon… How did you know that that was your brother?” Clint tried his best to put a smile on his face as this pain was nothing compared to Red Moon’s daily ‘teachings’… No, Red Moon’s classes were much more painful than this, which was the reason why he was able to endure the pain for a long period of time.

“It was uncle Red Moon who told me about it,” Baylon responded as she found a grooved metal piece that she could use to pour some water on him. Although the water in the sewer was dirty, it could still be used to wash one’s body after filtering it with the Mech’s system.

“Red Moon said so? What’s going on?” Clint wasn’t able to move at all from the moment he relaxed. He started to feel dizzy, and he could only lay down and wait for death even if he were to be placed in the same dangerous situation he had just experienced. As he calmed down and gave the biggest sigh of relief in his life, his body switched to recovery mode.

This was similar to someone wanting to sleep after too much training. However, as Clint was afraid that he might never wake up if he fell asleep, he tried to stay awake and kept finding topics to talk about. Most of the movies he had watched had people who slept and passed away peacefully, which had traumatized him deeply.

“He told me to rush over as you were in grave danger. He even told me that my brother… my brother, he…” Baylon looked at Clint’s missing left thumb and his left leg that had been on the verge of being amputated. Although the wound had stitched up together, it was still shocking to see the red flesh and she was very guilty about it.

“I’m sorry Clint. It’s my fault. I only wanted to go home and see my parents, brother, and sister. I didn’t expect… expect everything would unfold like this…” she couldn’t help herself but to cry once more.

“Don’t blame it on your brother. I believe he has his reasons,” Clint tried his best to act that he didn’t care at all as he patted her hair. “I’m a person who has done many good deeds and good karma will definitely come back for me. See, I didn’t die, right? If your brother didn’t evade at the very last second, I’m sure I would have died from it.”

He didn’t know that it wasn’t Garen’s error but Red Moon’s handiwork; he had twisted the space to save Clint’s life. As Red Moon didn’t mention anything about this to him, he really believed that Garen had decided to not kill him at the very last second.

“But your finger…” tears kept rolling down from Baylon’s red eyes.

“Didn’t Master Red Moon said that I will be fine? Don’t worry about it. This isn’t something you should bear alone as I wanted to go back and visit my sister as well. Stop feeling bad about it, I didn’t die, right?” Clint comforted her clumsily.

“Did Red Moon really say so?” Baylon continued crying as she asked skeptically.

“Definitely. Although I’m not sure why I’m sure he has his reasons, “Clint nodded. “Your brother is a good person, it’s just that he doesn’t express it. In fact, he’s the type of person who would act coldly on the outside but feel emotional on the inside! Trust me on this, for I have never judged people wrongly with my experience!” he smiled as he revealed his set of white teeth.

“You really don’t blame him for this?”

“Yes. Really.”

Baylon pondered for a moment as she bit her lips.

“Then… can I send some of the items to him? Now that I’ve become like so, no one should know except for you and me…”

Clint was helpless as the situation changed too quickly.

Chapter 858: Clue 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At noon, Garen and Celine were sparring again in the training room. After correcting her flaws and mistakes and training her hard, Garen left Celine’s place as he sat in the Levitating Car which had come to pick him up.

The Charm Mercenary group’s leader had personally driven the car to fetch him.

The captain of the group who had shoulder-length golden curly hair was none other than Inari.

This elegant captain who was in the driver seat kept looking at Garen who sat beside her. She seemed to have obtained intel of his battle in the alley.

“What are you looking at, Ms. irresponsible Captain?” Garen glanced at her coldly. “You didn’t finish a single one of the tasks I’d assigned to you. I feel that it’s pointless to hire you guys.”

Inari was slightly frozen as she didn’t expect Garen to scold her the moment he opened his mouth.

“Sir Nono, please don’t be mean to us. We are doing our best. You have to understand that the White Light’s Mech was overwhelmingly powerful. We’re just Level One and Two Pilots. How could we ever hope to fight against those Level Five elites?”

“Then what’s the point of me hiring you people?” Garen adjusted his hair which had been blown around by the wind as he looked at the view through the windshield while they sped along the highway.

“We weren’t just sitting there and do nothing, Sir Nono,” Inari smiled. It was the very first time that she had worked with a man that treated them equally as a mercenary. In the past, all their employers were just men who kept staring them as if they were some sort of meat instead of mercenaries.

This time around, she felt a sense of respect from Garen’s attitude. It was a respect that she had been yearning for a long time.

“Let’s hear about it. What can you guys do?” Garen asked softly.

Inari smiled again once more.

“I assume you’ve heard of the pulse wave incident, right?”

Garen nodded as he had just received intel on it from Kendall that the special detectives that had been mobilized by the higher-ups had focused their attention on the tracking device. They were too busy to pay heed to his radiation and the death of his team member. Even the portrayal of his immense talent and battle sense were neglected. It was obvious that the Forbidden Core was so important that the higher-ups were willing to ignore the rest.

He was happy with the results as well. If he were to obtain the core and hand it over, he might have been silenced by them as well. After all, no one could be sure that he hadn’t obtained any mysterious intel from the core. He would be dead the moment there was the slightest suspicion towards him.

This result was the best for him, where the higher-ups managed to obtain the tracking device. When he returned back to his team, he had purposely stabbed his Mech to make it seem like he was seriously injured from the Reflection and was too weak to chase after them. This was to prevent him from being suspected.

He was barely able to suppress the issue as this issue itself could be serious on its own. He was fortunate that he had been in good relationships with the higher-ups and Britney had tried to speak on behalf of him. In addition to that, Celine had sent people to tend the matter along with the Honorable Noble. Hence, the higher-ups had stopped going after him and focused their full attention on the Forbidden Core’s tracking device.

As he came back to his senses, Inari had already started her explanation.

“The main culprits of the pulse wave incident were the elites from the white light group,” she said softly. “It wasn’t one of their members that you’d faced but their actual elite!”

“Oh?” Garen felt worried now; he had to reveal his trump card to fight, and even so, he had barely been able to kill a typical member who was in a seriously injured condition. If he were in perfect condition, Garen would’ve been the first one to run away.

It was similar to a young trainee who had encountered a legendary elite. Their skills were not of the same rank and they weren’t even just a level apart. Garen could’ve died from his internal energy alone.

If the person and his Mech were in a good condition, he wouldn’t have been able to move from his Energy Field and he wouldn’t be able to use any battle skills at all.

“The White Light Group has the Shining Mech, which was the one you’ve encountered. The one who had performed the assassination was a Great Light Mech, which is considered a leader who manages the Shining Mech. He possesses incredible strength!” Inari said seriously. “Also, I’ve heard some intel regarding the Great Light Mech.”

“How is that related to me?” Garen questioned back.

“Since you’ve killed one of their Shining Mechs, regardless if he was a traitor, you’re the main reason the Blackboard Region’s higher-ups have obtained the tracking device from the Mech. The opponent will definitely hunt for you when they fight against the higher-ups,” Inari was very direct with a slight sense of ridicule in her tone. “When that time comes, no matter how gifted you are, the result of fighting against a few Level Fives and an even stronger pilot in the perfect condition would spell…”

“That is my issue,” Garen narrowed his eyes.

“So? Do you know how important we are now?” Inari smiled as she continued driving. Suddenly she felt something crawling up into her white T-shirt from below which went straight to her breasts. Her bra was taken off and both of her breasts were squeezed tightly and all she felt was an immense pain.

“You!!” her face blushed. Since she was driving on the road at high speed, she didn’t dare to take her hands off the wheel else she would risk being in an accident.

Inari felt that her breasts were being fondled with as though they were just toys. This made her very embarrassed.

“Even if you’re useful in this aspect, so what?” Garen casually responded as he felt the soft sensation on his hand without changing his facial expression. “Everything else is just an excuse if you don’t perform your duty.”

Inari suddenly felt that her T-shirt was being pulled upward. The side windows of the car were transparent. Without the cover, everyone on the streets could’ve seen her body the moment her shirt was taken off.

“Don’t you dare!!” Inari gritted.

“I am only giving you a warning,” Garen gently tapped on her body and a cold item came out from his sleeve and stuck lightly onto the underside of Inari’s breasts.

It was a light blue ball of meat. As it stuck onto her skin, it naturally opened up like a crumpled paper attempting to return back to its original shape. It soon became thinner and thinner until it was completely attached to her skin. Then, it started assimilating into the skin.

However, Inari didn’t seem to realize at all as she squirmed her body about embarrassingly, trying to get away from Garen’s hand.

The Distorted Seed…

Garen had created the seed of the Hellfrost Peacock which could create monsters. He then gently placed it into Inari’s heart. As long as he willed it, it would instantly explode and turn Inari into a chaotic radioactive monster.

Garen put away his hands without any change in his expression as if he had done nothing at all.

“If you like this kind of foreplay, I’ll let you play with Julie and the others when we get back instead of fooling around on the highway! Please hold yourself back!” Inari scolded in embarrassment.

“I’m not satisfied with your attitude,” Garen reached out his hand and pinched Inari’s chin.

Crack!!

“Ah!!! You…!!” Inari felt an intense pain in her chin, so strong that the sound of bone cracking could be heard. Her inklings of pride and contempt were immediately replaced by a sense of fear.

“A decoration has its own uses,” Garen moved his hands away calmly.

“Are you still a man! How dare you touch me when you can’t win verbally!”

“Of course, isn’t this what men do best?” Garen questioned her back.

Inari was speechless.

“Alright let’s stop fooling around. Drive the car safely,” Garen had a sudden interest in releasing his Distorted Seed’s parasite into her. He wanted to try out how effective it is and would activate it when the opportunity arose.

He decided on Inari as his subject because he had the right opportunity and this girl seemed to be very mysterious as well. She also seemed to have a rich amount of intel and channels, and hence she could be his ears.

He suddenly realized that he now had a lot of sudden urges to fool around, unlike back in the days where he kept fighting for his life. All this time, his life was about fighting and nothing else.

“Is this the effect of having more Soul Seeds?” he touched his chin as he listened to Inari’s complaints.It seemed that Inari wasn’t completely rejecting his ‘sudden ambush’. This was most likely because of his battle strength and his wealth, which gave this materialistic woman a good impression.

After putting away all these nonsensical thoughts, Garen recalled the scenario where he had let Clint and his brother escaped.

As his sword was bent in that instant, he had heard a voice from the cockpit, or one could say that the voice had been directly transferred into his consciousness.

“What you really need is a truly powerful Willpower Training Method. With your talent, you’re burying it by only using the Crouched Eagle Talon,” this voice immediately pointed out his weakness.

Garen stopped moving as he stood still. Although Baylon was speaking beside him and Clint was moving, he focused his attention on the voice.

“Who are you? What are you trying to tell me?” he tried to question back in his mind.

“I want your core, are you interested in doing a trade with me?” the voice continued asking.

“Trade? Can you give me what I want?”

“Naturally.”

After exchanging information.

Garen moved his machete and chose not to chase after Baylon and Clint who were running away.

He had originally planned on persuading the person who had the core to pursue what he needed, but he didn’t expect that the opponent had thought of working with him as well.

What he didn’t expect the most was that his own brother had turned into that appearance. Furthermore, he seemed to be in a good relationship with the man who possessed the core.

He didn’t plan to kill Clint as well and followed along with the flow when his machete was diverted. He wanted to observe in detail how different a person who could shock the Soul Seed was as compared to the rest.

In the end, both of them were satisfied with the results.

However, the only thing Garen was unsatisfied was to see that his brother Baylon was dressed up like a girl, or perhaps he had a transsexual operation, as it didn’t make any sense for him to turn into that state. Fortunately, he had killed the only witness and no one knew that his brother was related to the person who possessed the core.

Chapter 859: Line of Sight 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Fortunately, the core had given him a training method that seemed to be rather unique.

After the warehouse incident, Garen had downloaded the confidential document that was transferred via the core to him from the Mech’s computer. He then proceeded to wipe off all traces of it once he had done so. Once he had reached home and recovered the data, he made sure that he did not leave behind any loopholes multiple times before he deleted all the records. He even destroyed the hard disc and used a new one in order to prevent any leaks.

“After this incident, I should start analyzing the training methods that I obtained,” according to Garen’s estimation, this training method was no ordinary training method as it was at least a Level Five. However, he had no intention of retraining himself. If he were to abandon his Crouched Eagle Talon, it would be extremely difficult as his Willpower had already taken to its shape. Similar to a stone sculpture, it would be difficult to change it to another shape once its external shape was formed. He would have to exhaust more material and time if he were to start over.

As Inari kept driving along the road, Garen was thinking of a way to further perfect his Crouched Eagle Talon.

He didn’t plan to abandon this training method at all. In fact, he planned to improve it.

This was because the new training method was completely irrelevant to the Crouched Eagle Talon in terms of the involvement of body parts. The three main body parts involved with the Crouched Eagle Talon were the hands and chest.

On the other hand, the new training method involved his head, legs, and the back, which was the most important part. There were a total of four body parts and they did not overlap with the Crouch Eagle Talon. This seemed to have been considered by the Core.

Two training methods could be overlap and not interfere with each other. This was equivalent to wearing two sets of equipment and utilizing one of them whenever needed.

Unfortunately, the Crouched Eagle Talon could only go up to Level Five. Naturally, he could go the Eagle’s Nest and spend his Quest Points or Contribution Points to obtain the information for all five levels. However, the price wasn’t cheap as it was at least equivalent to hundreds of thousands of Universal Units.

Even so, the Crouched Eagle Talon was still a high-cost performance training method to the public since there were very few training methods that could reach Level Five.

Garen had realized that the strength of his Crouched Eagle Talon was just a mere Level Three. This was probably because he would need a military identity to reach Level Four. Before taking on the mission, he would have had no opportunities to be qualified to possess such an identity. However, after contributing to them with his strength, it was slightly easier for him to obtain a military identity and it should not be a problem for him to obtain all five levels of the training method.

Beep beep… Beep beep…

As Garen was lost in his thoughts, his watch started beeping.

He raised his wrist to eye level to find out that it was a new message.

‘The Merit Awarding Ceremony will be held at the second military division. The time will be tomorrow at 16:00. Please arrive beforehand.’

“Where is the Second Military Division located?”

Garen casually asked.

Inari who had been messed with by Garen didn’t dare to mess with him anymore and decided to be very honest with him.

“It’s just beside the Empire State Building in the Magical Rose District. Why do you ask? Are the upper levels going to award the merits?”

“Yep. You’re good guessing these kinds of stuff, no?”

Garen glanced at her as he knew that this girl possessed a great amount of intel.

Inari didn’t dare to speak further as she displayed the location of the place clearly on the vehicle’s map. They didn’t speak further after Garen copied it into his Watch Terminal.

They encountered a few red lights along their journey back to the Blackboard Academy.

The sky gradually turned dark while the number of cars increased as the peak hours were approaching. Red cars and buses started appearing more and more and their speed gradually slowed down.

A few motorcyclists in helmets and sports enthusiasts who had passed by Garen’s car would whistle and laugh loudly when they saw Inari in the driver’s seat.

“These kids!” Inari scoffed.

“You grew up around these people,” Garen casually laughed.

Inari didn’t refute as she seemed to be traumatized by Garen’s ambush.

The traffic jam became worse as everyone had just got off from work. Occasionally, honks could be heard from the front and back.

The traffic jam was terrible and the vehicles could only move at a snail’s pace. The VIP lane which was three meters above the ground was empty as usual. Since the cars at the bottom did not have the authority and the capability to rise up to that level, they could only move slowly at the bottom lane.

By the time they arrived Blackboard Academy, the sky had already turned dark.

Garen immediately went to report to the academy, called up his instructor and a few good friends, and took his dinner before going back to his dorm.

As he reached his dorm, he immediately looked around in an attempt to uncover any hidden cameras or bugs in every suspicious spot. Garen even used specialized scanning devices to ensure there was no spying in the area before tidying up the training method that he had obtained.

It was a nameless training method and the information that might have names involved were edited. It was obviously the doing of the Forbidden Core.

However, these were not important. What was the most important was that this training method showed signs of being capped at Level Six.

Although there were only five levels given by the Forbidden Core, it was obvious that there were signs of Level Six at the end of the information. It was something Garen could easily spot from the training method’s information.

“Planning to use this to negotiate with me, eh?” he managed to guess the Forbidden Core’s intention to use such a high-level training method as its offer. In addition to that, he’d even planned to rope him into this troublesome situation with his brother Baylon.

“However, this is fine by me as well.”

Garen was willing to take a step back as the training method that was given by the other party was incredibly powerful. According to Garen’s estimation, it was most likely the legendary Inherited Level.

Only training methods that could reach Level Six were considered an Inherited Level. There was one major distinction between an Inherited Pilot and a normal Pilot, which was that the latter was much stronger than the former. The drastic difference was comparable to that of an elite from the sacred martial art academy and a typical martial artist who lived by the streets. Their strengths were simply not in the same realm.

However, the most important take here was that the weakest Inherited Pilot was a Level Six.

He had temporarily named this training method as the Forbidden Training Method, which came from the very idea that it was a training method that was forbidden.

The main parts involved were the back, legs, and head. With each level up, it would increase the Mech’s Reflex, Endurance, and Recovery by a level each.

Reflex was a skill that temporarily increased the Pilot’s sudden movements by increasing the response of the Pilot’s nerves. This would increase the reaction time of the Pilot and Mech as a whole.

On the other hand, Endurance was similar to what the Red-White Mech had showcased, where it would increase its lifespan by reducing its energy lost via energy channeling. It would increase the lifespan of the reserved energy and hence Endurance. This meant that it could ensure the Mech retained mobility for as long as possible.

As for Recovery, it was the core of the training method. Before this, Garen had never heard of a training method that could heal on its own.

This unique ability was exclusive only to the Inherited Mech. The Inherited Mech could be best described as a Mech that had gained life. As long as it had energy, it would have the ability to slowly regenerate itself.

This training method surprisingly had the Recovery ability from the very beginning, which was to say that it was the most powerful aspect of the training method.

Garen could also feel that the reason why the Forbidden Core had given him this training method was that it would not clash with his Crouched Eagle Talon.

As he thought until here, Garen walked into the bathroom, took off his clothes and stood underneath the shower head, naked. He then turned on the cold water and allowed it to drip from his head to his toes.

As he looked over his current status, he felt relieved.

“The Potential Points have accumulated to this amount?”

With the Staff of Absolute Yin in his possession, it had given him an unlimited source of potential points. As long as he rubbed this staff for an hour each day, it would give Garen two Potential Points. It would then wilt but even so, it had given Garen enough cushion to face any problem.

The Instantaneous Paper Box that he had obtained together with the staff was a one-time-use item that could repel the Energy Field. Garen had been keeping it and had yet to use it, unlike the Staff of Absolute Yin which he had been utilizing on a daily basis.

The gem in the Staff of Absolute Yin was a treasure that could automatically generate potential points as it would store a small number of energy points inside of itself. Similarly, it would release them slowly. Hence Garen had to absorb the stored Potential Points inside frequently in order to not waste his time.

However, the effect of it being slow was that he could only absorb a maximum of two points per day. The rate would be greatly reduced afterward.

Even so, Garen was extremely satisfied with it.

Several days’ worth of accumulated potential points had been used to increase his Willpower by a level to reach Level Four when he’d fought against the Red-White Mech. After spending two potential points, he had sixteen points remaining.

“Sixteen points… I can use all of them at once to increase this training method. The reason why the Crouched Eagle Talon has no Level Six is simply that the limit of this training method is Level Five. Hence, a lot of people would try to earn more money and buy a better training method once they have reached level five and relearn it again with the Crouched Eagle Talon as their base. It is a viable way to earn money and learn a new training method at the same time,” Garen pondered as he started channeling his Willpower slowly into both of his legs according to the forbidden record. This was the first level of this new training method.

It was a good opportunity for him to obtain an Inherited Training Method. If he were to try to obtain an Inherited Training Method through the traditional way in the academy, he would have no choice but to enter a household, pledge a Mech’s oath and carve an absolute command order algorithm onto his own Inherited Mech. Furthermore, he would have to abide by a strict restraint on which training methods he could learn and he would not be allowed to leak any of this out to the public.

It would be equivalent to becoming the sect’s underling or fighter. Their contract would at least require from them decades of services or else, one would never be able to obtain Inherited Level resources. As these items were strictly controlled, they lived in a different realm from typical Pilots.

Garen didn’t want to become a slave to any household. However, he would be capped at Level Five without these Inherited Training Methods and have no hopes of improving further, just like Red Eye Medero.

Medero was not able to obtain the relevant resources and training method because she didn’t join any Inherited powerhouses. Furthermore, her academy teacher, who was one of the Three Heads, didn’t let them obtain any Inherited Level Training Method for some reason. Till this date, excluding the Three Heads, only Black Rain had obtained an Inherited Training Method. The rest didn’t have the opportunity and even among the bunch of instructors, ninety percent of them were capped at Level Five. They had been training themselves at this level for so long and yet there were no improvements.

There was only one special instructor who had managed to breakthrough into the Inherited Level on his own. He then inherited this to the Academy but was not able to improve further than Level Six.

Chapter 860: Line of Sight 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This was how things were at the moment. It was the same throughout the Blackboard Region, Polar Region, Maria Region, and other surrounding regions where everything related to Inherited Level was under strict control; even Red-eyed Medero could not obtain a Level Six Training Method to reach Level Six despite having served the academy for such a long period of time. Moreover, for huge influential households like the one Celine was from, or elites, there would only be a single digit number of pilots with Inherited Level training methods and Mechs. If Celine herself did not reach the top three in her entire clan, she could only attain Level Five at most.

If that was the case for such rich and powerful individuals, what of Garen himself?

Regarding Inheritance, the teacher would need to make a careful selection and scrutinize each generation. The level of aptitude and will required were extremely high and not everyone could easily meet these conditions.

After learning of these circumstances, Garen immediately set his sights on the Forbidden Core. This could be the only opportunity for him to acquire an Inherited Level training method.

Standing underneath the cold shower, Garen started to recall the Level One content of the Forbidden Training Method.

“…Inherited training methods vastly differ from ordinary training methods whereby the human fuses with the Mech to eventually replace oneself with foreign objects, while the original self would huddle up in the inner core of the Mech, achieving the state of a body within a body. At that level, the original self would exist as the core of life, reaching the theoretical limit of a human lifespan. Every kind of exhaustion and damage will be borne by the Mech’s body. At the same time, foreign objects can be used to recuperate and evolve the Mech’s body whereby their essence would be extracted to feed the original core, prolonging and evolving the levels of limitations of human life. This is one of the basic concepts in the early journey of Inheriting.”

Garen had read this numerous times but was still deeply shaken as he read it again. This kind of means equaled to constructing a truly mighty outer shell with life in it.

“According to the Yin-yang theory and the ways of the Secret Techniques, the source of life, also known as the innate vitality of the body, are fixed since birth, not just in human beings but in all kinds of living things. It cannot regenerate and can only be exhausted. Growth and development will expend innate vitality, while injuries and illness will result in the depletion of vitality for recovery; facing enormous stimulation will also exhaust vitality.”

“Life is like a brand new candle; birth is when the candle is lit while death is when it burns out. This is the essence of life,” Garen contemplated on the matter.

“No wonder some people view life as a journey. The candle is given by parents, by this universe. The parents, coming together under an appropriate circumstance influenced by the universe, will produce offspring and give us flesh. Our flesh results in thinking, which will then evolve into a will that influences the body. There are pros and cons to this type of influence. When the self is not influenced by distracting thoughts and desires will all miscellaneous cravings be altered and meld together for the purpose of feeding back into the innate vitality. Only then can one walk upon the path of evolution. Using the whole of self as a motivation for evolving…”

Combining the universal view and life view of the ways of the Secret Techniques, Ancient Endor, and other philosophies during Earth times, Garen formed his own kind of philosophical theory.

The function of philosophy was to point out a direction and to see the future clearly.

With the merging of the Inherited Mech theory from this world, Garen was able to visualize a whole new path before him.

“Right… If growing causes the exhaustion of innate vitality, why not construct a brand new body since the original body solely acts as a bearing tool? By cutting down exhaustion, growth and development, aging, and illness, it would certainly be possible to achieve a non-deteriorating life pattern under the protection of the mech’s body. In this case, it would most likely prolong one’s lifespan,” Garen nodded and continued reading attentively.

“Perhaps there are still many other schools of thought. Even so, the fundamental direction is as such: living things themselves have adaptability. This kind of adaptability is known as evolving or devolving. Changes occur in response to the environment and the genes of generations upon generations are modified to better integrate into the life pattern of the natural universe. This is inherent. It is an inherent trait for us to blend in with the natural universe as one. Every person of remarkable talent can learn to reflect on the law of nature and universe to quicken this process. Our learning ability can speed up our inherent adaptability, although this kind of adapting will cause the loss of life.”

“Why do living things have such adaptability?”

This question appeared next.

Garen was able to grasp some ideas. He had known about all these things previously but they were not put together like this and had never elicited such a strong emotion in him.

“Because the instinct to seek advantages and avoid disadvantages is incongruous with nature, there will always be friction and resistance.”

“For example, the tree that grows out of the forested area will easily be blown down by the wind, or the animal that eats only a single type of plant will die off when that particular type of plant goes extinct due to natural causes.”

“In human society, if we do not integrate into it, we will be viewed as strange species, be discriminated against and face prejudices. The friction with the outside world will also increase.”

“If the tender skin does not grow thick when it is constantly being blown at by the wind, chilblains will start to develop. If the strength of resisting heat does not increase when constantly being in a high-temperature environment, one will be scalded every day. There are many more similar principles…”

The notes of the training method kept going deeper, and Garen continuously deepened the engraving of the imprint in both of his legs in accordance with the content of the Forbidden Training Method.

“In order to reduce all kinds of friction with the outer world and to prevent the energy of life from depleting, previous wise men have racked their brains and figured out a whole new path, which is the Mech.”

“One will still be affected and have to suffer from the universe and light radiation as long as the person exists in this universe. Although many of the beams are beneficial at the same time, many forerunners have exchanged precious experience and knowledge on how to sift out the beneficial parts and reject the depleting parts. The Mech, as the mechanism of choice, emerged as the times demanded. Combat is actually just one of its additional functions.”

Garen nodded in understanding. This kind of pathway’s concept was way different from the direction of Secret Techniques. The Secret Technique’s concept was to exhaust all of the innate vitality in the shortest amount of time to upgrade oneself. When one reached the level of unending tapping, one would be able to transmigrate and revive even though the body had rotted. What differed was the switching of a bodily shell.

Both differed in their essence.

The Secret Technique was about enhancing the enduring essence of the body and integrating the imprint of the will of life into it.

On the other hand, the Mech used a foreign object as a protective shell to protect the body so that it could endure and prolong its development.

Put simply, that was what it meant.

The focus of Secret Techniques was on afterlife while for the Mech, it was the present life. They were somewhat similar to the philosophies of Buddhism and Taoism on Earth.

Garen’s mind became clearer as he comprehended this. By corroborating the strength systems of countless worlds with one another, he began to see clearly the path he was to take.

“By utilizing the strength of technology, the mech acts as an outer body to strengthen the original body and feed back into the body, thus achieving an indestructible state and maximum lifespan. Building on this foundation, the toxins and impurities of the body will be filtered out repeatedly while unused functions would be eliminated, leaving purely the source of life and reverting the human body to its primitive state. The substitution of the Mech as the body will turn into a brand new life…”

As Garen looked over the text repeatedly, the current situation he was in dawned on him. He wondered whether the Forbidden Core had come from such beginnings and if it possible that the Forbidden Core was, in fact, the pilot of the Forbidden Mech itself. After all, it was highly unlikely that a body would contain a second consciousness. Yet, the universe was so big that nothing was to be surprised at, even in such circumstances.

Garen put aside his suspicion.

Recalling the situation of Blackboard Academy, he suddenly realized that no one in the whole of the academy had ever made it known that they were Level Six, not even the instructors and professors. Even for those instructors who had made it to Level Six and left a legacy behind, they only stayed in the inner courtyard all year round and no one had ever seen their faces before. As for the big three professors, nobody had an idea of what their statuses were, as not a single person had ever seen them in combat nor had their Mechs ever appeared before anyone.

At this moment, Garen felt his legs getting slightly numb as the engraving of the imprint was half done. The basic level was completed gradually without much complication under his abundant Willpower.

He continued to read on.

“Exploiting all favorable resources by non-stop absorption of foreign objects to strengthen oneself. The pathway of the Mech is essentially the path of exploiting.”

“When at Level Six, there will be a sense of resonance between the human and the Mech to attain the state of fusing into a single entity, while the Mech will also gain the ability of self-healing.”

“Upon reaching Level Seven, the Mech will tentatively begin to fuse with the human body and parts of the body organs will start to degenerate. Some pilots will remain in the Mech so that their nerves will connect with the Mech naturally, whereas in some cases, the Mech will become an enclosed armor that covers the surface area of the human being’s skin. Not only that, it can condense and disintegrate to fuse into the pilot’s heart. The pilot may look like an ordinary person, but in reality, his combatting capability is equal to that of a large-size mech.”

“At Level Eight…” it stopped abruptly just like that.

Garen knew that this was the doing of the Forbidden Core. Nevertheless, through the philosophy views that he had read, he now roughly knew the direction he was heading towards.

It was nothing more than the fusion of the body to become the source of life by constructing a new body using foreign objects. This was a step-by-step interchange process just like how a silkworm secreted silk to build its cocoon before emerging as a moth. This conformed to the natural ways of evolution.

“Each unique Inherited Mech demands various specific materials to construct the Mech’s outer body. However, they all require a common material, which is Worma Crystal. Originating from the Well of Black Abyss, the Worma Crystal is a type of powerful ore which contains a high purity level of life energy. It does not just replenish the source of life but also is a scarce material that is essential for evolving to a higher level. That is the reason why the Mother Planet Federation and the Galatic Alliance are at war with the Finite people. Generations of powerful Inherited Level pilots engaged in a life-and-death battle with the Finite people’s Inherited pilots in order to take possession of large tracts in the Well of Black Abyss. Amidst the great amount of slaughtering and death, the life energy that dissipated was absorbed by the Well of Black Abyss to produce new Worma Crystal. This is the truth of the warfare. Everyone fought tacitly with the purpose of killing the opponent to obtain more resources for growth and evolvement. Pillaging, plundering and pillaging again! This is the essence of Mech. At the heart of it, it is to make use of the Well of Black Abyss to produce other sources of life, evolving oneself and head towards the way of eternity…”

Whir!!

A sound rang in Garen’s mind. Forbidden Training Method Level One had finally been attained. Two white ray prints appeared faintly on both of his knees before disappearing quickly.

Chapter 861: Military Rank 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Clint carefully scraped the green moss off the sewer pipelines into the small dish in his hands. Immediately, there was a smile on his face.

“There will be more ingredients for tonight’s dinner.”

In the dark and gloomy sewers, there was an underground river that flowed rapidly on the right side. At times, there was some white and yellow floating debris drifting by. Most of it was a layer of thick oily sludge that stank from afar.

However, Clint had gotten used to it. He looked around for more spots with such moss and scraped off the only bit of moss in the sewer into his small dish.

During these few days in the sewers, he had encountered multiple instances of underground pursuit. They were not by the pilots above ground but by mutated rodents that lived in the depths of the sewer and would appear in big groups every few hours. These rodents with glowing red eyes could gnaw through any objects. In order to conserve the mech’s energy, Clint did not dare to misuse the mech. It was a rigged-up mech in the first place. The power furnace was an old model and lots of its energy had been used up. A majority of what was left of the energy had been used for Red Moon’s recovery while the final bit was reserved for the opening of the hatch door.

Thinking of this, Clint sighed. Putting away the moss, he touched his stomach and it still felt a bit sore to the touch. He looked at the time, turned around and headed back to his hiding spot.

“Ten more minutes until the group of rodents appear. There should be enough time.”

After walking for a distance, he quickly wormed his way into a narrow crevice that was located in a small space between the pipelines. There was an indistinctive white light shining from the inside and a wet glaze was seen when the light reflected off the floor of the sewer.

Clint walked in and saw Baylon roasting a dried rodent. Both of them had been living like this for the past two days. They were only left with eating this as they had finished their dried food supplies. Luckily, Baylon’s Bright King Training Method could eradicate most diseases and infections; otherwise, eating this unhygienic stuff would cost both of them their lives.

The light came from the electric wire of a Mech. It was not very bright since it had to be used conservatively.

“How is it? How’s the situation outside?” Baylon looked over with wide eyes. She had now completely transfigured into a female, or to put in another way, she was a female all the while. It’s just that the training method helped shed off the epidermis layer.

Sitting on her knees by the fire, Baylon’s face was red and she looked rather worn out.

“Fortunately, no one seems to be coming after us,” Clint nodded and smiled helplessly. “Maybe this is part of the radiation area, so they don’t dare to chase us down? Their bodies could acquire the radiation disease after staying in a radiated area for a long period of time.”

“Yea…” Baylon nodded and lifted her arms. Grey spots faintly appeared on them as if the skin had shriveled.

“I heard that it is hard to treat radiation disease…” her eyes dimmed, “once a person has the radiation disease, there’s no way to live in the regions anymore…”

“Don’t worry, there has to be a way when Lord Red Moon wakes up!” Clint was always full of hope and confidence even though he himself did not know where this confidence came from, “If I myself have no hope, then there really isn’t any hope at all.”

“Yea… Lord Red Moon is very powerful. There sure is a way to solve it,” Baylon relaxed slightly. They had constantly viewed Red Moon as all-capable. Even though he had a foul mouth, he could always think of a way to resolve any matter. As compared to that, radiation disease did not seemed like a big issue.

Both of them quietly worked together to clean the moss with filtered water. They then boiled some soup with the dried rodent meat and moss. This food had been their main sustenance.

After boiling for some time, a booming roar thundered from the outside of the passageway. It sounded as if it came from afar.

The look on Clint and Baylon’s faces changed. They swiftly got up and blocked the only access to this small and narrow space using a piece of the shattered alloy plate from the mech. The alloy plate fitted in nicely to conceal this place. Clint braced both of his hands against the alloy plate in fear of it being knocked down.

On the other side, Baylon quickly extinguished the fire, leaving only a little material for starting a fire and covered the soup before spreading out clothing on top of it.

Not long after, there were several thudding sounds outside of the alloy plate, as if there were numerous little things ramming against the alloy plate non-stop. Clint had started to sweat and was exerting great effort. With his Level One Nine Mega Cannon Training Method, his strength was several times that of ordinary people, and yet, he still felt remarkably strained.

One could only imagine how great the impact coming from the outside was.

After an unknown amount of time had passed, the ramming sounds began to weaken. The blue veins on his forehead started to subside and he had sweated profusely.

He let out a long sigh and slid down onto the floor after the last ramming sound had died down.

“Hoo… hoo… hoo…” the sound of huffing and puffing as intense as a racehorse could be heard.

“Come, drink some water…” as there were no cups, Baylon filled the indented part of a small piece of alloy plate with water and brought it over.

“Thanks,” Clint took it and gulped it down.

“Did you hear something?” Baylon suddenly asked warily.

“What? Heard what?” Clint was stunned.

“I… I think I heard the sound of someone shouting on the outside…” Baylon replied uncertainly.

“There’s someone?!” Clint stood up, his eyes filled with worry.

Both of them lightened their breathing and Clint could hear it too.

“Carl!” “Carl, where are you?”

“Captain Carl!” “Big brother Carl~”

It did not sound like a person but a group of people with male and female voices looking for someone named Carl.

Clint carefully removed the alloy plate and poked his head out. He saw that at the end of the passageway where the rodent group had wreaked havoc, there was a group of people with fire torches approaching. What was most surprising was that these people were not wearing any radiation suits in this radiation area.

There were males and females, and all of them were more or less wearing nail plates made of metal on their bodies; some on their shoulders; some as helmets; but mostly on their arms, chests, and abdomens.

In the group of more than a dozen people, many of them wore torn clothing and some of their faces had radiation scars that could not be covered up.

“So many Radiation people…” Clint instantly knew that these were ordinary people with radiation disease, just like them.

He suddenly did not know what to do. In the absence of Red Moon, their safety was in their own hands. They would be lucky if this was a group of kind-hearted people. But if they had any bad intention… then he and Lon would…

“Who’s there?!” the leader of the group, a woman in a red shirt, shouted suddenly and looked over in his direction.

Clint jumped in shock and fell onto the floor, making a louder sound.

This group of people hurried over in an instant. Baylon quickly helped Clint to get up. Both of them huddled together and gazed at the access point. Soon, a husky, muscular man cautiously made his way inside. He was somewhat stunned when he saw Clint and Baylon.

“Chief, it is two kids!” he shouted loudly.

“Are you joking? How can little kids survive in this place?” the redshirt woman walked in and was surprised as well when she saw Clint and Baylon. “You guys… This is the region’s sewer’s dark maze, with radiation poison and mutated rodents everywhere. You guys actually…”

“Hel… Hello…” Clint forced a smile and greeted them.

**************

Blackboard Region Police Agency Mobile Hall

“This is the report,” Garen submitted the paper report in his hands. He was standing at the center of the large hall with the deputy director of the Agency seated in front of him. He was a bald, middle-aged man who had a small patch of yellow hair at his chin, making him look stern.

“You are part of the military and the academy. Being able to strike dead the terrorist in a kamikaze style with Level Three capability even though he was heavily injured, this combat record still exceeds the capability spectrum of an ordinary student,” the baldy browsed through the document and nodded his head while commenting.

“As is customary, the police bureau will hand over all your state-of-the-battle records and someone from the military will award you for your merit. Please wait patiently.”

“I understand,” Garen nodded his head.

“However, you must be mentally prepared,” the baldy looked up at Garen. “The mission this time had exceeded the scope of your assignment. No one would have thought that you could defeat a terrorist and it was only hoped that could stall the opponent, but…” he paused. “Well, I won’t say any more unnecessary things. The elite team that was in charge of this matter are rather disgruntled at you, so be prepared for the handing over of the mission as you might encounter some provocation.”

“Is it from the elite students?” Garen asked rhetorically.

“It’s good that you know,” the baldy seemed to admire Garen as he smiled and nodded. “Alright, you may go now. The military will send out the notice of military credit very shortly, so don’t be anxious.”

“Understood.”

Garen nodded. He gave a salute with the back of his right hand pressing against his left cheek and bent over slightly to give a bow.

He then stood to attention, turned around and left.

Garen let out a breath as he exited the hall of the Agency. The deputy director of the Agency was definitely a powerhouse with hidden depths. He was most certainly be a Level Five pilot, though not one who practiced any ordinary training method; the wave motion of the willpower energy field emitted by him gave off an intangible pressure.

This kind of feeling was many times stronger than when that of the Red-White Mech.

“He could fight against two at least,” Garen estimated in a low voice. Two of the Red-White Mechs might not even stand a chance against the Deputy Director. As expected, powerful and respected people in Blackboard Region had made it to a point of reality.

Capability determined everything. With capability, you could occupy important positions, while without enough capability, it would be impossible to be raised to a top position regardless of how knowledgeable you were. This was also the result of a single mech soldier’s capability of turning the tide.

Leaving the police agency, the guard stations were right next to it. A few of the guards who happened to pass by saw Garen from afar and greeted him warmly. These were the police members of Garen’s patrol area.

After exchanging some general pleasantries with them, Garen learned of the current situation and had some ideas in mind. He then immediately took a cab home.

His parents and sister were all at home. Due to the brother’s disappearance, everyone was feeling down and waiting for Garen’s latest news.

As he entered the room, his father who had been sitting on the couch instantly stood up.

“How’s it? Nono? Lon’s situation…”

Chapter 862: Military Rank 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen shook his head a little. In reality, he had only pretended to inquire around about his brother’s situation. He did not dare to tell the truth but buried it deep inside his heart. After all, this involved the Forbidden Core, and his family would not be able to bear the consequences at the present moment. Revealing the truth would only bring disaster.

The parents’ hearts immediately sank as they saw Garen shaking his head. Amy, the mother, lowered her head and began to cry.

Only the sister, the youngest one, had an appearance of nonchalance. She was still chewing on bubblegum, eyes revealing indifference.

“Look at all of you. Isn’t he just temporarily missing? If it can’t be done in the light, we could do it under the table. There’s got to be a way for sure. Cry cry cry. Can you get back the person just by crying?!”

Ker the sister commented impatiently. She was now extremely different from before. Wearing a white short skirt with a crop top, she had applied bright red lipstick, thick foundation makeup, and dark eyeshadow. She had on a pair of huge silver earrings and was sitting on the chair with one leg crossed high, unbothered about whether her underwear would be exposed.

“How could you speak like this?!” Rondo the father stood up and reprimanded.

“So what?! Want to beat me? Just go ahead! Beat here!” the sister stood up, pointed to her own face and responded loudly, “You didn’t manage to beat me to death the last time, why not you just do it this time! I’m sick of living anyway! There’s no point staying in this house at all!”

“Ker…” Amy the mother opened her mouth to speak but was cut short by the sister right away.

“In any case, I am no good at all besides bringing shame to you all. Just come. Beat me to death. I have no intention of living anyway,” Ker’s voice grew louder. When she saw that her father could not give any response, a pleasant expression instantly appeared on her face.

“That’s enough!”

Garen bellowed.

It was entirely silent in the house. The sister Ker gnashed her teeth tightly and dared not speak anymore. Ever since young, she and Baylon had always been fearful of Nono. Despite the fact that she had ‘seen the world’ outside, she was still afraid of him.

The father slumped into a chair, lit another cigarette and sucked on it fiercely with his head down.

For a moment, there was only the sound of the mother sobbing.

Garen’s face looked black as he sat down and looked at Ker.

“From now on, you will go out and mingle lesser. Do you hear me?!”

Ker pursed her lips tightly and turned her head away.

“Look at the way you dressed! What do you look like when you’re on the street?” Garen softened his tone, “Regarding Lon’s situation, I have a little progress. I know that he is still safe even though I couldn’t find him yet. Pa, ma, you don’t need to worry.”

“Sigh…” Rondo, the father, exhaled deeply. “It’s all my fault. I shouldn’t have agreed to let him work…”

“This is nobody’s fault. None of us could have expected that this was going to happen,” Garen replied in a low voice. “Alright then. Everyone continue to go to work as usual. I will handle this matter.”

“Is Lon really alright?” the mother, Amy wiped away the streak of tears on her face.

“Really,” Garen knew that Red Moon, this Core, had lots of tricks up its sleeve. There should not be any jeopardy while under his care.

“Nono, you must find your brother and bring him back. You must!!” the mother cried, distressed, as her eyes filled with tears once more.

“I will…” Garen nodded.

Garen left his house with a heavy heart.

He truly did not know if he could find Baylon. Even if he could, there was still no way of telling whether the family would accept her current self.

He was not discriminating against transsexuals. It was just that in such a life, one would have to face countless discriminations and setbacks. Moreover, there were too many people who were over-subjective and who looked at others with preconceived ideas.

Since he had now become this person, Nonosiva, and had received the favor of his parents, it was only natural for him to be responsible for taking good care of his family.

Leaving his home, Garen made a trip to the patrol station. The only life that was lost had been replaced with a naïve looking, short red-haired girl who seemed to have a strong sense of justice.

Alexander, who had been allocated a new Mech, was commended and officially became a Second Lieutenant in the military. This guy was boasting to the other teams about the newly added black stripe on his shoulder. His face was beaming with pride.

Not only him, all the members under Garen’s leadership had been commended as well and were given a Sergeant’s rank. As they were Level One pilots, this ranking among the Mech’s troops would cause them to be one level higher than the other teams. This made everyone super excited.

“Assemble!!!” Garen stood with his hands behind his back. As he was already in a bad mood, seeing this bunch of happy people made him felt sullen.

When he was in a bad mood, he would want others to feel the same as him.

After a loud roar, the dozen of team members in the field trembled and hurriedly ran to form a line before him.

Shoo!

Couldn’t say that it was a tidy salutation.

“Team leader!” their voices sounded in unison though.

Before Garen had any say, Alexander could not hold back and decided to speak.

“Team leader, the award notice of your military credit has arrived!”

“Mine came too?” Garen had been ready to take it out on the team members until he was distracted by what he heard.

“It’s this!”

Alexander carefully took out a tiny silver circular board from his pocket and threw it on the ground.

The circular board immediately released silver halos, forming a one-meter-wide silver light board. A middle-aged female military officer dressed in black military suit gradually appeared on it. The two stars on her shoulder meant that she was actually a Colonel level military officer.

“Holographic projection?” Garen was stunned and immediately gave a salute next.

The other party rapidly returned the salute too.

“Second Lieutenant Nonosiva Lin, due to your outstanding gallantry during the terrorist attack, you are commended for a first class-merit award. The military staff have decided to confer on you the Captain rank. You can search the military web to be aware of all your privileges.”

Garen knew that his provisional rank initially was Second Lieutenant due to the benefits of joining the military with willpower Level Three. Currently, he had been promoted by two levels instantly to the level of Captain just because of a one-time military procurement.

It was said that at the Captain level, one would acquire lots of benefits. As for the higher field ranks, that would be the stratum where its members held true power in their hands. Every field rank in Blackboard Zone had to have a minimum of Level Four capability and either brilliant combat records or a powerful curriculum vitae. These were the backbones that held the power of the military and their numbers did not even reach one thousand. Since the numbers were so few, the ranks would not be granted easily.

“Besides that, the patrol unit that you are leading at the moment will be your permanent team from now on, so there would not be any more changes to the members. You have your own appointing rights. All that’s needed is just a report to the staff department later on.”

After the female Colonel made her brief announcement, she gave another salute before the image vanished.

Garen returned the salute and his face showed that he was deep in thought.

“A small permanent unit and my own appointing rights.… Doesn’t this mean that I can build my own company? Looks like my performance has attracted the attention of the higher-ups. Even so, are they thinking of training me or are they simply observing me?”

Ever since he had leveled up that nameless Forbidden Training Method, he’d felt that his body and mind were constantly being restored. After using Secret Techniques to examine, he was surprised to discover that all the hidden injuries sustained from his previous practices were being repaired through the vibration of the Willpower from this training method. It followed the most natural and harmonious way of blending into the body to become as one.

It was like bringing along medical equipment so that even the minor wounds could be treated anytime.

He did not rush to advance to Level Two because if he were to practice and advance with his own efforts, there would not be any indications. However, using potential points to advance would also be a waste because the training method level this time was a little higher, which had surpassed Crouched Eagle Talon and reached the level of high-level Secret Techniques or even a higher standard. If a mid-level Secret Technique needed two points to upgrade one level, then high-level Secret Techniques would need five points. As for this training method, it actually needed as many as ten points to advance one level.

Garen did not have much left in stock. Every day he could only accumulate two points, which was why he planned to focus on advancing the Living Secret Technique; in order for the Living Secret Technique to spur on the advancement of Crouched Eagle Talon and this unknown training method. The overall efficiency would be higher this way because it would be advancing all three at the same time.

The Living Secret Technique had begun to advance slowly under the plentiful supply of White Peacock Stone. Garen’s Hellfrost Peacock Technique leaped over the highest level of the foundation stage, which was Level Five. The level after this would be leaving the foundation stage and formally entering the practice phase. The Hellfrost Peacock Technique would also start to manifest its power as time went by.

Then again, when Garen had persisted in following the Living Secret Technique to train his body, he did not notice any trends. The effects of White Peacock Stone had weakened immensely and so it was apparent that it was only beneficial for the laying of the foundation, but other times…

Now he finally acquired potential points. With the Staff of Absolute Yin in his possession, Garen could accumulate two potential points every day. The initial number of points at twelve had currently risen to twenty in just a few days’ time.

“Alright, dismiss,” Garen’s mood had been turned around because of the promotion of rank. He waved his hands to dismiss everyone.

Only then did the team members disperse and vanish quickly, as if they were amnestied. From afar, you could still hear a group of people with bent arms around one another’s shoulders suggesting to drink and eat at a restaurant.

Garen could not be bothered about these scoundrels. Except for Alexander, the rest were all useless. You couldn’t even see their shadows during crucial times. Among those he’d summoned, only Alexander had taken the initiative to come without the fear of danger and was almost annihilated by the terrorist.

“The reason I could win this time depended on Cold Chaos of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique. This thing is simply a bug. It can seep into the Mech and affect the body of the pilot. For those who do not have a strong will, it can also act as a big killer weapon by muddling up their minds,” Garen reckoned in his heart. If it were not for Cold Chaos, he probably would have gotten seriously injured and might not have been able to make the opponent stayed put. Victory would definitely not have come this easily.

“Previously, there was a lack of White Peacock Stones to advance the Living Secret Technique. Now that this condition has been met, I should be able to utilize the potential points to advance and bypass the accumulation of time, shouldn’t I?”

He surmised.

His gaze fell upon his Attribute pane and he focused on the Living Secret Technique Hellfrost Peacock Technique.

‘Secret Technique — Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Living Secret Technique, Level Six, Completion rate of Level Six at 1%.

‘Natural Ability Obtained — Devour Level One (Devours innumerable living things to restore the body).’

‘Natural Ability Obtained — Distorted Seed Level Two (Creating chaos is the Hellfrost Peacock’s favorite pastime)’

‘Natural Ability Obtained — Cold Chaos Level Three (Causes fluctuations in time and space and releases cold air naturally within an area of 20 meters to create a chaotic low-temperature area with the lowest point at zero degrees. Simultaneously, there is a small chance of muddling up the enemies’ mind, causing them to attack randomly)’

‘(Five foundation levels and three levels in derivative level, totaling up to eight levels in the whole technique) Achieving each level will cleanse the blood of the body to gradually acclimate towards the Hellfrost Peacock’s constitution and eventually reach its highest form with its limit at Army Level.’

There were still twenty potential points left.

Garen attempted to add the potential points into the Living Secret Technique. Regretfully, it did not work. The Living Secret Technique was still the same as before. It would not accept the advancement brought forth by the potential points.

He realized, however, that the potential points seemed to be able to advance the three additional natural abilities from the Peacock Technique.

The three abilities advanced according to the standard of high-level Secret Techniques. Each level would require five potential points.

Garen hesitated; he could use the potential points to advance these natural abilities or to use them on new training methods. He was unsure of which move to make.

The effect of the natural ability Cold Chaos was very strong and it could have a sudden effect of clearing the site. Its training method equated to inner force, which was the source of the formidable force in all moves. It would be very useful when facing a powerhouse one-on-one. However, the subsequent training method was in the hands of the Forbidden Core.

Chapter 863: A Sudden Turn of Events 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He hesitated for a moment and decided to invest in the training method since it was the root of all things. In this world, the difference in the level of training method had an effect on status, power, etc.

Even though his Level Four Crouched Eagle Talon seemed to be at a high level, it was actually only parallel to the Level Two of other people’s top training methods. The only edge he had was a greater amount of Willpower and nothing else.

His sight fell on the Attribution pane. After gazing for a number of seconds, the Unnamed Training Method ability blurred for a moment. When it became clear again, it had leaped to another level.

It jumped from Level One to Level Two.

‘Forbidden Training Method: Level Two achieved (a total of five levels, Incomplete), Reflexes advanced to Level Two, Endurance advanced to Level Two, Self-repairing advanced to Level Two. Involving the back, both legs, and the head.’

Garen felt the changes of the attributions after they had advanced, not just from those that were indicated, but also from those that were not marked out. A whole new Willpower had condensed in his inner body core within the Willpower of Crouched Eagle Talon. It was slowly moving in a circular flow by itself, like the nature of rivers.

“I don’t think Level Four of Crouched Eagle Talon can be concealed as it would be noticed by many of the practitioners who are above Level Four. But with its Willpower enveloping the forbidden Willpower, the latter should be able to remain hidden,” Garen knew in his heart that because there was no conflict in this nature of enveloping, the force field emanated by the Forbidden Training Method willpower could be kept hidden. People would think that he had the outer layer Crouched Eagle Talon willpower and neglect the other willpower on the inside.

Five potential points had vanished due to the advancement.

Garen looked at the remaining fifteen points and decided to use them all up in a go. He pored over the Forbidden Training Method.

Hiss…

The icon of the training method instantly blurred. This time, it did not clear up even after a number of seconds but remained hazy.

After half a minute, the icon of the training method finally became visible once more. It was not the former pitch-black patch anymore but a fluttering four-winged bird. Similar to an eagle, the four-winged bird had sharply curved claws and looked as if it was diving to catch something.

Garen gazed at the progress.

‘Forbidden Training Method: Level Five (a total of five levels, Incomplete), Reflexes, Endurance, and Self-repairing Level Five, resulting in special derivative strength: Heart of Endurance – greatly improving the effects of Self-repairing, level of amplification reached level one. The strength of Self-Repairing is now at Level Six standard.’

“Heart of Endurance?” Garen frowned a little as he thought of a vague possibility. “Does this mean that for better quality training methods, arriving at a certain level would yield this kind of derivative strength?”

Due to the lack of information in this area, he could not compare it with other higher level training methods. Nonetheless, the power shown by the training method given by the Forbidden Core had surpassed his expectations.

If this training method focused on one of these attributions: explosiveness, speed, or strength, reaching this level would be terrific because the force produced together by three Level Fives was unimaginable.

After standing on the training grounds for some time, Garen let out a small breath. Around him, there was a sudden burst of faint air-waves. If someone were to inspect closely, they would realize that those were not air-waves but a pure energy field that was spreading out towards the surroundings. This could only happen when the Willpower had reached a certain level of purity. It was also the hallmark of a Level Five pilot. Someone at Level Four might be able to master the energy field and spread it out all over their body surface to fight against the enemy. However, it was a different case for Level Five. The most formidable strength of the Level Five pilot was that the energy field could be dispersed through the mech. Every type of Willpower Energy Field had its own unique special effect, just like Internal Force, where both had exclusive corrosive power. And so, when used by itself, even the gentlest Willpower would have an effect on the enemy although its properties would be different.

Garen paid close attention to the feeling of the flow, immense amount and purity of Level Five Willpower.

After releasing it for a while, he swiftly collected it back and enveloped it using Level Four Crouched Eagle Talon’s Willpower.

To advance from Level Four to Level Five, the common pilots would usually need a couple of years to break through to another level because this involved the matter of will. Garen, however, did not need to worry about it because from the Soul Will point of view, Garen was still stronger than the common pilot in this area even though he was not of the same system.

“Looks like I’ll need some time to adjust to this new strength,” Garen opened his palms. There were still strands of willpower force field that he could not contain emanating from the edge of his palms. This was due to the unconscious dissipation of the sudden spike in Willpower.

It was just like when a person gained Herculean strength all of a sudden; when he lifted a cup with the same amount of strength he usually used, the cup would instantly be shattered.

As he quietly practiced the control of Willpower, Garen was able to hold in the force field of the new Willpower. People generally would need years of work to arrive at this step but Garen did not have this issue.

A few days passed by in a flash.

Garen completed his patrolling assignment. Since he was conferred with the rank of Captain, it came with many privileges such as being presented with special commodity facilities not just for him but his family as well. Formerly, he and his family were unqualified to purchase these things but now they could do so. There were products such as gene enhancement fluid, all kinds of nutritional fluid and mixed essence to prolong lifespan and boost the body’s constitution, a platform for repairing mechanisms and… he could purchase his own Mech!

Garen’s life became a routine of going to the academy for a while every day and spending most of his time at the provisional encampment to train the members. He would send some of the members off one after another because they were still students and would not stay here permanently. There were also some who came from lower-level academies and poor family backgrounds, and they would persist in signing the agreement of joining the military service formally; thus, becoming a member of the unit.

Garen also officially gave a name to the unit. Since the mechs were generally configured as a double-edge type of humanoid Mech, he succinctly named the unit as Double-Edge Unit.

The remaining five members were not a patrol unit tasked with patrolling anymore but had become a standalone special unit that could accept independent assignments. This was also the main type of teams in the Blackboard Region.

Many of the scholars would use this way to accumulate military credits after they had graduated. The military would give out assignments and various parties would go and complete them. Later on, members who had performed outstandingly and served for a period of time would be chosen to join the military’s Black-Clothed General Army.

Everything went smoothly for more than half a month without any problems.

Besides training the five members every day, Garen would practice familiarizing himself with his newly obtained training method Willpower and take note of the whereabouts of the Forbidden Core through various channels.

The everyday training caused the five members to complain about the hardship. Alexander, who liked to shirk work, contrasted sharply with that short red-haired girl who would complete the training tasks more than necessary. The other three who did not have a good family background and came from the lower quality academies in Blackboard Region were randomly assigned to be here. Even though every day they would cry out in misery, they would still complete the training tasks without slacking.

Garen was satisfied with this development. Since the higher-ups had bestowed upon him the authority over this unit, he wanted to build this team and made it into his own force. He followed Celine’s method by halving their training so that they could really develop their battle skills and improve their combatting achievements. Though they were unable to reach the level of elite in this short amount of time, at any rate, there would not be any incident like the last time where only Alexander responded and acted rashly.

At least in terms of boldness and discipline, these five were not rookies anymore.

More than half a month had passed in the blink of an eye.

The Eagle’s Nest martial arts computer simulation that Garen had applied to use had finally been approved and a timetable had been drawn up. In order to avoid clashing with other people’s time, he was scheduled for the weekend, on Sunday afternoon.

Garen had always wanted to have a look at the Eagle’s Nest Simulation Computer. After receiving the notice, he hastily arranged everything on hand and hurriedly drove over to the Eagle’s Nest headquarter on Sunday afternoon. He had not been there for a long time.

**********

The Eagle’s Nest appeared to be as deserted and quiet as it was before. It looked like a silver bird nest from afar. There were not many people going in and coming out of it since it was a weekend. Most scholars either had some business to attend to or they would go home to spend time with their families and rest. Some would be working, so there were not many people who would come here to train.

After all, there were designated places for training. The only thing to be done here was to refine one’s martial arts through simulation, interact with other Eagle’s Nest members and receive external assignments.

For the first two items, there would only be a greater number of people at specific times. Regarding the external assignments, there would not be suitable ones available all the time.

Garen got down from the school bus and hurried towards the Eagle’s Nest.

The gatekeeper on duty was a retired old man who smiled and greeted him.

“I haven’t seen you for a long time, Nono,” the old man was sipping a rich wine, sitting with his legs crossed. He knew all the famous scholars in Eagle’s Nest. This old man had once been a member of Eagle’s Nest when he was young, but he’d gotten into an accident and broke his leg. He’d become depressed even though he had a prosthetic leg. That was one of the reasons that many Eagle’s Nest scholars, who prided themselves as elites, looked down upon him.

But Garen did not discriminate him in any way.

“It’s been long, Abel,” he smiled and waved. He had always felt that this old man did not appear as simple he seemed to be. No one had ever seen him drive a Mech in the past few decades he had been a gatekeeper.

As he entered Eagle’s Nest with big strides, the inside was rather empty. Only a dozen or so people were leisurely training with one another in the training hall located at the center. The simulation combat rooms were also vacant with hardly anyone inside.

Only the entrance to the Assignment Room had some people. There would always be someone waiting there so that they could snatch away any high-value assignments that became available.

The top battling teams in Eagle’s Nest would usually send someone to keep watch here. The model of these teams was akin to the model of Garen’s current unit whereby the teams were established after they had completed assignments and performed deeds of merit.

Garen headed over there and had a quick glance.

Hornet Battle Team, Stinger-net Battle Team, Bell Ring Battle Team, Love-me-leave-me-not Battle Team…

These four were the strongest among the Eagle’s Nest teams. Their capabilities were not known but it was said that there were elite students in all of them. Those elite students who could resonate strongly with their Mechs were rising stars and had great hopes of attaining Level Five and above. Naturally, they would have powerful capabilities.

The top four battle teams would station themselves in the Assignment Room all year round. Inside, there was also a counter to recruit people at the same time.

Garen’s presence attracted the attention of a few as they recognized Garen’s identity. This Nonosiva, who had created a commotion when he had first joined Eagle’s Nest and was once the Freshmen’s First Seat, had naturally acquired quite a reputation for himself.

Nono did not pay any attention to them but walked past the Assignment Room and headed towards the martial arts simulation room on the utmost left. He swiped his student card and opened his eye wide.

Two red lights moved slightly, aimed at his pupils and flickered for a split second.

“Appointment found. Student Nono, wishing you a pleasant abuse,” the female computer voice sounded in a mischievous manner.

Chapter 864: A Sudden Turn of Events 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The door slid open without a sound.

Garen entered slowly.

It was an average-sized cylindrical room with silvery grey walls that had pipelines all over them.

In the center of the room was a huge silver ball of light formed by countless silver strands.

If you looked carefully, you would see that there were numerous data formula symbols circulating within the silver ball. There was also something that looked like planetary rings moving in a reversed flow.

Garen approached it. Uncountable minuscule white laser light bulbs suddenly lit up from the floor and shone at the ceiling above, forming several thin white beams of light.

Garen stopped in his steps and observed the laser lights on the floor.

Hiss… The countless laser light beams instantaneously distorted and formed a silver humanoid.

This humanoid had the same height and size as him but without any facial features, skin, hair or clothes, as if it was a fluid robot made out of molten silver.

“First stage of simulation begin…”

The female computer voice sounded from above.

Garen’s pupils constricted. In just a split second, the silver humanoid was charging at him in long strides, causing the ground to quake.

He suddenly felt an immense pressure coming down on him, suppressing his strength constitution to an ordinary person’s level and his Level Four Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower to Level One standard.

The silver silhouette’s arm bent forward and ferociously elbowed Garen’s face.

Boom!

Silver fluid splattered as Garen blocked the elbow with a single arm. A storm of attacks followed. The silver humanoid’s violent way of attacking was, in fact, his most frequently used attacking style.

Elbow tip, palm knife, side-kick and forward stomp. Every move was a basic combat technique, but when chained together, they gave off a wild and ferocious feel.

Boom boom boom boom!!!

Numerous deep explosive sounds reverberated. Garen and the silver humanoid exchanged more than ten strokes. Both parties took a few steps back and charged towards the opponent without any hesitation, attacking continuously.

Fist against fist. Palm knife against palm knife.

Garen’s face did not change. He paid close attention to his own style of attack and began to comprehend how this martial arts simulation could help correct his flaws.

The way this simulation quantum computer worked was by creating another self so that one could observe the exchanging of strokes and learn the pros and cons of one’s martial arts.

Both of them exchanged a flurry of blows. Not a single one showed any flaws. Garen’s martial arts had been thoroughly refined and tempered endless times, and so there would not be any loopholes. Since the silver humanoid was a computer simulation, the machinery would not show any weak points as well. It was a draw state as two flawless powerhouses competed with each other.

“Without flaws… this is my martial arts?” Garen gave another blow to the silver humanoid, “Wrong. My martial arts can’t be this shallow… I can create flaws despite there being none!”

He bellowed as both of his arms warped like spirals and transformed into dozens of fictional and real palm shadows.

Twelve Flying Dragon Fist!

Because he did not want to expose the true depths of this combat technique which he had taught Celine, he could only use this type of ordinary technique.

The silver humanoid was not tricked by the fictional moves and instantly produced many phantom fists. In the midst of all the phantom images, two fists collided with precision.

Bang!

The returned seismic energy caused both of them to be unsteady and forced them to fall back a number of steps.

Garen’s Crouched Eagle Talon willpower exploded abruptly. The air shook. With arms like a hawk, he suddenly charged forward and struck the silver humanoid’s epigastrium with a punch.

Splash…

The humanoid disintegrated and vanished completely.

“This is martial arts simulation? Battling with a flawless silver humanoid to grasp where my weaknesses and strengths are? Still, it was only a virtual figure simulation. Just a simple simulation as such is not enough to build combat awareness. Countless plots and schemes are needed as well.”

Garen let out a breath and felt that he did not gain anything.

“Second stage of simulation, begin…” the female computer voice sounded again.

The silver humanoid reappeared with a different look. He seemed stronger this time.

A punch came swiftly accompanied by the sound of whistling wind.

Garen still had the body constitution of an ordinary person. Staring at that fist, his heart skipped a beat. This humanoid had twice the attributes of an ordinary person. He himself was suppressed and was forced to fight with someone who was stronger than him!

His mind promptly spun and he made a similar punch. Halfway through, he changed his fist to a palm move and cut at the edge of the silver humanoid’s fist to make it go sideways.

Though in an instant, the counterpart abruptly released a mighty Willpower which struck the edge of his palm where it met the fist.

That was Level Four Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower as well, and it rushed out from their contact point.

Garen mustered up his Willpower to confront it. The power technique of high-level martial artists, Quake, was fiercely launched.

After several buzzing sounds, the silver humanoid’s Willpower broke off and it collapsed into a puddle of mud.

The power of Quake, a high-level technique that Secret Technique practitioners must practice, was not something that could be easily simulated. This was because it involved extremely complicated coordination control of the spirit and the body.

The computer did not have a spirit. The simulation of Willpower was programmed by someone beforehand because otherwise, it would not be able to produce even the slightest bit of Willpower. That was why this kind of simulated Quake was incapable and could only be defeated.

“Second stage finished. Would you like to enter the third stage? Willpower is advanced by one level, and the physical body by two levels with an additional Mad-blast attribute. Please take note, extreme attribute, the third stage would be to simulate the practitioner’s theoretical strongest form,” the female computer voice sounded again.

“Oh? My theoretical strongest form?” Garen was piqued. “Come on then.”

He was getting a little excited.

The silver humanoid formed once again. This time, it had a unique, half-transparent fluid body.

Whoosh… An explosive willpower energy field burst forth all of a sudden. It was Level Five. The humanoid’s body randomly made some hand-strokes and it tore the air instantly, creating ear-piercing sounds.

“Come on!” Garen smirked and initiated the attack, “Twelve Flying Dragon Fist!”

Dozens of fist shadows were sent forth in a barrage of fists. But in a flash, a violent and forceful energy field spread out. Without any movement, the humanoid simply stood on the spot, lifted his hand and flicked it at Garen.

Boom!!

Everything was wiped out.

Garen suddenly opened his eyes.

He was still standing in front of the huge silver light ball. There was nothing else around. No silver humanoid, no countless laser lights. It was as if he had just entered and fallen asleep standing.

“Silent hypnosis… or illusion system?” Garen closed his eyes. Scene after scene of what just happened clearly appeared in his mind.

“What a fascinating technology…”

“Congratulations on passing the second level. You are rewarded with Intelligent Robot Beginner Skill.”

A tiny half-transparent virtual chip appeared before him. Garen reached out his hands and lightly touched it. The chip immediately disappeared to becoming countless black lines which wormed into his terminal watch.

“Martial arts simulation correction ended. Evaluation result – Your martial arts are perfect without any loopholes. Martial arts simulation correction is not of much use to you,” the female computer voice concluded.

“Em… Besides me, how many have made it to the second level?”

“Up ’til now, one thousand two hundred and eighty-six people.”

“How ’bout the third level?”

“The third level is a theoretical battle model. Only one has made it through.”

“Alright…”

Exiting the simulation battle room, Garen did not receive any suggestions from the computer. Usually, when people left the room, they would receive suggestions from the quantum central computer regarding the strengths and weaknesses of their martial arts. The conclusion for him, however, was perfect and flawless.

Nonetheless, Garen was concerned about the third level because there actually was someone who made it through. Despite the huge difference in Willpower and the body, someone managed to break through this level. What a rare sight it is.

This was a pure power suppressing technique. And so, it was no longer an issue of technique. When a person could not even approach the opponent, what kind of battle method could he employ to win?

The Willpower in the third level had reached the peak of Level Five. When the energy field was dispersed, you could not even go near the body. Garen could not think of a way to defeat that state of himself.

Walking out of the simulation room, he still tried to ask.

“Could you tell me the name of the person who passed the third level?”

“A hundred and twenty-four years ago, Gero Kavis.”

Gero Kavis?

Garen repeated this name in his heart. This was the first time he realized that there was someone who could beat him in martial arts combat.

Fighting against a stronger opponent was never his way of martial arts. Yet, he admired the ones who could make it on this path.

After exiting Eagle’s Nest, a call came in.

“Nono, this is the latest news. The Great Light Mech of White Light Organization had declared war against Blackboard Academy at East Fate City. They have announced that they will take over East Fate City and have dispatched dozens of Shining Mechs. All of them are Level Five pilots! How imposing! What’s more, the capabilities shown by those Great Light Mechs surpass half of the Level Five pilots! They have defeated dozens of Black-Clothed Generals!”

“Doesn’t that mean this is an act of war?!” Garen was shocked.

“I’m afraid so. An instructor from the academy had set out with a team. It’s an Inheriting instructor, Thomas Andrew of Genre Red Whale. This is the first time an Inheriting pilot has been dispatched. I am already prepared to go and watch the battle. Are you going or not!?” Celine spoke quickly, “If you’re coming then come to Yellow Rose area, elevator-platform number four.”

“I’m coming now!”

Garen replied promptly.

“Remember to bring your Mech! This time, it’s not going to be peaceful.”

“Understood.”

Garen nodded.

As he finished the call, there was a trace of complicated emotions in his eyes.

“White Light dared to declare war against the whole of Blackboard Region. With this kind of capability, there surely won’t be just one Great Light Mech!”

A battle at Inheriting level… Regardless of everything, this was the top level battle strength of this world. He had to go and see for himself. This was a one in a million chance!

Chapter 865: Watching the Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

East Fate City

Looking down from a high altitude, the extensive dark grey city grounds below burst into a cluster of blue lights.

These bright blue flames rose into the sky without spreading. They merely burned in small areas of the city, unleashing eye-piercing blue flares. Thick white smoke billowed upwards through the flares and formed a vast greyish-white smoke cloud over the entire city.

Swish!!

A blue light beam descended from the sky and crashed into a grey high-rise building in the city. The blue ray instantly destroyed the center structural layer of the high-rise and penetrated straight through it.

With a thud, the entire high-rise collapsed into a pile of rubble.

“Warning again! Warning again!! All East Fate citizens, please immediately hide and flee the city. All citizens of East Fate, please immediately hide and flee the city to avoid injury,” Unfeeling announcements came and went, playing from a huge blue-black battleship hovering over the city.

These battleships looked like beetles that had been magnified many times and had spiking mouthpieces. Blue lights were spewing out from these mouthpieces.

Dozens of large battleships floated over the East Fate City and moved slowly, constantly scanning and capturing the ruins of the empty city below.

The residents of East Fate City who could hide had already hidden and those who could run had already fled, leaving an empty city.

The dead bodies and casualties over these days were not being precisely calculated anymore. Perhaps it had passed ten thousand, twenty thousand, or even a million.

In a huge beetle battleship, Garen and Celine stood together behind a group of commanders. Like many of the other youngsters from big businesses and huge households who were watching the battle, they did not make a sound. They were quietly listening to the big boss and commanders conversing at the front.

Standing in front of the crowd before a giant floor-to-ceiling window were three top pilots wearing a major general-ranked military uniform. An intense force field of Level Five Willpower was emanating off them without any restraints.

They were the supreme commanders and the tactical logistics team who were here this time to deal with the White Light Great Light Mech.

“If the real Great Light Mech appears in area A, His Highness Red Whale might not be able to arrive in time. We will need to resist the other party for at least ten minutes or more and hold him down regardless of the casualties. That is a result we cannot afford.”

“But the other party is in the dark and we are in the light. The key to campaign battles is in intelligence. They do not know which areas our main deployment are at. We also do not know which area their raids are hiding in,” the other man frowned.

“All the representatives of the major households here can raise up any suggestions you have. If it is indeed valuable, our military department and the academy will give out great rewards,” a long-eyebrowed Major General shifted his gaze over and looked in the direction where the wealthy youngsters were whispering among one another.

The reason why these people were called here was to make use of the power of the various households. Maybe there would be many unexpected channels in these households that could come into play.

This was also the practice of repeated battles.

“For the defense alert in the twelve areas of East Fate City, I think our Bane household can contribute,” a chubby young man raised his hand and said. “A new type of jamming device developed by our family can locate the enemy’s specific position in jamming mode, which is equivalent to the enhanced bat fighter system. We are willing to contribute a hundred sets for free.”

“The Bane household right? Thank you for your support! How are the specific settings and moving condition of this type of jammer…”

“The specific parameters are as such…”

The two began to carefully discuss the layout plan.

The rest of the crowd were still whispering to one another. Garen and Celine stood at the back where they had deliberately walked to.

“Where’s your Mech?” Celine whispered.

“In the battleship’s Mech depot, why?” Garen asked.

“Take note, we are now really entering the battle zone. My Mech is a high-grade good brought out from the household. I can jump and leave at any time during crucial moments. Yours is just an ordinary good. If there is any problem, you will be in trouble,” Celine whispered.

“I know,” Garen nodded. “But benefits and risks coexist, don’t they? Being able to watch an Inherited level battle doesn’t come easily. The last Inherited-level battle record was a few decades ago. It was even classified as the highest level of confidentiality. We have no way to access it. Now that there is this opportunity, it would be a waste if we do not take hold of it.”

“If we can find the key to Inherited Level, it will be very helpful for our advancement in the future.”

Minutes and seconds passed by. Garen and Celine conversed softly. Like everyone else, the two appeared to be inconspicuous in a group of rich youngsters who were dressed in fancy clothes.

After some time, a Shining Mech figure finally appeared.

A Shining Mech suddenly leaped and appeared in front of the battleship, wielding a dagger as it dashed towards them in an attempt to pierce through the thick armor with its lone strength.

“Kill him!”

The commander waved his hand and several Blackboard Mechs flew out to meet it.

All of them were Black-Clothed Generals. They stood directly before the Shining Mech in a group.

The second batch of Blackboard Mechs flew out next. When they were about to lay siege to the other side, they encountered another Shining Mech.

Under the gloomy clouds, the Mechs could only be seen as interweaving red and white firepower in the air.

Suddenly, a beetle battleship exploded a distance away. Huge red flames spread across the sky, engulfing an area of hundreds of meters in the city below.

Two black and white humanoid Mechs flew out of the fireball. One of the Mechs was black with striking red eyes and two huge red scythes in its hands.

The other Mech was fully white, and both hands clutched a giant machete that glittered brightly. It was pursuing and hacking at the black Mech.

“It’s Master Red-Eyed Medero!!” someone who recognized the black Mech called out in the battleship.

“Go and call for backup!” someone shouted.

“No! That’s the strongest no.5 Shining Mech under the Great Light Mech. I have seen the records before. None of us can be its opponent! Even Master Medero would not be able to hold out. We will only die if we go out!” someone opposed.

“Yes, and they’re too close to each other and are entangled in close combat. If we can’t keep up with their rhythm, we’ll be doing a disservice!”

A group of people quickly concluded. The three commanders did not voice out and were calm and steady as if they already had a plan for this situation. However, some people were already feeling a little scared. A similar beetle battleship had been blown up, indicating that their side was not guaranteed to be safe.

“With the presence of Master Red Whale there won’t be a problem!” someone said confidently. This statement slightly calmed the worried crowd. After all, this ship of theirs was different from other ships. This ship was carrying important figures and the defense force was also more than three times stronger.

Medero dragged the No.5 Shining Mech and left the area speedily, heading towards other areas. Very soon, they were out of sight.

Over on this side, the victor and the loser of the battle between the Shining Mechs and Blackboard Mechs of the battleship had also emerged. One Shining Mech had exploded while the other had fled; the Blackboard Mechs had lost two and a third had to be written off and could not fight again.

“Have you ever wondered why these White Light Mechs chose East Fate City for their declaration of war?” Garen looked at the Shining Mech that was fleeing away further and asked in a low voice.

Celine shook her head.

“I’ve never thought about it. But, the household analysts have analyzed that the real reason should be to attract attention and actually seek other purposes.”

“It’s possible. But the biggest possibility is that they are trying to figure out how much combat power Blackboard Region can currently deploy.”

Garen conjectured, “From the previous pulse wave incident to the current formal declaration of war, perhaps there will be a greater action later on. I feel that such a huge price and action is no longer for the purpose of getting something.”

Celine thought deeply.

“Indeed. This kind of move should not be simply for that. If it is only for that purpose, they could have done it secretly. There is no need to make such a big fanfare. Too much power is spent here on direct confrontation.”

“So I’m guessing that it is likely that White Light itself is tangled up with Blackboard Region in something else,” Garen whispered.

“Other aspects of the entanglement?” Celine thought about it.

At this moment, there was a sudden sound of an explosion from the battleship.

Pewwww!

An ear-piercing harsh noise came from above.

The entire observation window of the battleship immediately became red. It was blinding and more than a dozen people’s eyesight were affected in an instant. They screamed as tears flowed from their clenched eyes.

The battleship shook violently and returned to its calmed state.

“It’s Master Red Whale’s Bright Eyes!!” one commander shouted, “Don’t worry, Master Red Whale has made his move. I believe it will soon be a success!”

Pewwwww!

Suddenly there was a shrill cry again. The floor-to-ceiling window turned red once more.

Garen did not close his eyes but looked straight at the vast red light. Such brightness was nothing to him.

But from the cries of these two voices, he had a bad feeling.

While everyone was closing their eyes to avoid the red light, he promptly held Celine’s hand and swiftly moved backward, running towards the Mech depot. Their footsteps were silent and no one actually realized when they entered another passageway.

“What are you doing!?” Celine shook off his hand and asked loudly.

“I’m afraid there’s a bit of danger,” Garen explained as he walked. He quickly came to the Mech depot and took out his special permit. He brushed it in front of the guard and got permission.

After the electronic door opened automatically, he pulled Celine inside.

“Find your Mech right away. We may have to flee here quickly.”

“What do you mean? How could it be!?” Celine said unbelievingly. “We actually have a troop of thirty-two Black-Clothed Generals escorting our battleship. It’s impossible to have any problems!”

“Of course it is unlikely that something will happen now. But what if His Highness Red Whale is defeated?” Garen said plainly.

“That… shouldn’t be possible!” Celine looked a little sluggish.

“There’s nothing that’s impossible! I’m not here just to simply go one round around the city and then head back. Wouldn’t you want to watch an Inherited Level battle up close? The battle should be happening above our heads right now.”

Garen enticed.

“You’re crazy!” Celine’s eyes widened. “Both of us, Level Two and Level Three brats go up close to watch a life-and-death battle of Level Six Inherited Levels?”

“I’m not crazy. If you want to go then get into your Mech!” Garen went straight to the front of his Mech and stepped onto the elevator platform.

Wuuu…

The elevator-platform sensed the arrival of the owner and slowly rose.

Celine clenched her teeth and spoke no further. She quickly ran to her own elevator platform.

Her Mech was a black double shield humanoid with silver borders. Her two shields were weapons of destruction with sharp serrations at the edge, not just for defending.

At this time, Garen had already jumped into his own Mech and sat in the cockpit. He hit the activate key.

Duuu…

The Mech glowed all around. Blocks of floating light curtains and strips of white data flowed and surrounded the body.

‘Double Blade Captain, proceed with armor charge?” the battleship central computer enquired.

“Of course,” Garen sat up straight, his eyes sparkling with excitement. He took out a small black box from his pocket. It was obvious that the surface of the box had been disguised so that it looked ordinary.

He pressed the box to the console and the entire box melted directly into the inner parts of the Mech.

“Double Edge No. 1, all set to go.”

“Combat readiness system complete by default.”

“Combat readiness system complete by default.”

“Ejection device ready!”

“Ejection device ready!”

“Set off!”

Boom!

The Double Edge Mech lit up at once. The gigantic body blasted off and launched through the opening of the spiral pathway above.

Chapter 866: Watching the Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Just a split second behind, the wolf shield from Celine’s Mech also flew out. Two Mechs shot out of the battleship leaving a long trail of white smoke behind them. They flew straight up into the skies above.

At this moment, there was also a large number of different types of black and white Mechs flying up into the sky besides them. For a time, it was like many missile-shaped fireworks had flown into the sky.

The entire airspace of East Fate City was densely packed with numerous Mechs.

Up high at several kilometers’ altitude, two Mechs, one red and one white, were entangled in a high-speed battle.

The red Mech had circles of scarlet chains floating at its back that was constantly looking for a chance to bite like a poisonous snake. The whole body also exuded traces of Willpower ripples.

Pointed sharp knives extended from the white Mech’s fingertips. Each of them was half the length of a Mech’s body and they looked ferocious. They formed a storm of twisted metal blades with the white Mech as the center point.

As Garen and Celine came up, they were not the first group of people to do so. Several Mechs were already hovering around, watching from far.

“This is the Inherited-level battle? It doesn’t look any different from our kind of fight?” Celine doubted.

“The difference is huge,” Garen murmured, “watch their actions.”

Celine was reminded and began to watch closely every subtle movement of the two Mechs.

“This… This is…” not only did she saw with her own eyes that something was wrong, the detection equipment carried by her Mech itself also issued a warning signal. “Each time they clash, they have an average of fifteen Level Five pilots’ amount of power!? Isn’t this too exaggerated?!”

“This is Mech Resonance,” Garen had noticed the clues. “They are resonating with their own Mechs and have reached a very high level. At Level Six, the Mechs themselves are already equivalent to a living organism. They also have a potential explosion mechanism similar to that of a human body. It is Resonance that is able to take what was burst out from this kind of potential…”

“Watch out!” Garen pulled Celine’s Mech all of a sudden and retreated in a rush.

Pewwwww!!

Horrifying red lights suddenly flashed across the sky.

Red Whale and the Great Light Mech simultaneously burst into action.

Countless shadows of chains suddenly appeared behind Red Whale, hurling and whirling towards the other party.

The outbreak at this moment was way beyond the previous conventional battle. Each chain carried along a terrible impact and variable frequency magnetic field. They stabbed towards the Great Light Mech in an overwhelming manner from all angles like serpents.

“Red Whale Contend!”

An aged and low-pitched man’s voice rang through the sky.

“Old man! Your move is antiquated!!” a raging man’s voice came from the Great Light Mech.

“Pool of Radiance!”

The Great Light Mech suddenly erupted. Copious amounts of white liquid light dripped down the Mech’s legs and floated in the air, forming an oval white pool.

The red chains came into contact with the white light pool and everything was submerged in red and white light. Nothing could be seen.

In the midst of the silence, a huge tornado formed by the turbulent flow of red and white energy was slowly taking shape.

Garen once again tugged Celine and hurriedly retreated a few kilometers. Only then, did they break away from the hurricane’s traction.

Some of the Mechs who were watching the battle were one step slower. Several Mechs with Level Four and Level Five force fields were dragged into it and instantly smashed into pieces. Seeing this chilled the hearts of the others and they flew far away once again to keep themselves safe.

The red-white tornado stood at the center of East Fate City. It slowly spun and absorbed everything around it that could be absorbed. Looking into it from far, Garen’s eyesight could barely distinguish the silhouettes of the two Mechs. They were still confronting each other!

“This kind of power…!!!” although Celine’s main household also had an Inherited Level pilot, his status had not reached such a high level yet. This was also the first time he had seen a battle between Inherited Level pilots.

“I am finally understanding a little why pilots are the strongest players in the universe,” Celine licked her dry lips as her eyes were filled with irrepressible amazement.

Garen also felt the same.

Although the density quality of this level of destructive power was not too high, the scope of this destruction… He speculated that to physically fight against this level of destruction power, his physical constitution had to be at least more than 30 points. Even still, there was still a possibility of getting hurt.

This level had reached the terror level of the last battle in the Totem World.

And this was only the capability of Level Six. According to the training method given to him by Forbidden Core, after it, there were still Level Seven and Level Eight… maybe even Level Nine…

In all fairness, though Garen had always focused on Secret Techniques, such a level of relying on individual strength to destroy the planet was beyond even the power of Demon Lord Class. Ancient Endor’s Demon Kings might have been able to be invincible across the time and space of the surrounding parallel universes, but they were still inferior to the top Mechs in terms of pure destructive power. Although they might be able to achieve similar destructive effects through other methods, they would definitely not be so straightforward.

“Then again, there’s no need to belittle oneself. The merits of the Demon Lord Class is that its strength lies in other aspects. Its true soul is immortal and the demon can never die and will reincarnate. Even if the true soul is destroyed, as long as Mother Stream does not vanish, it can have a chance to make a comeback. But, it is almost impossible for the Mech to achieve this level. Although they are powerful, they cannot completely destroy the Demon Lord Class,” Garen was slightly relieved, though he still had a slight worry in his heart. He did not have the qualification to see the highest level Mechs. Perhaps there could be new top technologies and capabilities appearing.

The huge tornado slowly spun, connecting the earth and the sky. This terrorizing scene also caught the attention of all the troops around.

The battle between Inherited Levels had once again shown itself to the world after several decades.

This was no longer the level that quantity could make up for.

Garen quietly piloted his Mech and looked at the tornado from far. However, he was looking for a way out in the comparison of Secret Techniques and the Willpower system of the Mech.

He was seeking for a way to absorb the civilizational advantages of this system and integrate it with his own strengths.

Boom!!

The tornado collapsed. Two figures burst out of it and crashed into the ruined city below, creating two huge pits.

There was a distorted black light in one of the pits, from which the Great Light Mech jumped out and escaped. The spatial lockdown device that came after was one step too late.

In another pit, the Red Whale Mech flew up again, wobbling slightly. Obviously, he had been seriously injured. There was a huge crack in the Mech’s chest and abdomen. What flowed out from the inside was not the same type of components as the ordinary Mechs but a type of liquid silver mucus.

The Red Whale Mech was quickly led away by a special Mech medical team.

Garen and the group of watching pilots also left and returned to the original battleship.

Unlike the general pilots, on the surface, he appeared to have Level Four Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower but in fact, he had Level Five Forbidden Willpower on the inside. This training method given by Forbidden Core seemed very advanced. Although it did not look like the type that focused on battle, its level must be far greater than a general training method like Crouched Eagle Talon.

Garen could feel that the quality of the Forbidden Willpower had surpassed Crouched Eagle Talon’s by at least three times the density. Now that it had reached Level Five, even though it had been forcefully advanced using all of his potential points in one breath, it could somehow derive a special ability to increase self-repair by one level. That was already extremely abnormal on its own.

“It’s presumable that the Forbidden Core would never have thought that I could rush to Level Five in such a short period of time,” Garen thought. “The White Light Organization officially had declared war. Obviously, there can’t be just one Great Light Mech in place. There definitely should be a countermove. But now that no countermove has appeared, perhaps their main attention is really on the Forbidden Core. Could it be that I was thinking wrongly about it previously?”

He was puzzled. He stared at the distant sky towards the direction of East Fate City, where the White Light Organization had set up their defense area.

“Nonosiva.”

Suddenly a loud call rang out in his mind.

Garen stiffened. He did not discern how the sound had been transmitted to him.

“I am the Forbidden Core that made a deal with you, Red Moon. You could actually break through the training method levels in such a short time. Your talents are truly beyond my expectations.”

“So, it means that you really did some tricks to the training method?” Garen’s face darkened.

“Certainly. But surely you would have checked it many times, didn’t you? There were no dangerous changes.”

“Breaking through one level was the basis for you to be able to contact me?” Garen asked.

“This training method which I have given you is called Big Phantom Sound. It came from an ancient Inheriting sect that used to be glorious for a while. Their pilots used tones as their attacking weapons. At the same time, what was more outstanding about them was that they could achieve long-distance resonance communication technique even at this kind of low level,” Red Moon simply explained.

“Is there really such a powerful means of communication?” Garen did not believe it. The other party did not even know where he was, but the voice could cross over numerous disturbances in between the distance and still be heard clearly. Just a simple explanation of Big Phantom Sound would not sit well with him.

“Of course, there is a little bit of assistance,” Red Moon was not embarrassed to be seen through. “That idiot Clint has to make me worry about everything. There was no other way. I separated an imprint of mine and told him that there were only two imprints can be used.”

“What’s this imprint that you’re talking about?” Garen’s face looked a little darker, faintly feeling unsettled.

“Of course, it’s the inherited imprint of the Forbidden Mech!” Red Moon simply answered. “This, in effect, is the usage rights of Forbidden Mech that many had attempted but failed to seize. Only those who have a Forbidden Inheriting imprint can qualify to participate in the final battle. Of course, a Mech can only pick one pilot and the others are sub-imprints, all of which is to assist and ensure the existence of the main imprint.”

“Are you joking with me?” Garen’s expression changed.

“You thought I was joking with you? Let me tell you, boy, once you get into my boat, you can never think of going back!” Red Moon’s true form was beginning to show. “Once you abolish this level of Willpower, it will also affect all the Willpower you’ve had before and destroy them all! All the years of your hard work being destroyed instantly, heheheh…”

“You want me to assist the main imprint?” Garen suddenly smirked. “What a naïve idea you have.”

“The main imprint has absolute suppression on the sub-imprints. It would be useless even if you wanted to bring harm to it,” Red Moon chuckled sinisterly. “Once you make your move, your Inherited Mech in the future will completely disintegrate in one go and directly explode!”

“Merely an imprint?” Garen was too lazy to talk nonsense with him. “You really think that I couldn’t get rid of it?”

While talking, he had already begun to examine his entire body. He quickly found a floating object like a dandelion seed inside the unknown Willpower.

Truly, there was no way to move this thing using Willpower. But, Garen sneered and switched to the means of Secret Techniques. Blood flowed inside his body and numerous Living Secret Technique blue lines spread out and rushed toward the seed imprint.

Chapter 867: Changes 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Numerous blue lines rushed at the object that looked like a dandelion seed from all angles like a living creature and surrounded it.

Garen slowed down and became more and more gentle. Who knew what else the Forbidden Core had placed inside? If something went wrong, it would be very troublesome. After all, it was inside his body.

“Are you vainly attempting to remove the imprint? Just stop your wishful thinking. This thing cannot be handled by a low-level guy like you,” Red Moon laughed.

Before the voice had faded away, there was a light cracking sound.

The large number of blue lines that Garen had manipulated had wrapped around the seed completely. As they tightened and shrunk non-stop, they actually crushed it savagely.

There was no reaction. Garen had been ready to deal with any trouble and problems that might have arisen. However, after the seed was crushed, no unexpected changes occurred.

He gently manipulated the blue lines to draw the seed into the palm of his hand and formed a cluster of blue lines.

“Be fractured.”

As his voice sounded, the Living Secret Technique lines that were connected to the rear of the cluster of blue lines suddenly tore and broke. The cluster of lines independently formed a single ball and flew out of the Mech through the Mech’s nacelle.

Boom!

The cluster of lines suddenly shattered and turned into countless blue light spots. Bits and pieces of the seed fragments inside were clearly visible.

“Oh…?” the voice of Red Moon promptly became a bit surprised. “You actually removed the seed…”

He did not seem too surprised.

“I did not expect you to have reached the point where you can eliminate the seed imprint on your own… But, the real core part is not what you can imagine…”

“You really think that your imprint can be planted on anybody? That’s rather unbelievable?” Garen sneered.

He absent-mindedly held out his hand and opened them again. There were other clusters of blue lines gathering in the palm of his hand.

“Fracture…”

Clusters of blue lines broke off and flew out of the Mech.

“What!!” Red Moon’s countenance finally changed. “You…!!??”

Garen stretched his hand towards the clusters on lines in the air and gently made a grasping movement.

“Wait! Don’t!!”

Red Moon suddenly yelled anxiously.

Crunch!!

Almost at the same time, all the clusters of lines burst together, turning into numerous blue light spots, slowly dissipating and faded away between heaven and earth.

In that instant, Garen’s face went pale. He bent down and vomited a big mouthful of blood.

“You!!” Red Moon’s voice broke off abruptly and disappeared instantly.

Garen was faintly aware that something was amiss. This separation seemed to have stripped off most of the imprint restrictions. But, there were still some remaining parts that could not be completely isolated. These parts seemed to be the most crucial points but they were deeply connected to his heart and brain.

He could clearly feel that a slight wave of force field was constantly emanating from a distant place. It was not the force field of a human, but a kind of an irregular pulse, sometimes fast and sometimes slow.

Without any reason, he knew in his heart that it was Red Moon’s pulse.

“Is this the main source of the imprint?” Garen was suddenly enlightened. As a master of the body’s soul manipulation, he was able to keep abreast of the slightest changes in himself. Although he did not know the means by which Red Moon had planted the imprint on his body, at this moment, he could still clearly feel the remaining functions of the imprint.

The parts that restricted him had been forcibly eliminated using Living Secret Technique. However, the remaining part was Red Moon’s most fundamental source-of-life imprint. This thing could not be eliminated because it did not bring any harm to the body itself but had great benefits instead.

If an ordinary person thoroughly integrated this source-of-life imprint, he or she might be able to instantaneously stimulate Willpower and gain a level. The activation of potential was the function of the imprint.

Garen’s body did not have any rejection towards anything that did not harm his body.

There was basically no way to transfer this remaining part. It had already been deeply connected to the heart and brain and had begun to slowly release its own energy.

Garen closed his eyes slightly. He did not realize that this imprint would be so difficult to deal with. Absorbing the source of this imprint would undoubtedly benefit him greatly. However, it would also covertly create a direct connection with Red Moon. If he chose not to absorb it, on the other hand, it would leave crippling injuries to this body because it was already connected to the heart and brain. After removing Red Moon’s limitation control, there was only one choice left at all.

“Forbidden imprint? Since there are only parts that are good for me, then why should I not accept this gift?” Garen opened his eyes and there were blue traces washing over them.

Waves of Living Secret Technique blue lines emerged from the Secret Technique core inside of his body and quickly wrapped around the remaining sources of the imprint.

******************

Radiation area

On the deserted grey-yellow grassland, Clint, who was slowly following a convoy, suddenly trembled.

“What happened to you? Clint!” Baylon asked worriedly when she saw his abnormal reaction.

The two were closely following the team of people they had met in the sewers. This team was a small group in the radiation belt, an outgoing search team affiliated with a survival site. They specialized in hunting for edible mutated living beings and water sources with a low level of radiation. At the same time, they were also tasked with clearing all the hidden dangers of the surrounding areas.

“All right? Clint kid,” a yellow-bearded uncle at his side patted Clint’s shoulder. He was the only chemist in the team and could use a variety of radioactive materials and mutated biological plants to combine and mix together into an agent called poisonous mist. It could dispel the radiating poisonous fog in many places for a short time.

“I’m… I’m okay,” Clint drew back his body and lowered his head. His face, however, showed an unexpected joy.

“Watch your path carefully. You both just came out from the region. The danger of the radiation belt is not what you can imagine. Many times, even a small scorpion that suddenly appeared out of the ground can kill you easily. We can’t afford any antidotes and serum at all,” the uncle said earnestly. “Even if it’s an ordinary cold, it will quickly weaken a strong man as well. The viruses in the radiation belt are far more powerful than in the regions and drugs are even more expensive than gold and diamonds!”

“I understand, uncle,” Clint nodded wearily and looked at the tightly bundled-up Baylon. Unlike these Radiation people here on the outside, their skins had not been exposed much and seemed a lot more tender. Under the gentle reminder of the convoy’s big sister, Baylon quickly covered up her face and body.

In the radiation belt, even beautiful women could attract unprecedented disasters.

Seeing that Clint was alright, Baylon continued to hurry along while slowly twisting together the rattans of radiation plants in the car. After soaking this kind of entwined rattan in oil and tanning them, they could be woven into durable pouches. These pouches could not be pierced through by the fangs of mutated living beings. They made the best carrying bags and could be exchanged for some basic food items and drinking water in the team.

There were more than a dozen people in the convoy. Everyone had to work in order to obtain grade three filtered water and food. These food contained radioactive toxins. Eating them would result in more severe radiation sickness and finally, the body would rot and die. However, as long as it was not consumed continuously, drinking some water with the purity level of grade two and above would allow the body to self-detoxify without any serious problems.

As for drinking water that was less than grade two, the residual toxins would result in more ulcers and radiation spots on the body. So long as they did not eat it at frequent intervals, there would be no problem.

The team gradually calmed down.

Clint suppressed the joy in him and began to communicate with Red Moon in his heart.

.

“What! Radiation belt!?” Red Moon felt a little irritated after learning of where they were.

“You guys actually entered the radiation belt?! Even the food here is poisonous and the water source is filled with bacterial viruses and radiation toxins. Surviving itself is an issue if you don’t have filtration equipment! It’s worse than in the desert!” Red Moon seemed to be familiar with the radiation belt.

“Yeah…” Clint had some understanding of it during these days. “In the radiation belt, Big Sister told me that the most important things are pure water filters and medicines. Any team without a pure water filter cannot survive for more than three days. When facing any trouble, antibiotics and anti-inflammatory drugs will be the key to saving lives. Previously inside the region, we could buy a pile of these easily in the stores. Outside here, I did not expect it to be…”

He became silent. Those who had not been to the outside of the region would not have any idea that there existed a world out there which was arduous to live in and that this world was actually the main environment of the entire mother planet.

“You’ve finally found out? You all used to be little kids that lived in a greenhouse. In the radiation belt, anyone, pay attention, anyone would do anything just for a small piece of food or a vial of high-grade pure water. Women would sell their bodies, men would toil like beasts of burden and fight desperately with mutated beings. Anyone who can live above fifty years of age is blessed,” Red Moon seemed to be deeply moved. “What bad news…”

“So what do we do now?” Clint was at a loss.

“It’s okay. I have found a foreign aid for you. But it’s a pity that he can’t help you for the time being… Hey!!” Red Moon suddenly screamed in pain in the middle of the conversation. “That damn freak! How did he get rid of my imprint!” his voice turned into doubt.

“What’s wrong, Lord?” Clint asked cautiously.

“Nothing, it’s none of your business. Go and make sure you train your Willpower!” Red Moon replied impatiently. Comparing Nono whose talent had been overlooked by him the first time with this trash-looking maggot, his anger rose.

“Oh…”

Red Moon was distracted just now. He was simultaneously talking to Clint and Nonosiva, who was far away. But, the result was that there was a forced disconnection from that side. The outer layer that was mainly the means of his imprint control was actually eliminated and left with the source alone. This equaled to peeling off the shell from a shell-enveloped sweet and consuming the sweet itself.

“But it won’t be all lost if it’s eaten…” Red Moon said to himself.

Looking at the silly-faced Clint again, Red Moon’s heart was filled with sadness once more. If it wasn’t due to not having any other way and having to pick this trash as the main heir, choosing a real one-in-a-million talent like Nonosiva would certainly have restored some of his glory by now; maybe already even reaching the standard of Level Five.

Chapter 868: Changes 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“However, I am quite clear about the temper of that guy over there. I have to go along with him. Otherwise, things will backfire. Over on this side, I can use the way of the wolf…” Red Moon was sulking due to the Nono incident. He looked at Clint and suddenly gave a sinister smile.

“Clint!”

“Ah… Eh?” Clint was just about to get into the state of training his Willpower but was jolted awake. He opened his eyes and had a blank look on his face.

“From today onwards, I will arrange training tasks for you every day. If they are not completed, there will be various punishments. In order to improve your strength and combat awareness as quickly as possible, this is the only way we can do it. After all, we are now in the radiation belt. There are dangers here everywhere and if you do not increase self-awareness, you may not know even know how you died.”

“Oh… Oh… I see, I’ll work hard!” Clint nodded his head with seriousness.

“That’s good. You have to know that once you don’t finish the task, I will punish you by forcefully taking over your body. You have to be clear about this. Well, for the first task of the day, engrave the first layer of the Willpower imprint once again!”

“Ah??” Clint was stunned. Engraving Willpower imprint was the way to training Willpower. Each different training method would have a different imprint and each layer of training method would also have an imprint in increasing complexity which had to be engraved on different parts of the body to activate the Willpower of the cells in that part.

This was also the main method for training Willpower; repeated engraving would deepen the traces. This was the way to continuously progress in the training method.

In the past, it was possible to engrave an imprint once in four days under his normal state. This was considered to be very good for Clint, who had been forcefully advanced to Willpower Level One. Yet now, Red Moon actually asked him to engrave once a day!

“Lord… this…”

“If you cannot do it, you will go for a naked run! Or go show your little wee-wee[1] in front of the convoy’s Big Sister and shout three times, “I’m a scum!”” Red Moon grinned slyly.

“F*ck…” there was absolutely no way he was doing that!!

Clint’s head immediately went numb and he had goosebumps all over his body. Quickly, without saying anything else, his whole body and mind went into the state of Willpower training.

He knew that Red Moon would walk his talk. In the event of such a terrible incident, his reputation would be sullied for the rest of his life!

*********************

Garen walked into the academy. The number of students in the academy had decreased significantly as many students had received tasks of patrolling in the city, similar to the tasks he did before, as there was a lack of manpower.

Besides Blackboard Academy, other academies in the region were also doing the same thing. The higher-ups of Blackboard had officially entered into a war with the White Light Organization. With East Fate City as the frontline, both sides had invested large numbers of standard Mech units. The Blackboard army and the Ray Print Mech of White Light had been killing each other. There would be a big scale battle every three days while every two days, a small-scale one. The death toll on both sides was increasing.

The White Light Organization had shown more than just the strength of a terrorist organization. East Fate City was located at the border and back of the Maria Region. It was impossible that this situation did not have the acknowledgment and support of the other two regions.

Blackboard was now dealing with the issue of the forbidden core as well as the implication of a possible inter-region war.

Garen paced slowly on the sidewalk of the academy. The green belt beside that was planted with safflowers had been trimmed neatly. Looking ahead, there were maglev circular displays the size of washbasins playing the news.

‘In recent days, the Polar Region and our military have been conducting joint military training. The newest submarine-launched missiles have been revealed. According to relevant sources, the new missiles have not only enhanced the scatter-tracking on the foundation of the Nightingale models, they have also been equipped with a special erosion-type force field generator on their warheads. It can effectively carry out powerful interference attacks on high-level pilots…”

The news broadcaster smiled and spoke confidently as if local high-level pilots could completely overpower the terrorists with just a new type of missile.

Garen strolled past the display as he observed the increasingly tense atmosphere in the Blackboard Region. The atmosphere of the war had already seeped into the academy, where soldiers in military uniforms were often seen entering and leaving the campus.

“My uncle was involved in the research of the new missile. The actual power is not as imagined…” a few passing students shook their heads while discussing among one another.

“How is the situation in East Fate City?”

“Not sure. We were only responsible for the periphery cleaning.”

“If you are an elite student, you will certainly receive an inner job.”

“Some did receive it, but the casualties were quite severe. I heard that even Senior Red Eyes was seriously injured.”

Several students discussed while passing by on Garen’s right. They all looked like senior students, each emanating the force field of Level One Willpower. The senior-level eight-petaled flower silver logo was also worn on their chests. Eight years of schooling was the normal level of most students. For the tens of thousands of students in Blackboard Academy, ninety percent of them were actually at such a level. They made up the majority of ordinary people in the academy.

Even if the students were studying at home, they were also talking about the war.

For elites like Garen who could achieve Level Three Willpower, many of them had a lot of military ranks and they could officially enter the battlefield as military soldiers.

He continued to stroll forward. It was already late afternoon. The sun was rather dim, though it still shone on his military uniform. The black belt strapped diagonally to his shoulder reflected the light and dragged out a long shadow behind him.

The gap between students was vast sometimes.

Garen sighed in his heart.

All of them were students and yet, some barely met the graduation criteria. They only had Level One Willpower and could only serve as foot soldiers. Some, in reverse, could serve as one of the main players in the middle stratum.

This was just like the universities of Earth. Some students would be approached by top companies offering them high salaries while they were still schooling and had even built their own businesses with billions in net worth; whereas, some of them were still wasting their lives away and had to submit resume after resume to seek for a minimum-wage job after graduating.

Some had been able to leave their names in notable research papers while some could only plagiarize from elsewhere for their dissertation.

With a sigh and some stirring in his emotions, Garen quickened his pace and rapidly moved toward his destination.

The students he encountered on the road all showed sights of envy as they saw the Captain-rank military uniform on him. Being able to achieve the rank of a captain at such a young age, it was obvious that it was either someone in the family or he himself must have served with distinction. His future prospects were limitless. As long as one had reached Willpower Level Four, being a field officer was certain. If one were lucky enough to advance to Level Five, one could attain the general level.

Some first and second-year juniors and third and fourth-year seniors all thought that Garen was at least a year five student. They could not help but gaze over.

Garen kept his gaze straight and walked directly towards his destination.

A white mountain-shaped building stood more than one hundred meters away. There was a stone monument inserted on the edge of the green belt. The upper part was engraved with the words: Academy Main Building.

After adjusting the collar of his shirt, Garen strode towards the white stone staircase in front of the building.

************

Pap.

The jade-colored stone paperweight was slowly lowered and made a crisp sound on the redwood table.

“You want to apply for a jump in levels?” in the red office, the head of the department, Ansader, sat in his chair and calmly looked at the student in front of him who had submitted his application. This was the fourth student he had met today requesting a jump in levels. He had not been surprised.

But what really astounded him was that this student was able to attain the rank of captain when he was just a second-year student.

He looked down at the paper report.

“The reason you gave is that you have already reached the graduation standard in the academic subjects and you hope to formally join the military to become an official member. I have already received the test results. They were really good,” Ansader carefully considered his words.

“Thank you, chief,” Garen stood upright and looked straight ahead. It was a standard officer’s posture.

“Although your request completely complies with the standards, your application is indeed very difficult for me,” Ansader murmured. “No one had ever jumped across such a large span in one go. You want to jump from the second year straight to graduation. Do you think that you could finish eight years of schooling in just two years?”

“Chief, according to my investigation, there were indeed some precedents. Four people from the Black Rain Generals have had such a cross-level record. Black Star, Red Eyes, and five others have also made such a big leap,” Garen answered truthfully.

“You did your homework well,” Ansader rubbed his temples. It was not the first time he had encountered this kind of genius who thought he was the best in the world and would mention Black Star and Red Eyes at every turn. In fact, this happened quite often. Geniuses were always proud, thinking that they could be compared to any great celebrity and that the world’s successful powerhouses were only a little bit luckier than they were.

“Well, you were last year’s freshmen’s First Seat. Although you couldn’t get into the elite, it was due to the accident between you and Celine which caused you two to fight too early. Not being able to continue in the competition was an accident as well,” to tell the truth, Ansader still admired this genius Nono, who had worked hard with his own efforts and climbed up step by step. Seeing such a genius would always remind him of his past self.

“I will write a letter of recommendation for you. You can take the letter and go to Professor Van Doe in the inner courtyard. He is a good friend of mine and the leading master in the Crouched Eagle Talon Training Method. He has been exploring the feasibility of Level Six Crouched Eagle Talon in the inner court.”

It was not the first time that Ansader had done this. In any case, several geniuses could be found in each semester and he would send them to his old friends. Professor Van Doe was famous for his superb Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower. It was just that he had faded out from people’s horizon a hundred years ago which was why he was not known in the eyes of the juniors nowadays.

“Professor Van Doe?” Garen did not expect this result. “If I enter the inner courtyard, would I get the qualification to accept tasks that go out to the radiation belt?”

“Radiation belt? You want to go out?” Ansader’s eyes suddenly sharpened.

“Yes! I know the truth about the radiation belt,” Garen said frankly, his voice became smaller.

Both their vision met and Garen did not avoid it.

Chapter 869: Resonance Stage 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The radiation belt is an inevitable region between the regions,” Ansader withdrew his gaze and sighed.

“Since you wanted to go, I will talk to my old friend. However, you have to understand that once you have radiation disease, you will never be able to return.”

“I know,” Garen nodded.

“If you know it, then…”

“I have a personal business that I need to attend to and it can only be resolved at the radiation belt. Actually, I have been there once before,” Garen did not hide his intention.

“Is it?” Ansader naturally could find out the record of Garen leaving the region but he was pleased with the frankness of him.

He quickly wrote down the relevant approval documents and then sent a message to his old friend. There was a prompt reply after waiting for a short while.

“Alright, you can go now. It’s the inner courtyard mural area no. 13, Van Doe Manor.”

“Understood,” Garen nodded, stood to attention and turned around to leave.

“Let Fire Spirit in.”

The voice of Ansader came faintly from behind.

*********************************

Blackboard Region, East Fate City Emergency Action Center

In a black, dark base, numerous black buildings looked like black plates that had been inserted into the ground upside down. They had a unique design and stood up to several hundreds of meters in height.

At this time, various small, black spaceships with dimly sparkling sapphire-like lights were flying out of these plates continuously.

Black Mechs slowly rose from the ground, ready to storm the frontline.

At the bottom of the building, an outdoor balcony protruded from part of the building. Two young men in white uniforms were standing together at this moment.

“The Shining Mechs that were deployed by White Light have emerged in the battle zone. Their purpose is very obvious, charging straight into the radiation belt,” said a white long-haired man with glasses. He had a slender figure and a gentle temperament.

He was an emergency responder of the Blackboard Special Operation Team and a member of the team that was dedicated to assisting Red-Eyed Medero.

“What is the intention of Master Medero?” another woman with short red hair and a provocative look randomly asked as she stood by his side and scratched her short hair.

“If Master Phoebe can free up her hands and make a sudden attack while His Highness Red Whale and the other party’s Great Light Mech are wounded at the same time…” the man said in a low voice.

“Their purpose is very obvious. It is the forbidden core that escaped from the sewers,” the woman nodded. “So, Master Phoebe had already begun the chase. At the same time, most of our special teams have been dispatched. I was specifically left behind to exchange information and contact with you.”

“You all have a specific position of the core?” the man was stunned.

“There may be some clues,” the woman replied. “Three minutes ago, Master had contacted once saying that they would be arriving at the target location.”

“That’s great,” the man smiled.

************

Somewhere in the vast grasslands of the radiation belt

Jade-white shuttle-looking battleships slowly took off; some from the ground while some directly emerged from the underground.

Groups of flying spaceships like flew up like white bees from the ground and rushed out of the clouds. They flew straight towards the sky, appearing like an inverted rain.

Boom!

In the midst of such an overwhelming army, a jade-white humanoid Mech with horns slowly descended and looked up at the magnificent skies around him.

“Found the place where the core is. Boss asks you to go in person,” a voice came from behind the Mech.

“Understood. Boss was severely injured in the battle with Red Whale. Now is the time for us to shine,” Red Jade Horn Mech responded. It was a calm voice of a woman.

“Maria will send someone to assist you. Rest assured, with their traction light, you can always jump off and leave,” whispered that voice.

“Huh! These hypocritical people of the inner region only dare to move out in the name of our White Light,” Red Jade Horn sneered. Blue flames spewed out behind her and she flew into the distance.

“Twin Pole has already gone ahead. This time the problem should be easy to manage. Red Bud, you should go too. Be sure to stall the guys from Blackboard. The forbidden core must fall into our hands. Be careful not to be found out by Royal’s side. The motive of the people from Royal Academy is not that simple…” the voice whispered.

“Understood.” two white fighter jets took off slowly and chased after Red Jade Horn.

“If possible, kill all observers except for the core. The information must be contained and prevented from spreading out.”

*******************

Somewhere else on the grasslands of the radiation belt

In a grassy village that looked like a grey spot, an old and rusted large-size Mech stood in the center of the village. It was surrounded by a variety of shabby and crude-looking cabins and buildings. They were built in the simplest ways using obsolete cement.

Between the buildings, figures wearing dilapidated clothes came out one after another. There were men and women, young and old. All of them were all pale and they had rough skin. Some were leaning against their doors, watching the outsiders who were entering the village.

Some of them sat at the front door and kept grinding their knives. Their eyes followed the outsiders. Even the children who were playing were holding dead scorpions and dead snakes in their hands, their eyes staring at the team.

Clint and the group slowly followed the convoy and walked through the village, constantly feeling the hairs all over their bodies stand up as they were stared at by these people.

The entire convoy of more than a dozen people each looked relaxed. But beneath that, the atmosphere was much more nervous than usual, forming a condition in which the external appeared calm while the internal was on edge.

“Anyone in the village may take your life at any time. Everyone wants a better life, better food, better water and more beautiful women. These are the guarantee and the premium resources for a village to continue to prosper,” one of the big sisters named Wu Dan whispered to Clint and Baylon, explaining some information to be kept in mind.

“What do their need of resources have anything to do with us?” Clint asked innocently.

“Because it is lawless in the radiation belt. The strong are respected, and whatever you want requires power. This kind of power does not rely solely on capability but also here,” Big Sister pointed to her own head.

Looking at the crowd with their staring eyes filled with defensiveness and greed, Clint’s heart felt unbearably oppressed.

If he had not come out and had a look in person, he would not have thought that there was such a cruel world outside of the region.

“If there really is no food, even human flesh is often eaten. As such, the population is not just a good use of labor and reproduction tool but also as food stocks,” big sister Wu Dan said lightly. “So even if you guys have nothing and are going to starve to death, you must be careful of a good-hearted person who offers you a meal. This is because your flesh and bones may be viewed as resources in their eyes.”

Baylon covered her mouth, feeling nauseous.

Clint also felt repulsed, goosebumps raising all over his body.

“This is the radiation belt. For many years, there have not been any changes regardless of which planet it is,” Red Moon’s voice sounded in his mind. “Human lives are worthless in the radiation belt. Every day, many people will be killed or wounded; killed for revenge, for love, for no reason, or out of loathing. The ordinary people here who are powerless are at risk of death at all times. You guys must be careful. As the activator of the forbidden imprint, the biggest drawback is that without the Mech, you are just an ordinary person and you cannot use Willpower,” he cautioned.

“Isn’t there still strength?” Clint tightened his fist.

“It’s useless. No one will fight with you on the front. Here, just a bit of poison could knock you to the ground. Poison is the most abundant thing in the radiation belt,” Red Moon said coldly.

Looking at these villagers’ eyes, Clint suddenly felt a fear of solitary and helplessness. Unconsciously, he clung to Baylon’s little hand and the two were walking closer and closer to each other.

Wu Dan smiled slightly at the sight of this and did not say anything more. The original second team leader had died on this trip. However, she had not expected to acquire two little guys coming from the region. It was a pleasant surprise. If she could get all kinds of useful knowledge and intelligence about the inside of the region from them as much as possible, then it would also be of a great help to the team.

The convoy had now slowly driven to the front of a cabin with a dome. Wu Dan got out of the car, took out the key and jiggled it in her hand.

“Let’s go. Everybody check the equipment. All those that need to be modified, report them to me!” she raised her voice.

Woo-hoo!!

Everyone in the convoy cheered. The fatigue they felt on the way had suddenly been reduced by half.

“Come, let’s go and have a drink together,” the yellow-bearded uncle patted Clint and Baylon on the shoulder and laughed.

“We… We don’t drink…” Clint’s face reddened and he waved his hand. Baylon hid behind him and didn’t dare to speak up.

“How can you not know how to drink?! Men who do not drink are simply wimps plus idiots!” the yellow bearded uncle chuckled, “Let’s go, let’s go. Come and accompany uncle, I have a good drink!”

“But we really don’t know…”

“How would you know if you don’t drink at all?!”

Clint was dragged into the cabin by Yellow Beard and two other young people.

The cabin looked small from the outside but on the inside, there was an underground passage in the middle of the room. Looking down on the stone steps below, music and laughter could be heard coming out from beneath. It was bustling with noise.

The yellow-bearded uncle tugged Clint and went below.

“Seeing you two guys reminds me of my nephew, who also didn’t know how to drink. But in the end? He also loved this stuff after drinking just a few times!”

“This thing called wine… people who don’t drink can’t understand that kind of feeling. This is the only thing that you can rely on to truly relax and rest in this kind of place,” Yellow Beard brought the two and the rest of the convoy into the underground hall.

Red and green lights shone in the hall. It was a freak dance show with all kinds of beautifully and gorgeously dressed women and bizarrely dressed people everywhere. Some were doing fire-breathing performances; some had fist-sized holes in their earlobes and looked terrifying; some had the word ‘scum’ carved on their faces and weren’t bothered by it. They mocked and jeered at others loudly.

The group of people pushed through the crowd and sat down at the bar. Big Sister was nowhere to be seen. Some of the other team members swarmed in and before long, they had blended into the crowd and were having fun wildly.

Soon, there were only three people, the yellow-bearded uncle, Clint and Baylon.

“Now that we’ve arrived here, we can have a good rest. This is a desert hotel. No one is allowed to start a private fight here. Otherwise, you won’t be giving face to the managing gang of this territory. If you don’t give face to the territory gang, you won’t be able to do anything.”

Pap!

“Same old,” the bartender placed two bright orange-yellow-colored drinks in front of the three of them heavily, nodded at Yellow Beard and turned to handle the other guests.

“Come, drink!” Yellow Beard took one of the mugs and gulped down a big mouthful.

Chapter 870: Resonance Stage 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Clint, on the other hand, went to sniff at it. It seemed to be very fragrant, and smelled like lemons. All of a sudden a large hand reached over, picked up the cup and poured half of the alcohol inside into another empty cup.

“You can’t drink so much on your own, this portion is for the two of you!” Yellow Beard laughed heartily, picking up his own cup again and guzzling it madly.

“Thanks, uncle.”

Clint looked at the cups hesitantly, and reached out his hand to pass one cup to Baylon.

“Are we really going to drink that?” Baylon asked hesitantly.

“Just try a little…” reminded Red Moon softly. “Everything in the radiation belt is very dangerous.”

“Got it.” Clint nodded, and bent down to lick the wine lightly with the tip of his tongue. Instantly, a refreshingly sour, intense taste of alcohol entered his mouth.

Urk…

It was just a little, but his face was already turning red, the things in front of him beginning to sway.

Baylon was even faster. While he was still slightly dizzy, Baylon had simply collapsed onto the bar counter with a thud, and lay there unmoving.

Clint opened his mouth and tried to speak, but his lips felt numb and swollen, and he could barely make any noise at all.

Bam!

He collapsed onto the bar as well.

“Eh?” The yellow bearded uncle looked at them in surprise, and was instantly speechless. “These two kiddos can’t even take that little bit of wine? I’ve been holding back, y’know?”

“You settled it so quickly?” Only then did Big Sister Wu Dan walk to the counter, looking at the two young ones who were passed out. “Them?”

“Too weak, they fell just by tasting some Yellow Lemon,” the yellow bearded uncle shrugged.

Wutan was quite tempted, a hint of struggle flashing through her eyes.

Similarly, the yellow bearded uncle also glanced at her, with a similarly unknown emotion rising in his eyes.

The two of them did not have any ill intentions to begin with, but now, with such a great opportunity…

Wutan clenched her teeth, and turned her head away, reluctance flashing through her eyes.

“Bring them in, Lil’ Four is running out of time, if we have these two…”

Yellow Beard sighed, and glanced at the two young ones.

“Don’t blame us… We had no choice, either.”

He got up and lifted them, one in each arm, before striding towards the small door behind the bar counter.

The bartenders and the other people seemed completely used to it, they had no intention of moving at all.

One of the bartenders glanced at the two young ones who were being carted away.

“Hoho, two fresh ones, one boy and one girl. The girl can be deflowered immediately and sold to the brothel, but the boy is quite a looker too, smooth skin and juicy flesh. Recently there have fewer meat pigs, huh? Such fresh produce is really hard to find now. The last time I had a pie, the meat inside wasn’t all that fresh anymore.” He lit a cigarette and puffed nonchalantly.

“The Boss and the leaders are all here, they should be able to get a good price for that. That woman Wu Dan is going to get rich,” continued the other bouncer with a laugh.

“That’s a matter of luck as well, she walked out and caught two little lambs just like that.”

Clint was picked up and brought away dazedly, but he was not completely out of it, and he had heard their words perfectly clearly. His heart instantly sank.

“The situation’s terrible.” Red Moon’s voice was slightly anxious as well. At first, he had not thought that Clint and Baylon would so inexperienced as to collapse with just a little wine. Wutan and the others did not really have bad intentions to begin with, so he did not really remind them, but now that the two of them were sitting ducks, the situation was going from bad to worse.

“Clint! Clint! Wake up! Wake up now!!” He kept yelling Clint’s name, trying to wake him up. If he had not fallen asleep because he used his power too much consequently before, and now all his power could only barely maintain his consciousness, he would be able to remove the alcohol from Clint’s body right now with the power of the Forbidden Mech.

“I… I…” Clint was barely conscious, but he was as anxious as Red Moon inside. The only problem was that he could not move his body at all.

Red Moon was boiling over with rage as well, he had lost all his powers, and now thanks to one moment’s carelessness, Clint and Baylon were in such a dangerous state. This was really bad.

Clint and Baylon could not use their Willpower at all when they were away from their Mechs. And he did not have any power at all as well right now. If they were not careful, Clint might become the first inheritor of the Forbidden Mech to be easily killed off by normal people.

********************

Blackboard Academy

The Inner Courtyard was a strange and wide underground space. If Garen did not have someone leading him down here, he would not have dreamed that the school’s Inner Courtyard would be a huge empty abyss several thousand meters underground.

Above them was a simulated sky, with a golden sun slowly shining down on the earth. Unlike normal suns, however, there was a metallic silver ring around this golden sun, like a satellite ring.

Looking at the bright scenery outside, Garen pulled back his gaze, and sat quietly in his seat, waiting.

Right now he was sitting in a meeting lounge that was neither big nor small, and there was a black metal table in front of him. The wooden chair behind had a thick black leather cushion on it.

But no one was sitting there right now.

Ker-chak.

The door to the meeting lounge opened.

A wrinkled old man holding a staff walked in slowly, and then, glancing at Garen, sat in the chair behind the table.

The old man wore something like a long white robe, and Garen could vaguely see a line of deep blue code numbers printed on the right of his neck. They looked like tattoos.

“You’re here because that guy Ansader introduced you. We’ll cut the small talk, I’ll teach you properly. But you need to give me something equivalent in exchange. You get that, right?” said the old man mildly.

“Yes.” Garen lowered his head in a sign of respect.

“I, Van Doe, don’t have many rules, but you must strictly obey all of them.” The old man coughed twice, his tone softening. “You have two senior brothers and one senior sister, they are all experts at the Crouched Eagle Talon as well, and you will meet them later. Now, show me your Willpower so I can see your progress, and then I can teach you better as well.”

“I understand, Teacher,” replied Garen respectfully. He could tell that this old man was far from just Level Five. His own internal Nameless Training Method was already at Level Five, but he could not tell how powerful this old man was at all.

Before coming here, he had already investigated Old Man Van Doe’s reputation. In order to protect him, the prodigious elite, as well as due to the fact that he could reach Level Three Willpower in such a short time, Ansader did not treat him lightly. The teacher he recommended was one of the strongest among the Inner Courtyard’s professors. Actually, the academy had very few professors, most of them were strong fighters among the instructors. The title of professor came from a selection among the instructors anyway.

And Van Doe was one of the best of the professors, he rarely revealed his power, so nobody knew if he was really only at Level Five. Most believed that he had already long surpassed Level Five. There was a large gap between Levels Five and Six, unlike the other levels, there was also a long endurance period between these two levels.

The levels could be divided into four, namely New-Moon, Half-Moon, Full-Moon, and Two-Moons. There was a large difference between the four levels as well, because with different resonance degrees, there was a large difference in the amount of resonance power they could unleash. That was why the peak of elite students and the many instructors actually used these four levels to gauge their strength.

The Inherited Level was not that easy to enter, and once someone entered it, they would have basically surpassed the limits of the human body. It was immensely terrifying, the resonance skills released in battle can reach Army Level straight away. Fighting an army with one man, that is the power of the Inherited Level.

And since ancient times, countless prodigies and elites had tried to enter Inherited Level, but less than 1% of them actually made it. Most of the rest could only stay at the Full-Moon Level, and could not go further than that.

Faced with these four levels, humans matched them to resonance data and levels.

Between Levels Five and Six, there was detailed information about Mech resonance, and this information decided that from 10% to 30%, one would be in New-Moon Level. 30% to 50% was Half-Moon, 50% to 90% was Full-Moon, and finally, 90% up to the people endlessly approaching 100%, that was the final Two-Moons Level.

Only those who truly reached 100% could enter the Inherited Level.

Garen was now just dabbling into Level Five, forget resonance Skills, he did not even have any clue about his own Mech. Without a mech of their own, no matter how strong a pilot’s Willpower was, when faced with a true high-level Mech, they would still fall like flies. After all, without the boost of a Mech, the pilot’s own Willpower Energy Field could not even penetrate the opponent Mech’s defense fields.

A victory by using the power of Willpower alone would only appear in battles against low-level Mechs, Mechs that were Level Four and above all had the ability to increase Willpower and form a Willpower Defense Field System.

Garen looked at the geezer who looked like he had one foot in the grave from the corner of his eye.

At the same time, he slowly emitted his Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower.

“Definitely not a regular Level Five, New-Moon, Half-Moon, Full-Moon, Two-Moons, I wonder what level this old man actually is,” he hazarded guesses inwardly. Unfortunately, once he reached Level Five, it was not so easy to advance anymore just by practicing training methods. Most importantly, he needed his own Mech, only then could he continue to progress. So he had no frame of reference for anything higher than that.

Van Doe half-closed his eyes,as though resting, but also as though he was carefully sensing Garen’s Willpower.

After a long while, he finally spoke.

“Not bad, not bad indeed. No wonder that old boy Ansader recommended you to me so seriously. Level Four Crouched Eagle Talon, and you seem to be practicing another training method as well. You truly have great talent to reach such a level at such a young age.”

He said that, but he did not look very happy at all.

“However, it seems that you did not train your Willpower the normal way. Instead, it looks like you used some external force to forcefully raise it. Although you tried to fix your basics later, you still have too many holes. Once you enter a battle of Willpower, in the long run, you’ll be in trouble.”

Garen’s heart gave a jolt. Although he already had a very high opinion of this old man, he never thought that he could come up with so much in such a short time.

“I don’t know how you forcefully upgraded it. There are many ways, and although all of them can only be encountered by luck, that’s still your luck, and not that of others.” The old man took out a gold-rimmed pipe, put some tobacco into it, and snapped his fingers. He actually managed to light a spark in the air, and used it to light his pipe.

“That’s why you don’t have to worry that I’ll reveal your secret,” Van Doe said calmly. “I am always fair to my disciples, but I’m also very strict. If you do not reach my requirements, then do not blame me for not showing you face. After all, your true talents are only slightly below-average, the chances of you making a breakthrough in resonance are minuscule at best.”

Only then did Garen understand why the old man showed no fondness for him even after knowing his level.

“Sixty years ago, I accepted a student just like you, he reached a high level of Willpower at a very young age. But when it came to the hurdle of resonance, he spent eighty years before he could just barely make it to New-Moon Level. So my suggestion to you is that you should gather more wealth and equipment now, a good Mech will be very helpful to you in increasing your resonance as well. Although your natural talent is terrible, with a good enough Mech, you might still be able to advance at an average speed. Do not be too disappointed,” Van Doe comforted him.

“I understand, Teacher.”Garen was slightly relieved, the old man still could not sense his hidden internal Level Five Willpower, that meant that the training method the Forbidden Core gave him was still high enough in level, and mysterious enough to fool him.

Chapter 871: Fila 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As for resonance degrees, or several years of painful endurance, he did not truly believe that he would be held back for so long without breaking through.

Since he had the Nameless Training Method, his own side-project– the Hellfrost Peacock Technique, and even the help of his potential points, he did not believe he would be stuck there.

Van Doe looked at Garen, and seemed to have noticed how he did not appear to believe it.

“But that’s fine, Level Four Willpower is enough for you to get some things done already. You can accept missions only elite students can take, to earn credits and Quest Points. Those can be used to exchange for skills or ingredients you require.”

“I understand.”

“Good.” Van Doe took a small white item from his drawer, and tossed it casually. It fell right in front of Garen, who caught it precisely.

“That’s your Elite ID Tag, make sure you don’t lose it. The competition between elite students is a lot crueler than you imagine. There is no name on the tag, so if it was taken away, you would lose your status as an elite. If you don’t get it back within a month, you will be chased out of the Inner Courtyard.”

“Chased out of the Inner Courtyard…” Garen had not known about that rule.

“You know the three most important professors of the Inner Courtyard, they’re the principal and vice principals. They don’t have many students, but all their students are very powerful, even the weakest is at Half-Moon Level. Don’t provoke them. Other than that there are students of the Inherited Level instructors and professors, Red Whale and Rain Veil. Just make sure you don’t get on their bad side. The others are fine, you can treat them however you like. Of course, on the condition that you can beat them.” Van Doe picked up his pipe and took a sharp puff of it. “The rules of the Inner Courtyard state that you can hurt each other during battles normally, but you can’t kill anyone.”

“I understand.”

Garen replied respectfully.

“Well, now you’ve understood the gist of it. Every five days, I’ll have a lecture about the Crouched Eagle Talon, and your senior brothers and sister will rush back for it too. When they come back, you can meet them. For now, leave,” Van Doe chased him away.

“Yes.”

Garen lowered his head and retreated out of the room.

The huge space inside the Inner Courtyard was just like the real world.

There was a bright and dazzling sun in the sky, as well as orderly streets and rows of properly-arranged buildings of different heights. He could vaguely see the yellow and white lines marking the grey roads between the buildings.

The flow of traffic and pedestrians moved at different speeds down the roads.

Compared to outside, however, it was much quieter in here.

Coming out from Professor Van Doe’s house, Garen lifted his hand and glanced at his wristwatch. He had received some messages just now, but he had temporarily turned it to Silent, so he had just felt a slight vibration.

The Caller ID on the watch indicated that it was Celine.

“How’s it? How does it feel to enter the Inner Courtyard?”

“I don’t feel anything in particular. This place is very large, it looks just like another separate reality. The surroundings they created here are very realistic,” said Garen as he casually walked towards one of the streets.

After walking for some time, he found a spot, and sat down on a long bench. The bench was at the crossroads, so it was close to the point of highest traffic.

Garen talked to Celine disinterestedly while he observed the passersby here nonchalantly.

“As expected of the Inner Courtyard, any random stranger just walking around here has Level Two Willpower at the very least. On average, most of the people here are at Level Three,” sighed Garen, his eyes fixed on the people walking past him.

“Of course, the monsters in the Inner Courtyard are all the elites of the elites, carefully chosen every year. Even the two of us did not make it in the beginning,” Celine chuckled. “At first I was making preparations too, to get into the Inner Courtyard beforehand, but I never thought you would be so far ahead of me. As expected of someone with military credit, I’m starting to wonder if I should go and get some for myself.”

“Go ahead, your powers are pretty much there. Just go and patrol somewhere, catch some terrorists a few times, and it won’t be hard for you to create some military credit,” said Garen approvingly. “Now that the White Light has declared war, many terrorists in the area are just raring to go. It’s the best chance for you guys to make a name for yourselves.”

“True. I feel like I’m going to breakthrough my level soon. It should be this month or next, then I’ll be in Level Three too,” said Celine very frankly.

“Congratulations.” Garen felt speechless. If he did not have the help of the secret techniques and potential points, there was no way he could have reached Level Three so quickly. Celine truly was a real peak-level prodigy, she was already on the verge of Level Three just like that.

“After a while, we plan to work together to buy some Lamda Alloy, you interested?”

“Lamda Alloy?” Garen knew about that, it was a main material used in creating high-level Mechs, its specs were very good in all aspects. It was one of the best materials to make close-range Mechs.

“Yeah, we gotta start prepping now, right? The most basic materials for making Mechs, engine skills, quantum brain skills, and kinetic frames, those are the four most important foundations. These things are definitely resources required for battle strategies, don’t even think about finding them lying about the market. Even on the black market, you could only buy a bit of these for a ridiculous price. At the most, they can only be used for repairs. If you really wanted to get some, you needed to barter through your connections. If you’re interested, you can start buying with us as well, I’ll put your name in, it’s on me.”

“Is that okay?” Garen knew that the inner circles of Celine’s main family branch had some of the quota on these precious skills and materials. If he added his name to Celine’s, that meant he was taking away her already-limited Mech quota.

“It’s fine, it’s all thanks to you that my ranking could rise, you’re my teacher, y’know!” Celine chortled. This girl, she looked pretty good, and had a good body too, but that laugh… was even manlier than a man’s, completely carefree and with none of a girl’s self-awareness.

“Well, okay then.” Garen felt slightly guilty. The last time they intercepted the White Light’s Shining Mech, Red-White, Celine had not gotten any benefits from it at all. She had taken such a huge risk for nothing, and now he had to rely on her again.

But right now he really did not have channels to buy rare materials, perhaps he should look around the Blue Narcissus’ place, apparently they had channels especially for this. Only he did not know if he could buy such high-grade stuff.

Actually, Garen did not harbor many hopes, If it was that easy to obtain, Celine would not try so hard to find any channel. After all, it was a simple matter to get a member of Blue Narcissus to buy something for her.

“Okay, then you send someone over. I’ll get someone from this side to meet you,” Celine said shortly.

“I’ll send Kendall over to discuss with your man, as for the general details…” Garen’s voice stopped suddenly, his gaze sweeping over a slightly familiar figure, and his eyes abruptly narrowing.

That was a woman’s figure, long and slender, with some very long legs by proportion. She wore black leather clothes, her long golden hair let loose over her shoulder. She had curves in all the right places, and gave off an intensely sexy, well-trained aura.

This woman walked out from a convenience store on the street, holding a plastic bag in her hand, with some vegetables and fruits in it. Yawning, she walked towards a large black bike by the roadside.

“…I’ll call you back later, something urgent’s come up,” said Garen to his watch, and then he cut the connection. Standing up, he strode straight towards the woman.

But his gaze was trained on a small alley beside the woman, as though he was a passerby who wanted to walk into the alley.

The woman turned around, glanced at him, and yawned again. Her eyes were the perfect peach-blossom almond-shape, her pupils were scarlet red and very beautiful.

“It’s her!”

Garen had already remembered, this woman was that person dressed in black who had suddenly barged into his hospital room, back when he had first come to this world and was grievously injured. Her eyes, and her basically unchanged body proportions, all immediately reminded him of the situation back there.

This was the woman who nearly ruined this body’s eyes, and even worse, she nearly destroyed one of his Soul Seeds when he just arrived in this world.

Back then Garen had already decided that he would definitely find her again, and repay her properly for what she had done. However, he had never found her again, until he just stumbled into her in the Inner Courtyard.

The blonde-haired, red-eyed woman looked to be no older than twenty. Right now, she had none of the sharp edge she had back then, she just looked like a regular beauty who was extremely mentally tired.

She gave Garen a strange look, and put the bag into the bike’s carrier at the back. Lifting one of her long legs, she got onto the heavy-duty bike.

With a ‘vroom’, the engine kicked into gear. The bike moved slowly, and was getting ready to take off.

Just then, Garen reached less than a meter away from her, and reached out his hand abruptly.

Psst!!

His hand, arched like a claw, seemed to tear through the wind, making a hissing sound as it grabbed for the woman’s weakest area, her neck. With this claw, Garen had used 30% of his power. If a regular person was grabbed by him like that, they would surely be unable to resist. All the power in their bodies would be jolted away, and they would be helpless. If they tried to resist him face-on, with Garen’s vitality and strength, even regular weapons would not be able to block this move of his. As long as they were not peak-level weapons, stuff like blades would just be broken in half.

This grab was evidently completely out of the woman’s expectations, both her hands were on the motorcycle handlebars, and it was too late for her to react when she saw his claw coming.

“You!!”

Her pupils dilated abruptly.

Boom!!

A transparent jolt exploded around her.

The huge force sent both the woman and Garen flying. The heavy-duty bike was sent flying diagonally, and crashed hard into a wall, making a dull thud.

The woman was evidently fine, and she began to run as soon as she got up. In her hand, she held a small item like a white jade, and it was still dimming slightly. Evidently, it was the source of that explosion just now.

Turning around and glancing at Garen, she saw that he was getting up from the ground, completely unharmed. The woman’s heart grew colder.

“He’s fine!? He took a hit from my Heavenly Water Blast and he’s completely fine! You gotta be kidding me…”

She said nothing else, but ran even faster.

Garen shook his head, the impact just now was equivalent to a small hand grenade. But with his terrifying Vitality stat, that was nearly at five points, and the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s automatic Frost Protection, not a hair on his head was harmed.

Still, he could not block the force of the impact, and was sent flying.

Looking up, he saw that the woman had run quite a distance. He snorted coldly, and began to give chase.

“Trying to run, are you!”

Within a few seconds, Garen was already no more than several meters behind the woman. He reached out his large hand, and grabbed at her abruptly.

Psst!

A white laser shot past Garen’s claw. It landed on the wall but did not leave any mark except for a wisp of black smoke.

“Stop!”

A young man in a black suit rushed over, and he was somehow running at the same speed as Garen. Facing Garen, he smashed his forearm at Garen’s head. Strangely, his forearm had bolts of blue lightning coming from it, giving Garen a sense of immense threat.

Chapter 872: Fila 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen turned over, and pushed his opponent’s elbow with the shoe. With a thump, he used the strength from his opponent and moved back a few steps, staring at this man who suddenly appeared.

“What’s wrong? No one said that it’s not alright to seek revenge between Elite Students, did they?”

“I don’t care if you’re seeking for revenge, but blatant use of Range Blasting Weapons on the streets is a violation of rules!” The man stared coldly at Garen. “Let’s go, come with me to the Administrative Bureau!”

“The Administrative Bureau?” Garen knew that the Administrative Bureau was the department in charge of the Inner Courtyard’s security. What he didn’t know was that he would be meeting them under these circumstances.

“Come with me!” The man reached out to grab onto Garen’s arm as sparks danced on the tip of his fingers. “It would be an assault if you resist. If you don’t want to be jailed up for about a year, you better be honest with me!”

“It was that woman there, just now, who used the Blasting Weapon. Surely you can’t blame me for that?” Garen argued.

“I don’t care. You’re the one with the biggest threat here.” The man did not bother, grabbing Garen by the arm.

How could Garen submit to an arrest like that? So with one step back, he dodged.

The man closed in with every step, but Garen continued to dodge. The both of them twisted and turned like a game of catch. In a short few seconds, they had exchanged more than ten moves.

“Many thanks, brother!”

From the distance, he heard a woman’s voice thanking him.

Garen’s face sunk. He instantly knew that this man was on her side. But as he looked at the shield of the Administrative Bureau’s on his arm, and he was indeed a real Police Officer. However, the Administrative Bureau here was not like the officers from other places, who were merely laypeople with the strength of Level One or Two. These team of officers was formed with the Inner Courtyard’s Elite Students. Most often, these officers would possess the quality of Level Two or Three. There were many masters of Level Four and Five as well, but more so, there were also masters of the New-Moon Level and Half-Moon Level.

He suddenly had a plan. As he took a step forward, he crossed over from the side of the man, like a phantom, and quickly chased after the woman.

“How dare you resist arrest!” The man’s eyes widened. This was the first time some had escaped from him so easily.

Though unfortunately, when Garen showed revealed his true strength, his speed was much faster than the man’s. In a few steps, he had caught up with her, few meters behind.

“At first, you almost killed me in the hospital. It was hard enough catching you this time, and you think you could escape?” Garen said with a straight face.

Only then did the woman recalled what was going on here, her eyes revealed a fierce stare.

“If I would have known, I would’ve gotten rid you little bastard!” She gritted her teeth, but she did not stop in steps. From the fleeting exchange they had a moment ago, she felt that her opponent’s close combat skills far exceeded hers.

If he was caught, he would be facing a situation with only death involved.

“If you knew? If that is just mere empty talk, then you will die here today!”

Before he could finish his last word, Garen fiercely rushed forward in a ghost-like manner. His palm was directed towards the woman’s chest.

No wind, nor whistling sound could be heard from the punch, only a black shadow flashed past. The heart of Garen’s palm was almost touching the back of the woman’s leather clothes.

As if she could feel a chill running down her back, she felt a strong dangerous instinct that enveloped her whole body. From the reflective mirror that was on the street in front of her, she could clearly see Garen’s movements behind her.

Immediately, her scalp went numb, and she knew she was in trouble.

Bang!

A wave of blast once again exploded around her as she violently shook away the palm that Garen hit her chest with.

“Brother, save me please!” She screamed out loud.

The blast wave shook Garen back for a few steps, but the same moves didn’t affect him much. He too had prepared for this explosion and that’s why he wasn’t blasted too far away. As he took a step forwards, he rushed towards her again.

Whereas it was a different case for the woman herself — she was blasted dizzy. After that, she slowly struggled to stand up.

Bang bang!

Suddenly, a pair of arms with electricity fiercely grabbed into Garen’s shoulders.

“I’ve caught you!” All these while, that Administrative Bureau man was taking the opportunity to catch him. It was unclear what tricks he used, but there was not a single sound was made as he was pressed onto Garen’s shoulders.

He then looked at the woman who was getting up, and a harsh look flashed across his eyes. When his knee jerked and slammed onto Garen’s vest, the area that was hit formed a black spark of electricity. This was the explosive current that came from the Traceless Personal Mech that he wore. Usually, it is only used for capturing criminals with heavy crimes. No matter how strong his body was, this hit would have given any other Mechs a huge hole, let alone a human. The metal would have made him physically disabled!

Seeing as his favorite junior was forced into a corner by this guy, he was immediately enraged. With one knee, he fiercely smashed it forwards.

At the same time, his Level Four Willpower rushed forward with a loud crash.

Spike!

For a moment, the Willpower turned into a sharp prick that was stabbing towards the back of Garen’s brain.

Sensing danger, Garen’s expression turned cold. His body was suddenly startled, and he broke free from the opponent’s grip. His body twisted and turned. In the end, he escaped the Willpower’s stab and punched the guy with his backhand.

“How are you assault me!” The man yelled.

Swosh!

The punch was a meter away from his face, and it stopped there. It scared him until he started sweating profusely.

Garen lifted his head to look at the monitoring camera that was placed on the top of the corner of the street. He let out a cold snot. He could say that he was seeking revenge when he was chasing the girl before this because that was still within the rules of the Inner Courtyard. However, if he had hit this Administrative Bureau’s officer, then he would have committed a crime.

Garen glared coldly at the sluggish man, turned around, and quickly chased after the woman. Unless his Willpower far exceeded his Level, then if not, there would not have been a Mech Pilot in this Mech. In his eyes, that was good-for-nothing; there was no difference between him and a normal person.

The man touched the wrinkle on his face that was agitated by the strong winds. He was lifeless for while, but then he roared out loud. From his waist, he pulled out a Laser Cannon and aimed it towards Garen’s vest.

“Die!”

Chi!

This time wasn’t the same as the safe white laser before, its effects weren’t much. This time, the laser carried a tint of silver, as if it immediately hit Garen’s vest the moment it shot out.

This was not the Authoritative Bureau’s standard Laser Cannon. Instead, it was the man’s own High-Energy Destruction Gun. This was an individual combat weapon that would only be used to tackle small battleships! It can even penetrate through armored alloyed plates.

The silver laser was like a silver line that was behind Garen in an instant.

In a flash, a strong sense of danger crept into his mind. There was no time for him to turn around, and so, his left foot took a step to the right.

Bang!

His whole body suddenly tilted and turned around to face the side, maintaining his standing position. At the same time, a powerful radiating field violently spread, and distorted the air density around the body for a moment.

Hiss!

It was a close call, but the silver laser did not hit the vest after all. Instead, from Garen’s back, it slanted slightly downwards and brushed outwards, away from him. It hit a rubbish bin not far from where they were, and penetrated in. Nobody knew how far down the ground it went.

However, Garen’s back was dug out by the laser, giving him a bloody wound. A red line stretched vertically across his back. His blood was dripping down, wetting the edges of the shirt that was burnt.

Garen grunted, as his muscles relaxed. It was activated in one second and then relaxed the next automatically, just like a worm that was trying to wriggle its way. Under his skin, the muscles naturally goes through peristalsis to replenish the blood from the wound. Once it recovers, just like closing a door, the wound would close into a red scar.

This terrifying individual combat weapon was not designed to oppose human, it was designed to attack battleships!

Even though he was proud of his physique, he was vulnerable under these weapons.

Although he avoided a fatal blow, just because of the blasting force that erupted when he was trying to dodge, Garen tumbled hard and fell on top of the rubbish bin.

With a bang, a rolled down from the top of the bin. He leaped down immediately with the help of one hand.

He did not chase after the woman. He lifted his hand, feeling as if he broke something. However, he quickly turned around and dashed towards the Authoritative Bureau’s man who was behind him.

That man’s face was evil. To one’s surprise, he still wanted to continue to fire, but before he could aim, he saw Garen’s distorted wondering. His figure was traveling in a completely irregular pattern as he rushed forward. A claw was silently directed towards his neck.

At that moment, the shadow of death loomed upon him.

A hint of fear finally surfaced on the man’s face. However, as it was already night time, the claw was almost at his neck. He could feel the sharp nails already on the skin of his neck.

Boom!

At this moment, a huge surge of Willpower suddenly rushed in from the side. It was as if this entire street was distorted with Willpower; even the light in the air was vibrating slightly.

The impact of the huge surge of Willpower was transparent and colorless. As it formed into a snake-like shape, it coldly rushed towards Garen’s presence.

The impact of the giant snake’s Willpower was quite fast. It was even faster than all the pilots that Garen has ever witnessed. That speed was instantaneous. The next moment, it was in front of him.

As Garen lifted his eyes, it seemed like everything had slowed down. His frantic Level Five Willpower in his body was aroused with a crazy sympathetic response. It wanted to broke out to defend this terrifying Willpower.

But in the end, he did not make it.

Rumble!

A loud noise echoed in his brain, causing Garen’s whole body to roll out, and was pushed away.

This surge of Willpower was exceeding Level Five, and it had achieved a strange degree of change. Even though the impact was from afar, all of Garen’s defenses on the surface of his body was instantly shattered. It was as if his body was attacked by a baseball that was shot at a high speed.

At this moment, not only did Garen’s wound that was just healed burst out with blood, all the organs in his body felt as if an invisible hand was squeezing them hard at the same time. It was like it wanted to tear all of it to shreds.

That surge of terrifying giant snake Willpower suddenly broke through his defense, and went into his body, wanting to tear all his organs in his body.

Ouch!

He couldn’t control it as he spat out a mouth full of black blood. Garen’s vision went black. This opponent’s aim was to kill him after all, not leaving any chance for mercy. If it was any other Pilot, the ones without the right physique would definitely die!

Without the slightest hesitation, Garen held onto the heavy damages on his body. After he was pushed outwards, you used a similar technique like the Gecko Wall technique the moment he was about to hit the wall. As he slid towards the wall, he channeled it into an upward momentum, and with a few movements, he disappeared on the wall.

From a distance, he heard the Authoritative Bureau’s man’s voice shout in surprise.

“Captain Fila!”

“Fila!”

Garen remembered this name while he moved at an accelerating speed. He bore the horrible pull of Willpower in his organs, and head towards his Inner Courtyard’s Master’s place.

The places where the major professors were, in the Inner Courtyard, absolutely did not allow fights. Between Elite Students, they were not allowed to kill each other. At most, it could only cause them injuries, but the rules were the rules. With the cruel and evil personalities of each Elite Students, as long as it was a non-monitored area, killing duels of sorts would often happen. There were even people who would use an aircraft to bombard and kill. Just as long as they weren’t caught, it would be fine.

This was also the reason why the Authoritative Bureau man was carrying with him a High-Energy Destruction Gun.

Chapter 873: Resonance Degrees 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the alley, a young man wearing grey army uniform walked in. He took a look at the girl on the floor, and then another look at the Authoritative Bureau man by his side who was scared from the shock. In the end, his eyes fell upon the monitoring camera on the wall that was broken by something. That was the camera that Garen smashed just now.

“You two are useless! You couldn’t get rid of the new student even with the Destruction Gun.”

He wore a thick greyish-black cloak on this back. The cloak wasn’t long, it just completely covered his entire back. On the top, it was as if it was animal fur; it shone in a glossy luster. A blood colored sword pattern in the center was wrapped between two concentric circles, making it seem like the blood red color was aiming at the star-shaped pattern, and giving off a luxurious and mysterious feeling.

“Brother Fila! He… That guy before this! He wanted to kill me!” At that moment, the Authoritative Bureau’s man’s face became pale as he cried out loud. In that split second just now, he almost thought he was going to die. That terrifying claw did not give him the chance the react. Even if his Level Four Willpower had greatly improved his response speed and strength, he still would not be able to defend himself under that claw.

“Goldfish,” Fila ignored him. Instead, he looked at the woman on the floor, “if it wasn’t for your brother, I would not even be bothered with your personal enmity.” There wasn’t a single hint of warmth and emotion in his eyes. It was as if he was a real snake, even his pupils were vertical.

“Thank you, Senior Fila,” Goldfish seemed a little afraid of this man as she stood up and answered with her head down, and low voice. Her body was also shaking a little, uncontrollably. Her eyes glanced at the formal clothes in which Fila was wearing. Her heart was pumping.

Fila was ranked as the best expert under Red-Eyed Medero. In the whole of the Inner Courtyard, he ranked fifth. Although he was a level lower compared to Red Eyes’ and others’ Full-Moon Level, for an average student, he was far more powerful than the top three of the preparatory three.

The reason was that his character was always the same, neither happy nor angry. He was just moody.

Yet in his formal clothes, it was obvious that he was prepared to attend a formal ceremony. So she was the one who ruined his mood… Although this account did not seem like a big deal, Fila would definitely make her brother remember this!

Only then did Goldfish felt a cold breeze. Fila’s greed was infamous throughout the Inner Courtyard. Almost everyone who had dealt with him has suffered.

This time, she really hated that new guy that attacked her so much, that she gnashed her teeth. However, she could imagine that her brother might not have known how much it would cost to settle this Fila.

The Authoritative Bureau man suddenly thought of that as well, and his face became darker.

———————–

Slowly walking into the small courtyard of Professor Van Doe’s villa, Garen lifted his head to let the detection device core scan his pupil.

“Poor Student Nono, you look like you’re suffering from a serious injury. Do you need me to arrange a treatment for you?” The villa’s detection device had the sharp voice of a middle-aged man. It was this villa’s central management intelligence — Hill.

“No need. I will not fall for your poor quality drugs,” Garen laughed as if he had no injuries, and then he slowly entered the front courtyard. However, his pale face still could not hide the huge amount of energy he lost.

The strong Willpower was still tormenting his body. If it wasn’t for this physique, that was stronger than most people, there was no way he could have defended himself from the pulling of that Willpower.

The Level Five unknown Willpower was constantly resisting the remnants of the opponent’s Willpower. But it was obvious that their levels were very far apart, as if with one touch and he would collapse.

“Why are you calling it poor quality drugs? The injury in your body is an invasion of Willpower, and it is not an ordinary trick; it is a Half-Moon Level Master’s Willpower. More so, it is one of those who is about to break through,” Hill giggled. “You really don’t need my help? If you’re not careful, do you know this is a fatal injury?”

As a Knowledge Core, he was not any other normal intelligence. Instead, he used to be a human. Furthermore, he was an experiment that surprisingly survived in Van Doe’s experiment. His memories were washed away, but he became the biochemical brain that manages this place.

Over hundreds of years, it probably had seen many Students that had High Level Willpower invade their bodies. With this kind of injury, there usually isn’t any professional expelling devices. Only a small number of students were able to make the medicine using their own secret medicine. Without drug assistance, most of them would either end up disabled, or helpless because of the dysfunction of the internal organs.

When Garen came here, the first thing he did was understand the various commodity price lists provided by this intelligence. With comparison to the price out there, this was simply the world’s top profiteer. Originally, the prices in the Inner Courtyard had to be twice as expensive as the outside world. However, the prices in here were double the price of the Inner Courtyard’s which was absolutely a death trap.

Listening to Hill’s grumbling behind his back, Garen walked back to his room as if nothing had happened. As a Student of Van Doe, he had to pay a learning fee of one million Universal Units every year. At the same time, he had to assist the Professor by carrying out at last three experimental jobs. What he got in return was a shelter from the Professor, as well as the rights to purchase special goods that are not available elsewhere.

One should know that even though Hill was greedy, he still had good things that could not be bought elsewhere. Many of them were Hill’s private stuff.

Moreover, another benefit he had was having a small room for him to live in.

As he entered the room, the walls of the bedroom were white. There was a bed, a chair, a table with a lamp, and nothing else.

Garen shut the door, and it gave a beep-like sound of the door locking.

Only then did he let out a harsh breath. The wound on his back was burning with pain, and his internal organs were still entangled with his Willpower. However, this Willpower given by the Forbidden Core, Red Moon seemed to be very powerful. Although the Levels weren’t that far apart, it was still able to hold on for two seconds, unlike the destructiveness of the eagle’s claw Willpower. In this constant consumption, one would be able to constantly use that touch of unrooted Willpower.

“That bastard is amazing,” Garen harshly spit out a breath. This was still him. If it was someone else, their organs would have exploded in the very beginning. There was no way they could have lived.

“Fila…”

From his own suitcase, he took out his tablet and typed quickly. Once he was online, he started searching.

A red virtual keyboard was projected downwards onto the table. Garen quickly extended his hand and a knocking sound of his typing could be heard.

With the knocking sounds of the keyboard, all the information regarding the Inner Courtyard’s Fila quickly appeared.

A photo of a handsome man with a slight trace of blemishes showed up. He was dressed in a military uniform, with the silvery colonel ranking Silver Star sat on both his shoulders.

‘Fila Remington — ranked fifth in the Inner Courtyard, a top talent from the Remington Family. The Chief of the 105th Senior Students of the Inner Courtyard. Age: ? . Captain of the Special Forces in the Inner Courtyard’s Administrative Bureau. Commander-in-Chief of the Third Military Mech Corps of the Military Command. The year of 78, he achieved first in the battle of special pilots between three regions. The year of 52, he achieved third place in the Task Force Competition of the Central Academy. He got a special engine as a reward. He has served as the Director of Central Reporting’s Special Service Department in the Blackboard Region, Vice President of the Hualian Commerce Association, Managing Director of Annier Group…”

Behind that was a series of his various titles.

Garen swept his eyes across that bunch of titles, completely ignore a huge chunk of useless information, and looked at the evaluations at the end.

‘Strength evaluation: Level Five of Half-Moon Level; could break through to Full-Moon Level at any time. As the older group of the Inner Courtyard’s Elite Students, Fila is famous for his Shapeless Snake Training Method. However, he was always suppressed by the top four, causing him to not improve further. He does not make a breakthrough by suppressing his own strength might be because he wanted to lay a better foundation in order for him to defeat the top four experts.

“Half-Moon Level,” Garen sighed. He could feel the Willpower in his body was gradually consumed by his own Level Five nameless Willpower. Only a little of the battling remnants were left, so it should not take much longer until it would be completely gone.

Garen was now much more relaxed.

“No doubt it’s the Support Training Method.” Garen had also searched for anything related to the results of heavy damages caused by Willpower. Under the circumstances of no professional instrumental treatment, or no medicinal assistance, the results were either ending up a disabled person or death. There were no exceptions. Such injury like the bleeding of the arteries, if it is not treated quickly, the end result would be death.

However, this training method given by Red Eyes allowed him to self-repair to defeat foreign Willpower.

It was also his original plan, that if it did not go well, his only choice was for Hill to take a look at him. But now, he had put away most of his worries.

Fila’s name was repeating in his mind. Garen also paid attention to several other of his comprehensive rankings.

In the history of the entire Inner Courtyard, there were 48 people whom he needed to beware of, those Students who had achieved Level Five. Among them, eight people had achieved New-Moon Level, another four had achieved Half-Moon Level, and only three people had achieved Full-Moon Level. However, the surprising thing was that these masters either went to the army or held a position in some other places like Britney who had her name at the top. But in fact, she had left Inner Courtyard at an early age, becoming one of the leaders of the Blue Narcissus.

As for the three candidates of Three Black Rain Generals, they were also in the rankings. Just that they were positioned very far behind. More so, they only had a Level Four of Willpower.

It was obvious that this ranking was old information. Most of the figures above were comprehensive rankings of students who had graduated in the past.

It wasn’t the current ranking of the students in the Inner Courtyard.

Again, Garen carefully searched for current information.

A new list appeared on the screen. Though unfortunately, this list represented the current rankings of the masters of the Inner Courtyard. This made him a little disappointed, but Fila’s name did not exist on this list.

Ranked as the first was Black Star Diofie. Then among three of them ranked after him were Red-Eyed Medero, and he could not recognize the other two men — Karfi and Narisiss.

After the three of them were the three young people, who were known as Black Light, were honored as the future Three Black Rain Generals. However, the three of them only had Level Four of Willpower, not even close to Level Five. At the same time, there were still in the midst of training their Mechs. Though the resonance degree tests were very high, and they had a Half-Moon Level. They were masters with high potential.

Then, it was followed by the masters of Black Light. From the fourth ranking to the fifteenth, there were fifteen people in total. These people had special benefits of calling themselves as the Black Light Reserve. However, there wasn’t a lot of information on that.

This list was much weaker than the ones before, but only a few names could be found on both the lists. Among one of them was Black Star Diofie, and then it was the three of them from the top — Red-Eyed Medero, Karfi, and Narisiss. They were all masters of Full-Moon Level. Another thing Garen accidentally realized was that status of Medero and the other three seemed a little weird. The information on their Willpowers was labeled as Level Four, though it was obvious that it was because of their special training method.

After he finished reading the information, Garen left his tablet aside and stood up. His fingers were constantly messaging his abdomen area, in a special rhythmic way.

“These both sheets of ranking is a little messy. Figures from previous rankings remained on the current list.” He had also heard that Medero had been constantly overlaying and training her Willpower, wanting to break through to the Full-Moon Level, and then into the Double-Moon; she wanted to pace himself with the Black Stars. In fact, she had entered Level Five for quite some years now.

Putting this useless information aside, Garen focused his attention on Fila.

Master of Half-Moon Level. It was needless to say that no matter which rankings, he would be at the front of the top ten masters.

Furthermore, looking at the surprise attack just now, that guy had rich battle experience. The use of his Willpower Field was filled with fire, even his lethality was horrifying.

Coming into this world, Garen had prepared his foundations for situations like this, but this was the first where he was in trouble.

Chapter 874: Resonance Degrees 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The Willpowers of the current students are not that strong. The strongest three only had a Level Four of Willpower even though they have a Full-Moon Level of battle power. So the resonance degrees and the Willpower can be trained separately as two targets. Whereas Red-Eyed Medero and more who suppress their Willpower and increase the resonance degrees must have a special secret.”

Garen analyzed it in his mind.

The current three Elite Students were all on Level Four, but their strengths were terrifyingly unusual. They were the most powerful candidates for the Black Star.

Since Fila was an ex-student who had already graduated, he was not in the current rankings. Nevertheless, that ranking list he was in was done quite a while ago. As a result, it was still unclear what his strengths were.

He reorganized the two lists in his head and combined it into one.

There was no debate that Black Star Diofie would rank first,

Behind him would be Medero and the other two, Fila, Britney and the other ex-masters. These people were ranked differently in different lists as there was no battle. He did not know who was stronger, or weaker than the other. To know their strengths, he would need an insider information to understand.

After that would be the Generals of the Black Star Reserve, followed by many other New-Moon characters.

“The reliability of this ranking is quite high.” Using the compilation of various information that Garen had found, he had arranged it into a list. After all, different websites had different rankings. They also had different views on the strength evaluations of these masters.

The key point was that these masters were top talents. They would improve all the time, and so it was normal for the rankings of their strengths to change very quickly. It was also possible for someone to emerge suddenly as a master.

Garen’s own comprehensive ranking had maintained itself for many years, and the changes weren’t much.

“Fila is actually in the second echelon…” Garen thought about that attack just now — that surge and form of his Willpower, the Shapeless Snake. “Moreover, this is a situation with no Mechs. If he had a Mech, I have no idea how strong his Willpower will get!”

He had to admit that he was a very strong opponent. He was a prominent figure who was on the same level as one of Blue Narcissus’s Higher-Level, Britney. So compared to him, Nonosiva, who had just entered the Inner Courtyard as an Elite Student, their differences weren’t huge.

Garen had not started cultivating his Resonance Degrees. As he did not even have a Mech. there was no need to mention anything about achieving New-Moon or Half-Moon Level.

Sitting with his legs crossed on the bed, he began to sink his Willpower into his body.

The Level Five of nameless Willpower had already removed the Shapeless Snake Willpower in his body. When the Level Five’s strong healing ability played it’s part, along with the five points that were close to his physique, the damages of his internal organs were quickly repaired.

Getting close to the five points were classified as non-human. Even with this injury, his self-healing ability was very terrifying.

Garen’s Willpower could see the slow recovery of the wounds in his organs very clearly. A huge amount of blood was surging in his blood vessels, carrying tons of nutrients to each organ at a high speed.

The wound kept healing at a rate that was visible to the eyes.

“The Willpowers of Level Five Masters with high resonance level, what trick do they use?” While Garen urged his body to heal the wounds, he pondered on that question. Even getting close to the five points of the physique could not defend the impact from the attack of opponent’s Willpower Field.

After his injury was stabilized, he took out his tablet to inquire again. As expected, all the information regarding the resonance degrees were wiped off. There was no trace of the disappearance.

However, the internet in Inner Courtyard was terrifyingly safe. Garen had tried to hack it, but unfortunately, there was no effect.

He might as well gave Celine a call.

“Resonance degrees? I might have heard of this…” Celine was a little surprised. “It is said that it is a high-end thing. If you want to break through to Inherited Level, it won’t happen without a hundred percent of resonance degrees.”

“Regarding how resonance degrees will affect your strength, do you know the specific information?” Garen asked in detail.

“I’m not so sure about that. I can look it up in the family’s internal database for you. Hold on…”

Very quickly, the knocking sound of her typing could be heard.

“I got it! Resonance degrees… Once Level Five of Willpower is achieved, one would have to face a parametric. It is a key index to integrate with a Mech which would greatly improve your combat skills. Specific information… I don’t have enough confidentiality,” Celine got a little annoyed. “I’m sorry, my Level is not enough to look at this information.”

Garen had expected it.

“It’s nothing. After all, you’re only at Level Three of Willpower; you’re not qualified to understand. I’ll ask someone else.”

“Alright…”

After he hung up, Garen called Vivienne. Similarly, she did not even know what resonance degrees were. Compared to Celine, Vivienne’s Willpower only differed in one Level…

Garen put down the phone. Maybe in his contacts, only those rich and nobel guys would know about this. Though it was only a friendship where they exchanged benefits once; they had not crossed to a high-level of friendship yet.

“It seems like I can only ask the professor.” He moved his body, and felt that there was nothing serious in his organs anymore. The rest that still hurt was his vitality, which he needed time to replenish slowly. So, he opened the door and walked out.

He went to the second floor to find Professor Van Doe on the phone in his study room. It seemed like an old friend that he had a good relationship with. From time to time, he could hear laughter coming out from the room. Garen did not even understand the language he was using. It might be a minor language used in the Outer Region.

He waited at the door until the Professor was done with his call. After that, he lightly knocked on the door.

“Enter.”

Professor Van Doe replied in his usual indifferent tone.

Garen pushed open the door and entered.

“Professor.”

“Is there something wrong?” Van Doe lifted his eyes to look at Garen. For a moment, he frowned. “You’re hurt? We will not entertain the clashes between Students. You can only bring your injury upon yourself.”

Garen nodded.

“I hope to understand more information regarding the resonance degrees. I hope Professor can give me some guidance.”

“You understand how weak you are in the Inner Courtyard?” Van Doe’s expression softened. He then pulled out a drawer, took out a file of information, and passed it immediately to Garen. “All the information on resonance degrees are in there. You had to have your own Mech, only then you would be able to cultivate the resonance degrees. This is a key indicator of Level Five and Level Six. If you decide to change Mechs, this parameter must be recultivated. You should do some studying about it.”

“Understood. Thank you, Professor,” Garen nodded his head, and was ready to leave after he took the information.

“This information has a fee of 500 thousand Units. Please remember to reimburse Hill. After you’re done with it, do not leak it. Otherwise, do not look for me if you’re caught,” Van Doe’s voice came from behind him.

Garen had known that this was the result. He replied as he walked out the room, holding the information.

He looked at the information in his hand. It was just a thin piece of paper with a few pages, and that was worth 500 thousand Units… This was the reason why he did not want to look for Professor Van Doe.

In the Inner Courtyard, anything regarding learning came with a hefty fee. The price of anything here was not something that could be afforded by an average person. But relatively speaking, many good things or techniques were available to purchase here — things that one would not be able to find in other places, even top secret knowledge.

Holding onto the information, Garen was directly headed to the Canceling Room which was a place used to destroy things.

From the second floor to the first, it was only a minute walk. In this period of time, Garen had memorized all the information.

He casually disposed the information along with the contents of the Canceling Room, and into the room.

“Resonance degrees… The New-Moon Level’s resonance degrees could improve the pilot’s strength by twenty percent. This increment includes Willpower as well as a simultaneous increase of Mech amplification field. That meant that when there is no Mech, Willpower will increase by twenty percent. However, on the Mech, the increment would be twice the amount, resulting in an amazing forty percent…”

“After that would be Half-Moon Level. The degree of increment would measure up to around forty percent. No wonder that bastard’s Willpower was so terrifying. Originally he was in Level Five. Though after so many years of accumulation and the weight of his Upper position, he must not be lacking in all kinds of resources. With an increment of forty percent…” The information had recorded down some key points. “Achieving Half-Moon Level would be the first step towards using the Mech Integration Agent. During the initial integration, while the Mech and one’s own body goes through some adjustment, it would naturally create a resonance technique.”

“Full-Moon Level would achieve an increment of around sixty percent. Driving the Mech would double the strength, and the resonance technique would gradually improve. The strength would far exceed any other Pilot.”

“Double-Moon Level would achieve an increment of eighty percent and above. Every person’s Double-Moon Level would be different. That is the key to entering the realm of inheritance. One would need to have perfect synchronization with the Mech and their body to finally head towards the perfect goal. The rest is unknown.”

Each section, regarding the resonance degrees, were arranged in his head.

At that moment, Garen felt that his injuries had healed completely. Although it might have looked serious just now, the physique of his Hellfrost Peacock was not generally strong. And even though it was not as tough as top defenses, the powerful self-healing ability of the Hellfrost Peacock had shown its power.

In legends, the Hellfrost Peacock devours innumerable substances in the battle. While bearing the countless attacks and damages, no matter if it was a soul or physical attack, it would be to quickly respond to an enormous body through a terrifying swallow.

Although it is not as strong as combat power, it is one of the dozens of the largest strategic behemoths. As long as it was still alive, the ubiquitous chaos of radiation and coldness could bring endless nightmare to the enemy.

Often times, the outer damage would not even recover as fast as it does inside.

Garen tried to stimulate his Willpower. Both of the Willpower did not leave behind any aftereffect. This was in the state where he did not use the swallowing ability.

“No doubt it is the Hellfrost Peacock Technique…”

“After this, I should carefully consider the problems of the resonance degrees. Only then should I take a look at the differences between the Elites of high resonance degrees and I.”

He straightened out his clothes, and walked out the huge door of the villa.

It was quiet outside; no many people were passing by. In the distance, a small red shuttle-like spacecraft was flying around. Around it, laser cutters were firing out from two black Mechs that were formed into one.

Most of them on the road were young faces. A few stopped to watch, whereas the remaining ones had on an expression as if it was nothing new. They just went on with what they were initially doing.

Bang!

Sometimes, the small aircraft would suddenly land on the ground, and burst into a ball of fire. The wreckage would hit the buildings around. However, it then activates circles of ripples that does not harm the pavement.

The two Mechs in front were hacking each other up for a while. Regardless of the flames, a green-haired girl was pulled out from the wreckage of the aircraft and they flew away.

“This is so destructive…” Garen rubbed his belly as the pain of the pulling of his Willpower was still fresh in his mind. A flash of bright light flashed across his eyes, so he turned around and slowly walked towards that direction.

Chapter 875: Real Inner Courtyard 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Inner Courtyard was made up of three libraries, sixteen training grounds, thirty-six wrestling rings, and the residential houses of numerous professors, instructors, and Elite Students.

It was also a fully Gothic city. The flow of people there and their consumption demands required shops to be built there. The presence of the stores then produced sparse differences in the rate of foot traffic there.

Garen walked a full circle around the periphery of the Inner Courtyard carefully and ensured that his tracks would not be discovered by Fila and the others. There were surveillance cameras everywhere, but most of them had been damaged by other people. The areas that were not covered by cameras were completely covered in traces of fights among students. Blood stains could even be seen on certain walls.

This was the Inner Courtyard, the real Blackboard Academy where the weak were the prey of the strong.

Fighting was prohibited in the department headquarters cum administration building in the center of the area. However, they could fight in the other places that were monitored by the cameras as long as they did not kill others. Meanwhile, no one would care about their actions within the unmonitored areas.

This place prioritized the survival of the fittest and weaklings would be eaten from the first moment they stepped foot inside.

When Garen was walking over, he saw many groups of students that were actually part of organized factions. There were also Mech fights everywhere while Willpower contests resembled frequent fireworks explosions.

He had gained many legitimate benefits after entering the Inner Courtyard, such as specialized training grounds.

These training grounds were equipped with first-class technology that could create battle simulations with any opponent. The entire Inner Courtyard was only able to maintain such great momentum despite cutting themselves off from the outside world because of these ruthless mechanisms.

After Garen had carefully evaded a few brawls and scuffles that were occurring on the streets, he finally arrived at a black rectangular multistoried building.

This building was was perfectly straight and strong, and it stood out from the crowd of silvery white buildings as it looked abnormally eye-catching.

A circle of thin dark-red crystal-like rings was suspended in mid-air around the buildings. They were surprisingly beautiful.

Garen raised his head and admired the power and influence of the rings. He could vaguely feel immense Willpower forces coming from above that were way beyond the abilities of an average person. He felt as if the Willpowers of numerous people were being gathered in one place to form a terrifyingly powerful Energy Field.

There were dried blood stains on the steps in front of the training grounds. There were faint cracks in certain places while it was impossible to form holes in other areas even if they were struck by airborne explosions. He had not expected to see any sign of damage on the steps.

Garen glanced around briefly and noticed two middle-aged people passing him from behind. Without even looking at their surroundings, they took large strides and entered the training grounds before disappearing behind a large pitch black door, as if they had been teleported instantly.

A group of blonde, nonconformist youths walked out of the black door together with solemn looks on their faces and blood stains on the corners of their mouths. If they tied white silk scarves around their heads, they would have looked like the master martial artists portrayed in the daily papers, who had held fatal grudges during the era of the Republic of China.

None of them paid any attention to Garen. Those who entered and left this place would only have either exhausted or solemn expressions on their faces.

The training grounds and library were special benefits for the Elite Students. These were the most important part of the other benefits were for their family members. Although there were monetary allowances, they were never sufficient for the expenses within the Inner Courtyard.

From an outsider’s perspective, the students of the Inner Courtyard received unimaginably large allowances. However, every single one of them was actually extremely poor.

Many students who had reportedly been sacrificed themselves during missions had actually died because of the vicious fighting within the Inner Courtyard.

Garen thought of the things he had seen on the way and the information he had obtained by using his watch to access the internet in the Inner Courtyard. He exhaled firmly.

“This is the real Blackboard Academy…”

He took large strides and walked into the black door.

Bang!!

Moments after he stepped foot inside, he saw a human figure being flung across the room violently. The figure was plastered against the large arch-shaped wall on the left side before it slid down slowly seconds later.

The person who had been sent flying was not that old. He looked to be about twenty years old and was a man with a face full of bruises. His Willpower seemed to be around Level Three.

The attackers who stood on the right side were a group of four to five people. Their leader, who had short black hair and wore black leather gloves, was currently doing wrist exercising movements.

“Anything else you want to say?” Black Gloves asked casually while looking at the young man on the ground. “You weren’t my opponent three years ago, and you’re still completely hopeless three years later.”

The man on the ground tried to crawl up determinedly even though his body looked terribly injured. He had suffered serious internal injuries and could only lie on the ground weakly after numerous attempts to get up.

A few curious onlookers were scattered around the area while Garen stood on the edge and eavesdropped for a while.

The attacker and the victim had once been good friends who had, unfortunately, fallen out after falling in love with the same girl. They had initially planned to use peaceful measures to compete with each other, but their friendship ties were severed at once when the girl had died in an accident while trying to save the current victim of the attack.

Garen stopped and looked for awhile before turning around and walking towards another arch-shaped passage on the left side. That passage was one of the two entrances to the training grounds and rooms.

He had not gone too far along the passage before he saw two males clashing with each other against the wall. Both of them had terrifying looks on their faces while their lips were right next to each other’s ears as if they were whispering something. Suddenly, the male who was pinned against the wall suffered a blow to his stomach and spat blood immediately.

The male who had attacked cast a threatening glance at Garen but remained silent as he continued with his own business.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows; he realized that the chaos here was worse than usual.

After walking further inside for a period of time, he saw a boy and girl who were badly bruised and clad in nothing but their underwear. They were in the middle of a circle of people who were constantly pushing them around. It was clear that they were being bullied.

Garen glanced at the room. The information above stated that the degree of the simulations here could only reach Level Two Willpower. Therefore, they could only simulate opponents with Level Two Willpower. Garen continued to walk deeper.

Along the passage that began to spiral gradually, Garen could see various acts of bullying, fighting, and quarreling happening after a specific distance. If he had forgotten that he had actually entered an Inner Courtyard of Elite Students, Garen would have suspected that he had walked into a completely chaotic fallen city.

People were being robbed, chased, beaten, charged with protection, confronted by other factions, and even raped. Anything that was imaginable could be seen here.

“Save me!” while walking past a group of people, a badly beaten up female student in the middle of a crowd reached her hand towards Garen and begged for help.

Garen could see that she was about to be beaten to death as she was wearing a fifth-year student’s uniform despite only having Level 2 Willpower. Mediocre individuals like herself who did not have any natural talents and possessed lower than Level Three Willpower would always be the easiest bullying targets here.

Ignoring the chaos here, Garen quickened his steps and soon arrived at a place where there were fewer people scattered about.

The information on the doors to the rooms gradually increased to Level Four and Five Willpower simulations before the Resonance Degree divisions slowly appeared after that.

There were very few people entering and leaving this place except for a few whose expressions were advising him not to enter this place. Some of them furrowed their eyebrows lightly when they saw Garen walking inside. However, they remained silent when they felt the Level Four Willpower wafting out of his body.

Willpower forces were the best way to display one’s own identity and level here. There were only a few Elite Students within the Inner Courtyard who had achieved Level Four. Moreover, if they had not achieved their Resonance Degrees, those with Level Four Willpowers could not be compared to regular Level Three’s or Four’s as they were merely middle ranking individuals within the Inner Courtyard.

Garen chose a random room and noticed that most of the rooms here had Level Four Willpower simulation abilities and New-Moon Level Resonance Degrees.

He picked a random room and walked inside.

He moved his hand backward and closed the door firmly. The inside of this room was snow-white and completely empty without any furniture. The floor, walls, and ceiling were completely flat and bright.

‘Welcome to the simulation training grounds. Please choose your fight simulation.’

‘1 — Regular simulation, undergo daily training, consumes 1 Quest Point every hour.’

‘2 — Strengthening simulation, undergo fighting simulations with other students, consumes 10 Quest Points as payment for challenging the opponent.’

‘3 — Vicious simulation, fight a simulation of the current record holder, consumes 20 Quest Points as payment to avenge the record holder.’

‘Rankings will be formed after each challenge according to one’s combat power. These rankings will be integrated within the rankings of the entire Inner Courtyard.’

A cold but neutral computerized voice echoed beside Garen’s ear.

‘Selection method is voice-controlled, please choose.’

“Select simulation 1,” said Garen calmly.

‘Simulation 1, regular, simulated opponent is being formed. Level Four Willpower, New-Moon Level Resonance Degree. Fighting method: bare-handed.’

A distorted transparent figure was gradually formed ten meters in front of Garen. It rose from the ground quickly before parts of its silhouette were speedily formed. A beautiful girl with bountiful, bright red curly hair was formed there.

‘Opponent has been formed. The strongest New-Moon Level competitor in this room with Level Four Willpower, Havana. Fight- begin.’

There was a brief beeping noise.

The red-haired young lady’s gaze was stern when she moved both of her legs at once and leaped forward suddenly like a tiger that was flying over. The cries of a large tiger could be heard around her body vaguely while a transparent, blurry, tiger-shaped Energy Field enveloped her entire body.

Garen leaped forward and countered her with one direct punch.

Boom!!

His fist and her tiger claw clashed with each other, forming a strong cyclone. Their flesh bodies did not come into direct contact but both of their Energy Fields collided with each other directly before forming a whirlwind-like Willpower explosion.

“Tiger Lightning Whip!!” the girl spun around and swung one leg over. Crimson light flashed across her thigh.

Her whip-like leg formed a crimson after image that hit Garen’s left inner arm at once.

There was a quick banging noise and Garen took two steps backward as the tremendous collisions that were far beyond Level Four Willpower crashed against him. His gaze stiffened when he realized that this person was definitely not using normal Training Methods.

It was impossible for his Level Four Crouched Eagle Talons to counter it. He would need to adjust the Level Five components of his body to offset the impact of this Willpower.

Havana began moving quickly as both of her legs swept continuously, each time faster than the last. However, it was obvious that the level of her Vitality was far from Garen’s in close combat. Nonetheless, this girl’s strongest ability was enveloping her body in an Energy Field. She was not afraid of strong collisions and possessed terrifying explosive force.

Garen was always able to block off her attacks during the most important moments. Time passed slowly before his opponent’s rhythm became quicker and more frantic unconsciously.

The thing that shocked Garen the most was that the Willpower inside his body had been shifted to counter his opponent’s speed, which had increased gradually. This involved his Level Four Crouched Eagle Talon and the nameless Level Five Willpower inside his body.

“Faint Resonance Technique: Red Lotus!!”

Suddenly, Havana spun both of her arms as numerous red electric currents appeared around her body. They bloomed instantly like crimson electric flowers and made crackling noises while covering more than ten meters of the surrounding area.

These electric currents swept around her surroundings like a whip.

Garen was instantly hit by one of the exploding electric currents. He was forced to take a few steps backward before rolling over and dropping to the ground far away. Only then was he able to dodge this explosive move.

“Amazing… I think I know Resonance Degrees affect and amplify Willpower now…”

Garen could clearly feel that the New-Moon Level Resonance Degree Willpowers possessed their own awareness. They soon felt like continuous dynamite-like explosions when they crept into his body. When the Willpower inside his body was unable to counterattack and destroy them in time, they exploded to cause even more damage.

Chapter 876: Real Inner Courtyard 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

When he detected that he had suffered some internal injuries, Garen vaguely understood the terrifying effects of Resonance Degrees and realized that they could produce special abilities from within one’s Willpower.

On the opposite side of him, it seemed as if Havana’s ultimate move had ended and she had run out of Willpower. She disappeared slowly after that.

‘Times up. The fight has resulted in a tie so there will be no rewards or penalties of Quest Points. Please exit the room,’ the computerized voice spoke again slowly.

Without another word, Garen walked out of the room and entered a different one under the indifferent glances of other people. He entered a room with Level Five Willpower and New-Moon Level Resonance Degrees this time.

He underwent the same process and selected the same options before fighting an hour-long battle again.

A strong naked man with a dark green sun tattoo on his chest appeared this time. The records in the computer stated that his name was Conbasque.

“Barbaric Strength…” the hefty fellow swept his right hand in front of his chest before a frighteningly bloody wound appeared on the skin there suddenly. The holographic image of a black bear appeared beside him and began to circle his body before disappearing slowly.

The man then took long strides towards Garen.

Garen did not want to show any signs of weakness and decided to use his Level Five Willpower to face him head on and seize him in one go.

His opponent swung his arm over in a scratching motion as well. Both of their palms came into contact momentarily.

Roar!

The roar of the bear could be heard from the strong man’s body.

Garen staggered and was forced to take more than ten steps backward when he was hit by the tremendous quake.

“What powerful strength!”

Shocked looks appeared in his eyes but he was not afraid at all. Unlike these genetically strengthened Mech Pilots who only possessed Willpower, his biggest advantage was his hidden Secret Techniques and his strong physique.

Once his Living Secret Technique and Hellfrost Peacock Technique had fused within his physique, there were two main abilities that had formed there. The first one was his terrifyingly powerful regenerative abilities; injuries that were normally considered serious among other Mech Pilots could be healed within a short period of time when they were inflicted on Garen. This was how the Peacock’s body strengthened him. The next effect was intense Cold Radiation. This move was used as a trump card. However, he would always need to get rid of those who witnessed him using this move, as it would be his own fault if he was chased out of the inner region after being mistakenly identified as one of the Radioactive People.

“Again!”

Garen used the Ten Thousand True Technique secretly and shaped his hands into fists before turning his body sideways and charging over in that direction. The Ten Thousand True Technique had its own set of specialized skills that were extremely amazing and could utilize three different moves when he used it with all of his strength.

In other words, although it was impossible for practitioners of other battle skills to use different moves once they had used up all of their strength, Garen was different. When he was not using these specialized moves, the Ten Thousand True Technique was his strongest close combat skill that was also the greatest accomplishment of his martial arts.

His opponent let out a bear’s roar once more before clawing at him again.

Clap!

Garen relaxed his fist and opened it into a palm suddenly, before clasping his opponent’s wrist from the side and snapping it brutally.

Crack!

A crisp noise could be heard from his wrist but it was not completely broken yet.

At this moment, a terrifying, thunderous Willpower explosion occurred beside Garen’s ear.

The explosion that was caused by this move would have caused the ears of any other Mech Pilot to bleed from the vibrations and become extremely dizzy. However, Garen was only dizzy for a moment before returning to his normal state at once.

His powerful regenerative abilities could be seen immediately.

“Exceptional!”

Upon realizing that he could not break his opponent’s wrist with one hand, Garen outstretched his other hand at the same time and used both of them to pull downwards.

There was a clapping noise before the hefty fellow swung his other arm downwards and attempted to slap Garen’s cheek. Snake-like hissing noises could be heard when his palm came crashing over. It was obvious that it was possessed by a certain creature’s Willpower.

The slapping motion resembled a snake even more closely when it used its quick speed to move even faster than before.

The hefty fellow let out a fierce roar and took one step forward before the neighs of war-horses could be heard. They stomped on the ground loudly and the entire room shook for a moment. His Willpower turned into the shape of a warhorse in the blink of an eye.

As an experienced veteran, Garen was naturally unafraid of surprise attacks like these. Garen positioned his elbow horizontally and dodged the snake-shaped palm. Meanwhile, he turned his body sideways and casually dodged his opponent’s colliding stance.

His basic attributes were still weak right now and he did not have many advantages as compared to these other Mech Pilots that had used genetic adjustments to strengthen themselves. The amplification of his opponent’s Willpower by his Resonance Degree was alarming. Moreover, amplified Willpower would also strengthen the Energy Fields around one’s body as well. Therefore, he was able to form extremely powerful and terrifying short-term combat abilities.

Essentially, the short-term explosions in this world were extremely amazing. This was another advantage of Willpower. In other words, these attacks were like firearms that were already loaded with bullets. As long as the bullets had not run out yet, these weapons would greatly surpass the combat strength of average people.

If an individual’s basic attributes were at least ten points each, they would definitely be able to defeat opponents of these levels. However, his current Vitality attribute was unable to affect his Willpower greatly and he was merely slightly faster, stronger and had better regenerative abilities in comparison to the average Mech Pilot. He could not compare his own abilities to the advantages of using Willpower Energy Fields.

If he was fighting with an opponent who was also a practitioner of the Crouched Eagle Talon, they would be able to see that Garen had Attribute Points and advantages that were worthy of pride. However, the strongest opponent in this room that he was currently fighting used first rate and rare Training Methods and Willpower. Therefore, Garen’s assumed advantages were not as prominent anymore.

Garen fought with his opponent while experiencing the effects of his Resonance Degree carefully. He was forced to painstakingly counter his opponent many times which injured his body in the process. It was clear that Level Five New-Moon Level individuals were not opponents that he could take on right now.

As he still did not possess sufficient knowledge of Level Five opponents, after the match ended in a draw again, Garen decided to find another room that did not have a Level Five Resonance Degree opponent.

His next opponent was a walk in the park, which made him feel that they were much weaker than the previous New-Moon Level opponents. It was also obvious that their actual combat strength was not even half of that of the earlier opponents.

Garen was able to suppress his new opponent easily. When he used all of his Level Five Willpower, the few advantages that he possessed within his physical body began to appear as well.

He entered a few more rooms with Level Five Willpowers without Resonance Degrees. Garen was gradually able to understand the current rankings of his power clearly.

He was currently between Level Five and Level Five of the New-Moon Level. He could not defeat New-Moon Level individuals directly but could hold them off for a certain period of time.

The sky had already darkened as it was already past ten o’clock at night when he finally walked out from the training rooms.

There were slightly fewer people around him now as numerous students with Level Four Willpower were entering and leaving Level Five rooms. There were about ten rooms around him that were empty while the rest were lit up with red lights above their doors, indicating that they were occupied.

Garen looked down on these students who only possessed Level Four Willpower. Moreover, the students that were entering and leaving around him did not look like students at all. There were middle-aged people, old people, and even a few dwarves who were even shorter than average.

Garen felt that they resembled a large gathering of freaks rather than students.

He could not understand why there was so few Level Four students in the ranking list when he could see so many other Level Four candidates here. This Inner Courtyard continued to give off an abnormally chaotic feeling.

The Outer Courtyard was a haven in comparison to the Inner Courtyard. It was no wonder that the Elite Students in the Inner Courtyard would not leave unless they were going out for quests. If a ban had not been set in place, there were definitely other measures that confined them here.

“Hello, you must be the new student that came in from the Outer Courtyard, right?” suddenly, a gentle voice echoed over from beside Garen while he was observing his surroundings.

He turned in that direction and saw a white-haired youth with round-framed glasses looking at him and smiling. He was dressed like a model student and wore clean and neat clothes. He was surprisingly normal-looking and made Garen feel as if he had momentarily returned to the Outer Courtyard.

“You are?” he furrowed his eyebrows. In an environment like this, normal people like this person were definitely the most abnormal.

“My name is Anda. I’ve been observing you here for a long time now. I never expected that you would enter so many rooms consecutively and still have any energy to spare afterward. You made it look extremely relaxing. It seems that you’re not a normal Outer Courtyard student, huh…” he pushed up his glasses and smiled while flattering him.

“It was alright. I merely entered to take a look. It’s not like I actually did anything. I mainly did not expect that the people inside would be so amazing,” said Garen while smiling gently. He was disguising himself as well. He was previously born in a family of aristocratic territorial lords and had to make sure that he did not seem lower than the other person.

“Disregarding your hour-long foray is being too humble. After entering the Inner Courtyard, you probably saw the environment here. We jokingly say that this place is equivalent to the second wasteland and is comparable to an actual radiation wasteland. The only difference is that the food and drinks here are slightly more abundant,” said the bespectacled Anda softly. “Walk with me?”

“Okay.” Garen was looking for someone to chat about the situation here anyway.

Both of them walked through a passage that led outside. Strangely enough, Garen realized that the bespectacled Anda’s reputation seemed to travel far and wide. Fearful looks appeared on the faces of the people in their surroundings when they saw him. They would give way and form a path for him wordlessly.

While they were walking, Anda briefly introduced the situation, general knowledge, as well as certain important things that happened here while speaking to Garen.

Garen multitasked while listening. He was pondering about how he would face that girl Fila later.

Since he could not fight Level Five New-Moon Level individuals, Half-Moon Levels would be even harder to counter. Meanwhile, that girl Fila was almost at the Full-Moon Level by now. After spending all of the resources that he had accumulated throughout the years on his Mech, he was currently at the critical breakthrough point. Therefore, he could surpass himself greatly at any time.

Garen thought about his advantages carefully.

He had two advantages. One of them was his Living Secret Technique and his trump card, the Cold Radiation from his Hellfrost Peacock Technique, which was his upper hand against the other Mech Pilots. He also had Devour and powerful regenerative abilities that were his hidden strengths that were longer lasting and greater than the abilities of other Mech Pilots.

His second advantage was that his body’s Attributes were able to utilize Potential Points to upgrade itself constantly. The Staff of Yin allowed him to accumulate two Potential Points daily. Therefore, he would be able to grow consistently as long as he had enough time. As long as he was able to achieve at least ten points on average for his physique, he would be able to fight opponents with Level Five Willpower directly.

Furthermore, his Ten Thousand True Technique had fused with his Seven Star Life’s Secret Point. Although they could not be used interchangeably because the laws of their respective universes were different, there were still certain pressure points that possessed amplification effects. Perhaps it could not do certain things, but increasing his combat ability by twofold was definitely not a problem.

He could not utilize the Seven Star Life’s Secret Point fully because the bodily components of the humans here were different. However, the Ten Thousand True Technique’s greatest advantage meant that he would not have to get used to different bodies next time. This External Technique used large parts of the universe and was formed by some of the principles behind Garen’s Living Secret Technique. Therefore, although it did not possess as much strength, it was impossible to find compatibility like this with any other Secret Techniques.

There were two paths in front of him now. The first path required him to upgrade his Living Secret Technique, which meant that his Hellfrost Peacock Technique would definitely undergo impressive qualitative changes in the future. However, this path was slightly more difficult.

The second path would need him to upgrade his Attributes and use the Ten Thousand True Technique to improve himself.

Chapter 877: Ruthless 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Although the effects of Garen’s martial arts environment were much stronger than those of other people’s, the desire to achieve a great advantage with martial arts within the foundation of the perfect fight simulations and practices in this world was merely a pipe dream.

Once the martial arts environment surpassed the King of the Century level, Garen would then obtain great advantages that came from being on the same playing field. He would be able to grasp opportunities in a more precise manner than other people. He could also do things without hesitating or wasting any of his combat energy. Furthermore, his combat strategies and instincts would undergo shocking improvements.

However, this meant that only his martial arts would become strong. When he encountered situations with enemies that possessed exceptional Willpower techniques and belonged to high levels, it would be completely impossible for him to anticipate all of his opponent’s various abilities. Therefore, he could only take the most conservative approach to achieve the highest probability of winning reliably.

He was only able to progressively display the true strength of his martial arts environment once he had gradually learned more about Willpower techniques through numerous reports, information, and experience.

The only thing that Garen could use now was his combat strategies. However, these strategies could not help him at all if he did not practice and perfect his martial arts and combat skills, as these things relied on an individual’s own selections and style.

Once he had arranged the information in his mind, Garen decided to upgrade his Living Secret Technique immediately. After all, this ability could improve his physical Attributes and even his Willpower level.

As for the methods of using upgrades that required Potential Points, Garen chatted with Anda leisurely while secretly thinking of ways to add his Potential Points to the Hellfrost Peacock Technique. As expected, there was no way to upgrade the Hellfrost Peacock Technique in one go. It seemed as though its progress had been paused because something was lacking. However, a few of his Potential Points had disappeared, making it clear that some of them had been consumed.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows slightly and used his Willpower to activate the Living Secret Technique core inside his body. A series of information flowed out.

“I need both the Red Peacock Stone and the White Peacock Stone to enter the next stage?” Garen recalled the ores that he had seen previously. The White Peacock Stone was a variation of the Rainbow Stone while the Red Peacock Stone that was described by the Living Secret Technique was actually the Red Rainbow Stone. However, the production rate of these stones was much lower as compared to the White Rainbow Stone and they were sourced from different places as well.

His Hellfrost Peacock Technique had almost reached the Level Six stage. However, its progress rate had been stuck at 5% all this while without moving at all.

“…We’ve almost arrived at the battlegrounds, do you want to go in and take a look? This is an impressive place,” he had not noticed when Anda had started talking about the battlegrounds beside him.

Garen’s mind snapped back to reality and realized that they were very far from the training grounds now. They were now walking in front of a huge circular ashen building in the Inner Courtyard. This place was completely tranquil as there were only a few people who were leaving and entering. Most of them were rushing inside with furious looks on their faces.

“This is a place to settle grudges, whether fatal or not. Of course, there are only a handful of people who actually come here to duel while most of them are here to watch the mutated beasts fight. This place hosts major gambling tournaments and is also the biggest place to select and purchase mutated beasts. Most of these mutated beasts can help with quests when they are brought outside to the radiation belts,” Anda smiled while explaining.

“Mutated beasts?” this was the first time that Garen had heard of people keeping these playthings as pets.

“Wanna go in and take a look? You can occasionally find good things inside the battlegrounds,” Anda smiled.

“Alright, just be frank,” said Garen while glancing at the edge of the battlegrounds. “What were you planning to do when you reached out to me personally? Don’t just say that you wanted to chat because you were bored.”

Anda pushed his glasses.

“Naturally, I wanted to get some people to join my quest unit. I’ve already gotten three people to join but I need two more suitable candidates. You’ve caught my eye.”

“You’re certain that I’ll be useful even though I’m merely a new student who just entered?” said Garen calmly.

“You managed to escape Fila’s grasp and survive despite just entering this place. Moreover, it seems like all your wounds have healed in less than half a day. You may be a newbie but you’re not a regular person…” Anda smiled again.

Garen was shocked. This fellow’s information sources were extremely active. He had just healed and come out to understand his circumstances, yet the other person had been able to obtain detailed information about him instantly.

“You are certainly well-informed.”

“Those who are able to prosper eternally in the Inner Courtyard definitely have their own strong suits,” Anda stood still and patted nonexistent dirt off his clothes. “Don’t worry about Fila and the others. That girl is arrogant, but she will not look for you again if she didn’t kill you the first time unless you provoke her on your own. She’s currently facing a critical moment in her life and is about to face a great enemy. Once she releases the strength that she has accumulated, there is a high probability that she will be able to enter the perfect stage of the Full-Moon Level. When she stands side-by-side with Red-Eyed Medero, she will have the chance to fight him for a place in Black Star.”

“Other than Fila, I offended two other people as well.”

“Don’t worry about those two. If you don’t have enough strength to defeat them, it will make no difference if you die by their hands or if you die during the quest,” Anda smiled while saying these cold words.

“You don’t sound like a twenty year old guy at all,” spat Garen while furrowing his eyebrows.

“I’m so sorry. I’m actually 108 years old this year,” said Anda with an indifferent look on his face. “After spending more than forty years in the Inner Courtyard, I even managed to unearth a few top class prodigies in the beginning.”

More than a hundred years old?!

Garen was astonished because this guy did not look as if he was over a hundred years old.

“You don’t have to act so surprisedly. Forgive me for going through your information, but I discovered that you were born in a normal family. Therefore, it is natural that you would not know many of the higher level Mech Pilot’s hidden secrets,” smiled Anda. “Do you know why so many Pilots in the Inner Courtyard view Resonance Degrees so highly?”

“It’s rumored that only individuals with the highest Resonance Degrees will be able to enter the Inherited Level,” answered Garen calmly.

“That is only one of the reasons. There’s another reason that nobody can evade. It is also the reason why everybody suppresses their own strength and Willpower in every possible way. It is the main reason why they are constantly trying to break through their Resonance Degrees,” Anda raised a finger. “That reason is their lifespan.”

“Lifespan?”

“Yes, lifespan,” a strange look glimmered in Anda’s eyes. “In theory, an individual can use certain measures to improve themselves and enter the Inherited Level once their Resonance Degrees have achieved the Full-Moon Level. This level is called Full-Moon to indicate that it is full and perfect. The main reason why numerous Full-Moon Level individuals have painstakingly suppressed themselves in vain to enter the Two-Moons Level before promoting themselves naturally is for the sake of their lifespans. Once they have entered the Full-Moon Level, their lifespans will increase by ten years every time their Resonance Degrees increase by 1%. This is the general consensus of the secret that those of the higher levels are hiding.”

“Those with Resonance Degrees of less than 90% are already part of the Full-Moon Level, so the 10% gap between the Full-Moon Level and Two-Moons Level would allow them to increase their lifespans by a hundred years?!” Garen was slightly shocked as well.

“Yes. It’s like this, although the current Genetic Adjustment Technology and Biochemical Technology are extremely advanced, things like lifespans depend on things that happen by chance. Those that belong to the Inherited Level and the levels below that only have one chance to increase their lifespans. Therefore, no one would be willing to give up on something like that. Why do you think Red-Eyed Medero refused to enter the Inherited Level for such a long time? One reason was that her tutor did not give her Inherited Level Training Methods. However, the main reason for her refusal to enter the Inherited Level was because she wanted to lay down her foundation and be well-prepared,” Anda explained matter-of-factly.

“An individual’s Resonance Degree is like a magnifying glass that can increase the foundation of one’s strength. If the foundation of your Willpower is too weak, it will naturally remain weak even when it is amplified. However, if the foundation of your strength is strong but you failed to increase it sufficiently, you will not become any stronger. Both of these factors need to increase proportionally for it to work best,” said Anda calmly while rearranging his glasses.

“So what kind of help were you hoping gain after coming all this way to find me?” Garen asked the most important question. He did not believe that the other man would be so kind as to come here specially to help him clear his doubts.

“I need your healing abilities,” the glow from a nearby light source reflected off Anda’s glasses. It was a bright, snowy light.

“Healing abilities?”

“You managed to heal your deadly wounds in one afternoon. Do you know if you can use this ability on others?” asked Anda honestly with a sincere expression on his face.

“My healing abilities can be used to backup and support other people. However, the effects will not be as strong as when they are used on me,” nodded Garen. His nameless Willpower did have healing effects on other people. However, it could only restore their physical wounds and did not seem to have any effects on the restoration of their Willpower. This Willpower was mainly used to heal Mechs instead. However, it would probably not have any healing effects on Mechs than belonged to levels that were lower than the Inherited Level.

“I guessed so too,” Anda nodded and smiled. “Our unit is coincidentally lacking a support member, so we’ll leave this to you.”

“Don’t tell me you don’t have medicine or things like that?”

“Of course we do. However, the distance of our quest is too great and our expenses for medicine will be too burdensome as well,” answered Anda. “Have you heard of the Mingchuan Snowy Mountain?”

“Mingchuan Snowy Mountain? The large snowy mountains on the border of the radiation belt? You’re not afraid of going there despite the hordes of mutated beasts?” asked Garen. He had seen some information about that place once. His upgraded Intelligence gave him a photographic memory that greatly surpassed the abilities of regular people. Although the information had been vague, he still had some impressions of it.

“The traces of the radiation belts that were left behind on the Mother Planet are everywhere. Although they are dangerous, the risks and rewards are acceptable. Naturally, our main plan was to accept the quest because we would gain Quest Points no matter where we went while obtaining certain things that we were looking for. Unless you decide to join us, we cannot simply leak any more information.”

Garen quietened down for a moment and began to consider his gains and losses.

“Can you give me a hint about what this is about?”

“Of course I can. It has to do with the Mech materials that both you and I desire,” nodded Anda. “Moreover, they are materials for the main parts such as the frame systems.”

“I’ll need to return and consider this for some time,” Naturally, Garen would not agree so easily when he did not know anything about this quest.

“Let’s exchange contact details. If you don’t contact me personally after ten days, I’ll assume that you’ve declined,” Anda tapped his watch against Garen’s to exchange their contact details. “I’ll leave first then.”

“Alright, thank you for providing this information,” Garen thanked him sincerely. The other man had actually given him a lot of information. Although he did not know if it was truly reliable, at least he had a rough idea now.

“Fila is just part of a neutral party. There are three main parties in the Inner Courtyard and you can check the others as long as you don’t interfere with these three. Go back and investigate them properly,” Anda waved without turning around and entered one of the battlegrounds in front immediately.

Garen watched him leave the area and enter the battleground before he turned around and walked in the other direction. He wanted to go to the library now as he could probably find more information there.

************************

“Clint…”

“Clint… Clint…”

“Wake up now… Wake up…”

A voice that was calling out his name echoed beside Clint’s ear continuously. It seemed as if it was drifting over from an extremely far place and was somewhat fuzzy and unclear.

Clint woke up from his deep slumber slowly.

It seemed as if he had fallen asleep on a huge bed. The room was pitch black and the silhouette of a man could be seen sitting beside the bed while smoking.

“Awake?” the man’s voice was very hoarse as if his throat had suffered serious injuries. The sound of leaking air could be heard when he spoke.

“Where am I?” Clint tried to raise his body while he was still dazed but soon realized that his entire body was stiff and completely immobile. “Where’s Lon? Lon…”

“Are you talking about that girl? She’s sleeping next door,” said the man before taking another puff of his cigarette.

“You… Were you the one who saved us?” asked Clint carefully. He realized suddenly that his body was completely naked! He became frightened immediately.

“Yeah. I happened to be carrying out a vendetta against that shop when I saw both of you being taken away. I decided to save you just because I was there,” when the man stood up, the lines of his taut muscles could be seen vaguely.

“I would have ignored you if you hadn’t looked like someone I knew. Hurry up and get out of here once you’ve rested. I’m going to leave now too.”

The man walked out of the door while he was still speaking. Once the room door was opened, blinding golden sunlight cascaded inside and illuminated the entire room at once.

Clint could feel that his eyesight was somewhat blurry. He could only squint his eyes shut while the man walked out and disappeared on the other side. Red Moon’s voice began to echo in his mind again.

“How was it? Did you get any rest?”

“Lord Red Moon!” Clint could not stop the tears that were brimming in his eyes which had almost overflown. It seemed as though he had found his birth mother suddenly.

“Don’t cry, don’t cry. I used your Willpower to hypnotize that man for a while before he agreed to save both of you. Isn’t everything all right now?” it was rare for Red Moon to speak gently like this.

“But… But…” this was the first time Clint had cried so pitifully.

“Don’t worry, Lon is fine. That man wasn’t interested in her at all. He didn’t even touch the clothes on her back,” consoled Red Moon.

“But… My backside really hurts…” Clint began to cry loudly.

“…”

Red Moon was unaware of what had happened because he had used too much strength. He was unaware of the frightening things that Clint had undergone after he fainted again. After looking at the expression of inconsolable grief on Clint’s face, he vowed not to ask about his experiences during these dark moments of his life ever again.

Chapter 878: Ruthless 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In a different room.

Baylon hugged the blanket tightly and curled into herself on the bed while taking in her entire surroundings.

After fainting from intoxication, she had woken up and found herself lying on this bed. There was no one around her and the room door was locked shut.

Suddenly, a familiar cry echoed from the next room.

“It’s Clint!!” she was happily surprised at once. She crept over anxiously and leaned against the wall closely while listening carefully.

“Clint!! Is it you?!” she yelled loudly.

The cries from the next room softened at once. Half a second later, a timid voice drifted over.

“Lon?”

“It’s really you!” Baylon’s mind was freed of anxiety immediately.

“Alright, little girl. You’re all right now. I’ve examined the area and both of you are currently in a place that is almost a thousand kilometers from the previous shop. You’ll be staying at this inn temporarily,” the sound waves of Red Moon’s voice were transferred into her mind.

“Clint. What happened to Clint? Why is he crying so sadly?” Kind Baylon was concerned about her friend immediately.

“He’s fine… He just encountered one of life’s minor obstacles…” Red Moon did not know how to explain this either. The things that were supposed to happen had occurred already…

“Is he really okay?” Baylon was still worried.

“Don’t worry. A man will definitely be able to get over a small pain like this,” consoled Red Moon. “The person who saved you has left. It’s best that both of you get up immediately to check your surroundings and geographical conditions. This place is just a temporary residence so other than yourselves, there aren’t any other living things, food, or even water here. If you don’t hurry up and find a way out, don’t blame me if you end up starving to death here.”

These words echoed in the minds of these two people simultaneously. Both of them had been able to distinguish when Red Moon was being honest or lying long ago. Now, they could clearly tell that Red Moon was speaking the truth. They crawled out of bed immediately while Clint looked around for clothes that he could wear.

He pushed the door open and walked out.

Bright, burning golden sunlight cascaded inside and spread across his skin, leaving a painful burning sensation there. Their surroundings were primarily a stretch of barren wilderness that included yellow-green plains and a little winding stream could occasionally be seen. Strangely enough, the water in the stream was green while thin shrouds of green mist would rise from it faintly.

The entire place was deathly quiet and there was not even a single fly to be seen.

Baylon looked into the distance. Near the horizon, a man in an eye-catching leather jacket could be seen riding his motorcycle speedily into the distance faintly. Strangely enough, the motorcycle was silent.

“That man saved you. This place was initially just a dilapidated hut that he turned into a temporary resting stop,” explained Red Moon softly.

“What should we do now?” Baylon felt suddenly thirsty.

“Think of a way to survive,” answered Red Moon solemnly. “You can’t drink the water here because it’s toxic. Since there are no other living things, it means that there won’t be any pieces of radioactive meat for you to eat either. It’s a good thing that I had brought some edible supplies with me in my space knob. I can support you for a period of time, but if you don’t find a way to solve your food problem within a week, you will definitely starve to death in this radioactive wasteland.”

“This is the radiation belt, huh…” this was the first time Baylon had felt the brutality of the radiation belt. First, it was the betrayal of the supposedly kind Big Sister and Yellow Bearded Uncle, and now they were in a situation where they had nothing to eat or drink. At this moment, the lack of food and water had become a life-threatening issue.

“Think of it as a form of self-training,” Red Moon sighed. “This is one of the main reasons why most people in the radiation belts don’t live past seventy or eighty years. They can’t preserve their health whenever they drink water, and their food sources are limited to a few plants and mostly the flesh of mutated beasts with lower rates of radiation inside their bodies. Most of the time, they are only able to consume a fist-sized amount of meat from mutated beasts that are the size of buffalos. After risking their lives to kill these animals, the food they get is usually only enough for one person.”

While listening to Red Moon’s explanations, Baylon suddenly understood the brutality and hardships that were part of the radiation belt wastelands.

“What would my big brother do if he was here?” she murmured softly.

“Your brother… I guess he would be at ease here,” Red Moon recalled the man whom he had judged wrongly. “That guy… has an extreme ruthlessness in his bones…”

******************

After circling the Inner Courtyard a few times, Garen realized that it was impossible for him to encounter that male student from the administration office again. There were no traces of that female student nicknamed Goldfish either. Meanwhile, he heard from others that Fila had gone to participate in some ceremony.

Once he had visited the library and read up on more of the general information here, Garen finally understood the makings of the entire Inner Courtyard properly.

To put it simply, the Inner Courtyard was the true, ruthless side of Blackboard Academy, while the Outer Courtyard was merely a place to train military and government personnel. The Outer Courtyard was mild and gentle while the Inner Courtyard was where the savage fights took place.

Quest Points were needed for everything. They were needed for training, purchasing items, duels, and everything else. Of course, one could pay with Universal Units instead if they were wealthy. However, the prices of the items here could hardly be borne by average multi-millionaires, as the goods here were twice the price of their normal rates outside. Moreover, the more valuable items here were easily priced at millions of Universal Units while they were actually much cheaper when they were bought with Quest Points instead.

It was obvious that life throughout the entire Inner Courtyard revolved around Quest Points.

Most of the professors and instructors in the Inner Courtyard were aloof and detached. They usually stayed within their own domains and hardly left; perhaps one wouldn’t even notice if they went out.

The students were the only ones who were active in the Inner Courtyard. The professors and instructors would never involve themselves in the fights between students and would be sent home if they died or became useless. Perhaps they would even be placed in simple positions if necessary.

The students in the Inner Courtyard were distributed into three main parties; the Black Star Party where the Black Star was the head, the Black Rain Party that was led by Red-Eyed Medero and three others, and Leo that was led by the exchange and transfer students.

There were many other smaller and larger organizations and many strong drifters like Fila. Garen understood that there were others like Anda who formed temporary groups and quest units. Most of them did not have close relationships and would only work together on quests. There were probably twenty groups like this in the Inner Courtyard.

Batches of students in higher grades such as Fifth-year and Sixth-year students would enter the Inner Courtyard yearly because this was the only place that contained information about Resonance Degrees that could surpass Level Six Inherited Levels. Therefore, many people continued to rush over continuously for a chance to find a rare opportunity despite being aware of the abnormal dangers here.

The life of an Inner Courtyard student was very simple.

There was nothing but quests. They would constantly accumulate the necessary resources for their Mechs, various techniques, and Training Methods. Other than quests, they needed to complete specific durations of training sessions during public classes. They would use up a lot of Quest Points if they failed to complete these training sessions. When their Quest Points were insufficient, they would be kicked out of the Inner Courtyard and all of their memories regarding Resonance Degrees would be wiped completely.

The two main things were their quests and public classes. These public classes were supposedly classes but were actually more like tests. They were used to get rid of batches of students that could not meet the mark while quests were used to continuously train the students’ progress.

The tutors and even outsiders would constantly release quests for the Elite Students of the Inner Courtyard. Students that were able to survive in this environment would definitely surpass the even first-rate cream of the crop of the Outer Courtyard.

Quest Points meant everything here. They could be used for business transactions, payments, punishment, and could even be used to purchase various techniques and materials that people of the outside world had never even heard of.

Meanwhile, the relationship between the students and tutors here were more like business partners that traded in technical knowledge rather than merely students and teachers. The tutors were like sellers who peddled various technique knowledge while providing the students with secret, high-grade information.

The students would trade technique knowledge among themselves as well while the tutors would turn a blind eye to their actions. Therefore, they would be able to purchase technique knowledge from certain powerful or high-level instructors and professors. Moreover, they would be able to gain even more Quest Points if they traded this knowledge. This would also show the key difference between high and low rankings.

Garen thought of his own Professor Van Doe. He was considered to rank in the middle of the Inner Courtyard but was actually concealing the depths of his powers. However, most of the instructors and professors here would hide most of their true strengths. On the surface, Van Doe only belonged to Level Five of the Twin-Moons Level. In reality, no one knew the true extent of his strength. There were twenty to thirty other professors like him in the Inner Courtyard that had indistinguishable powers.

Once he had understood the initial parts of this information from various aspects, Garen began to gain a brief understanding of life in the Inner Courtyard.

As for Anda’s invitation to join his quest, Garen had gathered some information from the quest section of the library. He learned that they would truly need to travel for a long journey and would need to pass through the radiation belt and even pilot Mechs. They would also need to pass through a vast terrain along the way. The entire quest would take at least half a month up to a whole month to complete.

Garen had thought of visiting the radiation belt as well. Red Moon had previously informed him that they had already entered the radiation belt and he wanted to see if he could find Clint and the others.

He would also need time to purchase the Red Peacock Stone.

Upon returning to the tutors’ villas and entering his own room, Garen contacted Kendall’s external phone number immediately.

“Boss! Tell me your instructions!” after relying on Garen, Kendall had become the boss of a larger than average company. His main business was arranging the transport of Rainbow Stones. Once he had gained Garen’s trust, his daily life was completely smooth sailing. His face on the screen of Garen’s watch was currently rounder and chubbier like a smiling Buddha.

“Purchase Red Rainbow Stones on the market immediately. It’s best if you find a stable goods supply channel.”

“How much do you need?”

“Get two tonnes from the market and just store them first. Separate ten percent of the profits and purchase them slowly once you’ve found a channel. Send me a report of the revenue and expenditure accounts once every two months,” said Garen in a straightforward manner.

“No problem, this will be easy. Numerous clients have chased me previously to ask if I needed anymore Rainbow Stones of other colors,” Kendall’s eyes became two slits when he laughed. Then, he happened to think of something. “Boss, there are more of the other colored Rainbow Stones but their purity levels are lower. Their prices might be slightly more expensive than White Rainbow Stones too…”

“Don’t worry about the expenses, just be as quick as possible,” Garen pondered for a moment. “Buy two tonnes of the other Rainbow Stones and kept them in the warehouse as well in case we need to transfer them suddenly.”

“Understood, it will be done in less than two months! However, it will probably take a longer time for them to be sent over. After all, the red ones are scattered within a wider area and their production rate in a single area is very low.” Kendall sounded extremely confident when he spoke. It was clear that he had obtained the channels of many clients previously and knew the necessary information like the back of his hand.

“No problem. It’ll be fine as long as you can to do it. I’ll be waiting for your good news.”

“I swear that I won’t let you down!”

Garen exhaled slowly once he had disconnected the phone call.

“It’s time for me to solve the problem with Goldfish and that guy…”

Chapter 879: Take Action 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the top floor of the multistoried building, the strong wind tousled Garen’s hair and clothes. He stood at the edge of the floor, allowing the gigantic billboard to block more than half of his body while he lowered his head and looked downwards.

On the street below that stretched between two tall buildings, among the people on the pavement, a young man and woman walked out of a building and walked along the street together towards a few parked motorcycles.

Through the corner of his eye, Garen saw that the red-haired girl who was currently chatting with two males was actually Goldfish whom he had seen previously.

“Apparently the information I received from Anda was pretty accurate,” that guy named Anda was clearly an information trader as the information that he received from him for one hundred thousand points was extremely reliable.

Garen raised his watch and glanced at his own Quest Points.

“I only have three points left after going to the training room even though I had twenty points in the beginning… Looks like I’ll have to get some Quest Points soon or it’ll be troublesome during the examinations.”

He lowered his head and stared below at Goldfish who was saying goodbye to the two boys and walking with another girl back to her motorcycle. He turned around and rushed downstairs but Goldfish had already gotten on her motorcycle and left the building area once he had reached the bottom floor.

Garen had fully memorized the terrain of this area clearly a long time ago. He used the alleys and shortcuts to follow Goldfish closely. After modifying his body, he was almost able to match the speed of the motorcycle when he ran at full speed.

While following her closely from behind slowly, he saw Goldfish arriving in front of an ashen, pointed multistoried building a little while later. She stopped her motorcycle, switched off the engine and got down.

Garen glanced at the name of the owner of this large building that was marked on the side.

“Von Anise. The information states that this person is one of the instructors in the inner domain but this place looks very unassuming…”

After hesitating for a moment, Garen walked out of the alley and took large strides towards the doorway of the building that Goldfish entered.

Goldfish was pushing the revolving glass door that led to the lower floor of the building when she saw a figure behind her that was reflected by the glass suddenly.

“It’s that person from that day!” she was shocked. “He actually followed me all the way here! How did he find me!” she had begged her seniors to help her find information about the man but they had yet to give it to her even until now. She had never expected that the other person would be slightly faster than herself.

Fortunately, she could still use that item for a third time.

Goldfish reached into her pants pocket and grasped the item inside her pocket tightly while steadying her mind.

She turned around and faced her opponent head-on while getting out of the way so that other people could come and go.

“Should we step aside and chat?” the voice of the other man drifted over. Goldfish furrowed her eyebrows and looked at him. He had short black hair, dark blue eyes, and pale skin. He looked vicious even though the corners of his mouth were curled when he smiled which made it seem as if he was sneering cruelly. His body was muscular and he gave off an oppressive atmosphere faintly when he stood there.

“Do you always move so quickly?” Goldfish teased.

“It was just luck,” Garen smiled.

“What do you want to talk about?” Goldfish observed her opponent’s actions and stance carefully. After suffering terrible injuries the last time, she knew that this man was strong. However, should she really be fighting right in front of the building where her tutor was staying?

While looking at this man cautiously, Goldfish made a mental note to be extremely careful.

The other person smiled.

“I still remember the first time I was in the hospital. You came into my room at night, ambushed me, and almost mauled me. I’m here to repay you.”

Goldfish recalled everything immediately. He was the strange young man whom she had encountered that night, the same person she had met suddenly while carrying out her mission. Her memory of him was still so vibrant even though a long period of time had passed since then.

“What are you planning to do?” fear began to fill her mind. She looked on as the other man continued to smile calmly as if he had no intention of taking action against her at all. However, she could not understand why she felt terrified while standing on the opposite side of him.

“The compensation for that night and the injuries that Fila inflicted on me previously will be part of your debt to pay. How many Quest Points do you have now?” asked Garen calmly.

“I have two hundred and sixty-three points and I’ll transfer all of them to you! Don’t come back and bother me!” Goldfish took a step back and tried to increase the distance between herself and the other person. Fila had just happened to pass by coincidentally when she saved Goldfish and her seniors that one time. However, it was impossible for her to have such good luck every single time.

“So few points,” Garen twisted his neck.

“What do you mean ‘few points’?! We only managed to accumulate these Quest Points after doing many difficult quests over a long period of time!” Goldfish’s voice had become slightly higher. However, she tried her best to suppress it immediately. “How do you plan on letting me off then?! I still have more than a million Universal Units and I can transfer all of them to you too. I also have a few techniques on me that I can give you too!”

She knew that she would have no way to live if she did not solve this problem properly now. Her opponent was not someone that a Level Two individual like herself would be able to defeat.

Initially, Garen had come over to try and understand the situation better and planned to find an opportunity to kill his opponent later. However, he had never expected that this woman would be tactful enough to admit defeat immediately. This made it difficult for him to go on with his original plans.

Just as he was hesitating, Goldfish opened her mouth again.

“Tell me your requirements. I have some girls in my downlines that I can let you play with, including myself if that’s what you want. As long as you stop looking for me and giving me trouble. Anything is fine.”

“What are you…” Garen was slightly shocked.

“That’s right. Why do you think I have so many Quest Points?” Goldfish brushed her long hair away from her forehead. “I’m the one they call ‘Thorn’, so wouldn’t it be natural that I have so many beautiful roses around me?”

The supposed ‘Thorn’ was actually a female pimp who engaged in the flesh trade while the female students below her merely nicknamed her with this euphemism.

Garen understood at once when he heard everything.

“Thorn? No wonder you have so much savings and tricks despite your low level.”

“Since I’ve already admitted defeat, you can either kill me or dismember me now,” Goldfish stretched both of her arms open and raised her ample bosom intentionally.

“If it’s going to be like this, we have certainly solved our problems quickly,” Garen smiled. “Tell me the information about the person from the Administrative Bureau who made a move that day then…”

Tch!!

He charged forward suddenly and curled his finger upwards like a hook before stabbing it in front.

A popping noise could be heard before a wet, bloody eyeball was gouged out of Goldfish’s eye socket. While she screamed in pain, Garen used his palm to hit her lower abdomen swiftly.

Goldfish’s entire body was sent flying before she collided with the glass door behind her violently. The glass did not break from the collision but the impact caused her to bounce back right after she hit the door.

“This will write off our previous grudges,” smiled Garen while walking over. He stomped downwards and cracked Goldfish’s right thigh bone in one movement.

Ahh!!!

The latter let out a blood-curdling cry instantly.

None of the surrounding passersby came forward to stop them. When they witnessed the violence happening right in front of their eyes, most of the people who were entering and leaving the building walked around the pair instead and hastened their footsteps to leave the area quickly.

No one would be willing to intentionally start a fight with a Level Four pilot here in a low-level territory like this. Therefore, most of them just evaded him and left.

Goldfish wailed painfully and pressed one hand against her thigh while using her other hand to cover her eye. Every single trace of her beautiful disposition had disappeared, leaving nothing but miserable howls. Large puddles of sweat that had formed from the intense pain drenched her entire body and soaked through most of her clothes. Next, dark patches appeared where they were dirtied by the dust on the ground.

Garen shook his head faintly.

“Remember to pass me the information.”

“I… I will!” Goldfish ground her teeth and trembled when she spoke. The pain that was coursing through her body made it almost impossible for her to focus her attention.

“And about the Quest Points, transfer two hundred to me. Forget about the Universal Units,” said Garen casually.

After forcing Goldfish to transfer her Quest Points and give him the information about the person from the Administrative Bureau, Garen leisurely left the area.

“I’ll come and look for you again if I need to,” he waved at Goldfish with his back towards her and left in a relaxed and happy manner.

Goldfish’s soft curses echoed behind him from afar.

“Don’t think I didn’t hear that~” Garen’s single sentence was enough to scare Goldfish into shutting her mouth tightly.

******************

Reagan’s mind felt somewhat disturbed when he exited the Administrative Bureau.

He had just received news that the ‘Thorn’ Goldfish had been ambushed outside the doorway of her own home. One of her eyes had been blinded while one of her legs had become lame. Her opponent was violent and cruel and there was no way to fit her with new artificial parts yet. It was rumored that he had used special measures to completely destroy the edges of the parts that could be used for artificial implants.

Goldfish had almost lost her own life as well. The scariest part was that her opponent’s moves were as precise as surgical operations as there had not been much bleeding. Instead, most of her bleeding was internal.

Goldfish was completely quiet when they saved her life. She remained silent and left the hospital immediately after paying the treatment fees.

Some people said that her attacker was a black haired, muscular man who was tall and looked vicious.

This made Reagan immediately think of the man that he had helped Goldfish get rid of recently. If Fila had not coincidentally inflicted him with critical injuries that time…

“There’s no way that it could be that man…” he shook his head and walked out of the Administrative Bureau. He greeted a few of his colleagues before walking towards the underground carpark.

“That man was badly injured by Senior Fila. He wouldn’t be able to heal his injuries so quickly regardless of the treatment methods that he used. Moreover, according to what Senior Fila said, if that person didn’t die in the fight, he would be crippled at least.” Reagan walked into the quiet and empty underground car park. He walked to the side of his car quickly before pulling the door open.

“Hi, how are you?”

Suddenly, he saw a black-haired man sitting in his own car. This man had dark blue eyes and was currently stretching his hand outwards and greeting him while exposing his pearly white teeth.

“You!” Reagan wondered if he had walked to the wrong car. He was just about to open his mouth and ask when he was suddenly overcome by a bout of dizziness.

He lowered his head in a daze and looked at his lower abdomen. A pale arm had appeared there suddenly and was now stabbing deeply into his stomach. Blood flowed down his pant leg continuously and dyed his shoes red. It dripped on the ground and formed a little puddle of bright red fresh blood there.

Instantly, he looked over at the other man’s hand that was being outstretched slowly. However, there was not a single drop of blood there.

“A favor for what happened during the last few days. Thank you so much for your care,” Garen’s smile was both alluring and vicious.

“You…!!” said Reagan in disbelief while covering the wound on his abdomen. However, the hole there was too big and he could actually see the ground behind him faintly through his stomach.

He knew that he would not be able to leave today.

“My big sister… will not forgive you!!” he staggered a few steps backward and sat on the ground. His face had already turned ghostly pale because of the dangerous blood loss he was suffering.

Vroom… The sound of a car engine could be heard before a Hover Car was positioned towards his body precisely. The car traveled at the quickest speed before crashing into him violently.

A popping noise could be heard when Reagan was smashed in between the car and the wall. He turned into a mess of bloody red bits of flesh before he stopped moving completely.

Garen sat in the driver’s seat and turned the engine off and got out of the car. He had turned off the automatic surveillance cameras in the car park long ago and was not worried that any traces of his identity as the killer would be recorded.

“This has been solved as well. The last one is Fila,” he took his gloves off and rubbed his slightly cold hands together before turning around and walking out of the car park exit.

Coincidentally, a slender man in white clothes was walking down the slope that led to the car park slowly. He held his car keys in his hands and watched Garen who was walking out. The tip of his nose twitched slightly as if he had smelled something unpleasant. Unconsciously, he glanced at Garen once again.

Garen turned to him and curled his mouth into a smile before walking out of the car park leisurely.

Mech Pilots with strong Willpowers were incredibly powerful when they were prepared. However, their reaction speeds and accomplishments could never surpass Secret Technique users when they were ambushed suddenly. Mech Pilots needed to adjust their Willpower to strengthen their bodies to use both attack and defense moves. Moreover, Willpower could not be used unconsciously and required nerve reactions before they could come into effect.

Chapter 880: Take Action 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

These pilots were like superpowers that were physically weak; or like mages, who were powerful when they were fully prepared, but once they were caught off guard, the previous scene would occur. Reagan could not even react and was killed with one blow in a split second.

Their bodies did not have the protection of energy field. Without gene enhancement, they could not even match some of those trained musclemen.

“In that case, maybe Fila should also be the same case. Perhaps I can go and see if there is a chance to move in,” Garen assessed.

The biggest weakness of pilots was that they could not maintain their state of strength at all times like Secret Technique practitioners. Their Willpower was equivalent to the bullets in a pistol that had to be reloaded after opening fire. Therefore, they would not be in a state of preparedness at all times because this kind of state would exhaust Willpower.

In this way, they were not that powerful in their usual daily state. When faced with threats that they could not respond in time to, it would likely be the end of them.

Walking out of the parking lot, Garen looked up at the artificial sun. The sun, which was surrounded by silver halos, was shining unceasingly with its great brilliancy.

He had found the best way to deal with pilots, which was close-range attacks. When the opponent did not even have a chance to react with their Willpower, he would be able to hit them hard.

Pilots without the protection of Willpower Field were, at best, slightly stronger than ordinary people.

They were not like Secret Technique practitioners, who would always have a robust physique defense on par with their own strength.

“Freeze!” suddenly, a man’s voice shouted from behind.

Garen did not care. Yet, he felt a sudden cold at his back and immediately bowed his head. He mustered his Willpower and reached out his hand above his head, making a grabbing movement.

A hard and sharp feeling instantly reached his fingertips and Garen retracted his fingers in the nick of time but was still scraped a little.

Only then did he saw clearly what was passing over his head.

It was a mechanical bee the size of a fist. The bees were made of silvery-white metal while the wings behind were of non-metal materials that were vibrating at high speed. Some parts of the body were even covered with some kind of flesh and blood, giving the impression of a fusion of mechanical and biochemical science and technology.

Garen looked at his fingers and a layer of skin had been broken unknowingly. Blood was vaguely seen.

“I told you to freeze!” the man’s voice rang again.

Garen turned around. He actually completely ignored the mechanical bees that were still flying in mid-air but looked directly at the man in a white shirt who was coming after him.

This man was the man who had just entered the parking lot.

His face clouded over and there was an identical mechanical bee hovering around him.

“Daring to murder in the Administrative Bureau, you sure are bold!”

Garen felt that it was strange that he did not feel any Willpower of aggressive nature on the other party. There was only a layer of protective film like a protective cover overlying the person.

“What murder? No idea what you’re talking about, friend,” Garen shrugged innocently. “You may have a mouth but you wouldn’t want to simply frame a good person.”

“Whether it’s framing or not, we’ll know for sure once you follow me back to the Administrative Bureau!” the man’s voice had not faded out.

Garen then felt a strong rush of wind at the back of his head. Without looking back, he lowered his head, stomped the floor and leaped backward like a compressed spring, drawing out a perfect arc. The oncoming bees rushed past him and before they could even respond, he had disappeared around the corner in just a few steps.

“What a terrific skill!” when the white-shirt man saw this scene, his face expression immediately turned serious. “Even the mechanical bees with Level Three speed couldn’t catch up with him…” his eyes flickered. He decided not to get involved in this matter. The opponent this time was not an average person. This response was purely that of a veteran killer, and not someone to mess around with.

*****************

Sprinting on the edge of the street, Garen did not sense any tracking behind him. He gradually slowed down and quickly returned to the same posture as the average shopping person, looking left and right.

Although the inner courtyard was very chaotic, there were not many who would strike openly on some of the monitored streets. In many places, once someone began an assault, there would be people who would come over to maintain order. These people who maintained order were not from the Administrative Bureau. Instead, some of them looked like students, obviously the managing gang of the area here.

Whenever an assault occurred, it was natural for the gang and manager of the site to be responsible for the aftermath.

There was no good or evil here, no compassion nor mercy.

As Garen strolled along, he had seen a lot of that. A pure and beautiful young girl with two watery eyes had been lured into the alley by several bad students. After half a minute, it was the shrieking of the few bad students that was heard instead.

Several lovely girls who looked like they were going shopping were quarreling with someone at the entrance of a shop. One of the girls was hot-tempered and she slapped a seemingly strong-looking bald man. Both of his arms were fractured as his whole person flew more than ten meters away.

Of course, not all cases were of this contrast. But throughout the way, all of those people who dared to shop on the streets was not someone to be messed with. They either had powerful capabilities or they had at least some objects for body protection on them.

The inner courtyard was always in chaos. There was no difference even in those street areas that had people in charge of them.

Robbery, fighting, revenge, high-energy gunfire, semi-mechanized armor brawls and small-sized spacecraft chasing battles; for people who were generally weaker without special means, even walking on the street was an extremely absurd thing.

Garen had nearly been affected several times. The horrific strength of thermal weapons was something that even he did not want to experience himself.

As he carefully rushed back, he began to think about the means used by the man he had just met.

At the same time, he quickly checked on his wristwatch, which could connect to the inner courtyard network here and access tons of information that could not be found in the outside world.

Soon, a job other than pilot appeared in front of Garen.

‘Energy machinist — a powerful career that uses various biochemical technology and mechanical intelligence to create bodyguards, tools, experimental platforms, and more. One needs a special kind of Willpower and mastery over a lot of professional knowledge, which is divided into many schools. There are energy machinists who focus their research on warfare and there are the scientific kinds of energy machinists who research on drugs.’

“Energy machinist?” Garen suddenly recalled the Glowing Radiance Training Method, the kind that did not have any combat power. That had been seen during the trade with the Honorable Noble.

“Wasn’t biochemical modulation technology eliminated many years ago? How is it that the inner courtyard actually has energy machinists, such talents who could master biochemical machinery?”

He was slightly curious and continued to inquire.

‘Energy machinists differs from modulation engineers, who used biochemical pools in the ancient times. They mainly rely on mechanical intelligence and used biochemical technology as a supplement. This has a lot of advantages over modulation engineers. The biggest point is that they can have their own research platform and use it to synthesize many materials and components which are needed for high-end Mechs. It can accelerate the repair and treatment of high-end Mechs, improve technology and strengthen their power and other comprehensive maintenance.’

‘The numbers of energy machinists in the inner courtyard are extremely few. Often, their own actual combat capabilities are not high but they have a good relationship with many high-end pilots. They are one of the rare talents.’

Garen looked through the data carefully and skimmed through other special rare occupations. He found that besides pilots, there were energy machinists and biochemists, two of the most complex professions. He already had some understanding towards energy machinists. If the role an energy machinist played for the pilot was to concentrate on the maintenance and treatment of the Mech, then the biochemist was responsible for the treatment and maintenance of the pilot.

‘Biochemist — a special occupation based on pharmacy, biochemistry, and virology. Many biochemists advanced from the doctors’ profession. They are mainly responsible for the high-end treatment of injuries, treatment of congenital diseases, intractable diseases and various troublesome illnesses of high-level pilots. Their status is more sublime than that of the energy machinist and their numbers are extremely few.’

There were no other special and rare occupations worthy of attention anymore.

“Energy machinists are responsible for the repair and maintenance of high-end Mechs. That being said, the general maintenance factories are unable to meet the needs of high-end pilots. In this way, an energy machinist would surely master the secrets of many high-end Mechs. Tsk tsk… What a huge network…” Garen was secretly astonished. “With a talent like this, touching him would equate to meddling with an entire interest group.”

“I’m sure biochemists would be similar as well.”

Suddenly, he was moved in his heart. With his biochemistry attainments, it should be a lot easier for him than the average person to become a biochemist.

Plus, the potential points might also be able to help. These two kinds of occupations were more suitable for him to build potential background forces and be the main strategy to buy him time to grow up.

“However, both professions need special training in non-combat Willpower. This is a troublesome condition,” Garen pondered about the solution while walking towards Professor Van Doe’s little villa.

Upon returning to the villa, he approached the smart hub, Hill, right away and asked of the whereabouts of the professor. It was almost time for a lecture. Just a few days after entering the inner courtyard, he had almost forgotten that Professor Van Doe would have a lecture once every five days.

“You’re asking about biochemist and energy machinists? Every student is interested in these two professions. Of course, they’ve all failed,” Hill laughed at him mercilessly. “There are no relevant training methods for biochemists. There are two for energy machinists though. You can choose to buy one and minor in it.”

Sitting on the wooden sofa in the living room on the first floor, Garen sighed with relief.

“What’s the price?”

“I’ll give it to you cheaper. Rounding it up, it is two hundred quest points,” Hill mentioned a random price. This guy was clearly aiming for the two hundred quest points that Garen had just obtained. He could check the account of every student who entered the villa to know how many quest points they have. He really was a profiteer.

“Which two are they?” Garen was not bothered by it. Quest points or whatever, he could go and snatch them if there was not enough. He was never a good person.

“Wow, you really want to buy. But judging by your aptitude, you may be able to do a good job in this energy machinist line. Many genius pilots will choose to minor in this occupation. After all, who is willing to let the secrets of their future high-end Mechs fall into the hands of others? Am I not right? Many of the energy machinists whom I have seen in the inner courtyard have a similar temperament as you.”

“Forget about it, Hill. How many times have you said this to me since the beginning? After coaxing so many people, you’re still trying to coax a new junior!” a woman strode into the living room.

This woman had large bones and was taller than the average person. She looked like a female giant and was more than two meters tall, donning a red dress that contrasted her pale yellow long hair.

Behind the woman were a tender-looking young boy and a young girl. The two were of youthful age, estimated to be only eighteen or nineteen years old. They actually had the symbol of a freshman on their clothes.

“These are the two juniors selected by Teacher this time, Milo and Nehri,” the woman introduced to Garen with a smile, “I’m your senior sister, Galafil, born with giant disease. Don’t mind it.”

Garen smiled and stood up

.

“I’m Nonosiva. You guys can just call me Nono,” he got up and the left-over bloody smell from the earlier murder instantly diffused. Galafil squinted her eyes a little.

This guy… was not a simple character…

Gallafil had originally thought that this junior, just like the others, needed some guidance before daring to lead a normal life in the inner courtyard. She did not expect this guy to be someone not of good nature as well.

The two freshmen, Milo and Nehri, had a sense of closeness as they looked at Garen. Apparently, their similar identities as newcomers naturally narrowed their distance in between.

Milo was the little boy. He was going to try to talk to Nono but was slightly pulled back by Senior Sister.

Chapter 881: Planning 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen sized up these two people. They were obviously newcomers who had not experienced any battle or endeavors. They might not even have an understanding of the environment and the competition system in Blackboard Academy itself.

Slightly revealing a smile, Garen’s line of sight shifted to his senior sister, Galafil.

“Tomorrow should be the time for teacher’s lecture. Do you know if the other two senior brothers will come?”

“Maybe yes, but one of them went to the annular meteorite belt. It might be a long time before he comes back,” Galafil said casually and sat down with the two newcomers.

Garen did not mind and sat down.

“Alright, Hill, let’s continue our trade from just now.”

“No problem, no problem!” the smart hub, Hill, answered quickly.

Soon, a transparent light screen appeared before Garen. There were countless densely-packed numbers and lines flowing on it. They then quickly stopped and only showed two lines of words.

“These are the energy machinist training methods you wanted. They are the latest training methods that anyone can practice though it may take a little longer time…” Hill laughed.

“A little longer?” Galafil, who was watching coldly from the side, interjected with disdain, “Not even one percent of progress in a year is still called ‘a little’?”

Obviously, she intended to remind Garen that it was a pit that he would not be able to come out from once he jumped in.

“Just because you couldn’t do it doesn’t mean others can’t,” Hill retorted. “I can see that Nono is clearly not an ordinary person and maybe he really does have the composition of an energy machinist. Once you become an energy machinist, there would absolutely be no problem living it up!”

“Wasn’t that the same thing you once told me?”

“That is because your own aptitude couldn’t succeed, who can you blame? I had always reminded you and hinted you since the beginning but in the end, you…”

One person and one core started quarreling with each other.

Garen could not be bothered about the argument between the two but simply glanced at the description above.

‘Energy machinist training method — NIS: An orthodox school founded by the ancient Elsie Republic’s grandmaster, Neer. They have the most standard advancement progress of an energy machinist. Their level of fusion of machinery and biochemistry was second to none. They were mainly famous for the manufacturing of flying-insects type of energy machinery.’

‘Training method special skills: Each level enhances the experimental platform to produce energy machinery with 0.5 level of basic defense, 0.5 level of speed.’

‘Energy mechanist training method — Laura Wireless Control: a cumulative training method created by the mystery grandmaster energy machinist, Laura. The most special characteristic of the experimental platform is its cumulative nature. It will naturally create a high intelligence combat energy machinery every other year and their numbers will depend on the level of the platform. Energy machinery does not impose any Willpower burden on the energy machinist. It is an automated intelligent control but the defect is that it may be affected by possible electromagnetic influences. If there are enough materials and energy resources, then it is easy to create an army of energy machinery. The prerequisite is, of course, a sufficiently large platform control.’

‘Training method special skills: Each stage can increase the upper limit of the mechanical capacity of the platform by 1 (all the energy machinist’s energy machinery have an initial upper limit of 1) and each level can reduce the consumption of energy machinery manufacturing by 5%.’

‘Take note: The above training method may consume more time and more resources.’

Looking at these two types of energy machinist training methods, Garen also roughly understood that the main strength of an energy machinist would be coming from the energy machinery and that the manufacturing process of energy machinery required a lot of resources and energy.

“This is a job which only wealthy people can afford. Even if it is a rich person, spending too much energy on the energy machinist training method would not yield a good future all the same,” Galafil was watching by the side. She sounded casual but was in fact, reminding Garen.

“Are energy machinists able to extract the materials themselves?” Garen suddenly asked.

“Of course,” Hill replied quickly. “Any energy machinist can purify or synthesize materials like metals. Of course, he would need an energy furnace.”

“Then I want… NIS,” Garen chose this as his attempt.

He did not forget that he had acquired a similar training method, Glowing Radiance, from the Honorable Nobles.

That training method was very bizarre. It only emphasized the design of the biochemical modulation pool.

“No problem!” Hill was instantly joyful and giggled. With the sound of a ring, all the quest points in Garen’s account were swept away.

The NIS training method also appeared in the database of his wristwatch. He lowered his head and began to look it up slowly.

For a moment, the people on the sofa slowly quietened. Galafil and the duo also noticed this change. There was nothing to say. They began chatting in a small voice, their volume lowered by a lot.

Garen quickly glanced through the NIS training method and found that it was not very similar to Glowing Radiance Training Method. However, there was something in common. Both mentioned a very important object, the biochemical modulation pool.

The mainstream of an energy machinist was to concentrate on creating a variety of energy machinery with semi-Willpower control. Whether they were auxiliary type, combat type or logistics type, each type could have a great application. Many of these creative technologies could even revolutionize the technology of the entire industry. They were the top-level scientific research talents.

Of course, the basic learning knowledge required was also enormous. Besides the basic sciences which had about twenty-something fields themselves, there was also advanced high-level learning, high-energy mathematics, magnetic field research, energy-saving magnetic materials, nano-electronics, nano-biotechnology, cyclical fusion energy bases… and all sorts of research sciences.

Even though there were training methods to improve brain intelligence, many things had simply reached the level of pure aerial. One had to establish a model from physical reality, calculate and find the formula patterns, use these formulas to infer new formulae and then use them to calculate all kinds of physical phenomena to derive a new physical model. Building on this foundation, quantum computers were then used for the accumulation of phenomena or the qualitative transformation of phenomena to form the ultimate desired state… A primary state…

This was the process that a primary target state needed to reach. In the midst of it, it involved numerous basic constants, basic calculations and various types of complicated work. There must also be a sufficiently powerful quantum computer, otherwise, it would not have the capabilities to calculate and deduce.

The primary state may be the most common application environment parameter on many energy machinist’s platforms. Tens of thousands of parameters were always needed on the platform.

When understanding up to this point, Garen finally understood why energy machinists were so rare. It seemed that the degree of complexity involved in all this was far from the perception of those pilots who relied on natural talent to have their way.

However, there was a slight advantage to be an energy machinist. Its training method could be learned by anyone. The government never restricted this aspect of content. It did not require any kind of identity or the likes to be able to learn it. But even so, without a vast accumulation of knowledge, resources and wealth as reserves, it was impossible for an energy machinist to develop even a single hair.

“True enough, what a burning-money industry…” Garen sighed.

“If you have tons of money, you don’t have to be afraid of anything. Of course, there are too many people with too much money, but the possibility of becoming an energy machinist is only one in ten-thousandths,” Galafil took up the cup of coffee delivered by the smart hub and sipped it.

Garen silently nodded, sorted out the information obtained and returned directly to his room. He did not have any intention to communicate with the other two newcomers.

Milo stood up and tried to stop him but Galafil pulled him back and shook her head slightly. He could only watch as Garen entered his room, closed the door and made a locking beep sound.

“Senior sister, why didn’t you let me…” Milo sat down, confused, and looked at Galafil. He knew that the other person had a good heart and was not like that kind of person who deliberately did bad things.

Nehri, who was beside him, was also puzzled and looked over. Obviously, she had also had this doubt in her heart.

Galafil put down her coffee.

“The guy is not an average person. He has killed people.”

What…

In two exclamations, both Milo and Nehri were frightened. They were new students who had just entered the academy, chosen because of some special relationship and was brought in by Professor Van Doe, not due to achievement but relations.

“Don’t provoke him,” Galafil said bluntly. “There is a kind of people who, on the surface, can speak gently in conversations and looks very good-tempered. But once the tables are turned, he can eat you up in an instant without leaving any bones.”

“That person is also a freshman, right?” Milo’s face paled as he asked. Killing someone? Never mind killing someone, he even had never used a knife to kill chickens before. Seeing others fight would also terrify him.

Nehri, who was beside, was similar. She clutched at Milo’s arm tightly.

“There are also big differences among freshmen,” Galafil shook her head. “It will be alright if you don’t provoke him in any way.”

As time passed, Garen had spent eight or nine days at Teacher Van Doe’s place. It was time for the appointment with Anda.

Every day, he merely stayed behind closed doors in the villa and studied the newly acquired training method while accumulating enough potential points to spare.

Galafil and the other senior brothers were here. As expected, both of them had Level Five Willpower. At the same time, their Resonance Degrees were at New-Moon level and they had their own Mechs. The two even had a space button; this sort of thing was a space object that could instantly store and release the Mech. This was an eye-opener for Garen. It was the first time he had seen space storage technology that he had only seen in novels previously.

Then, there was teacher Van Doe’s lecture.

Without any intention of waiting for the progress of Garen and the two newcomers, Van Doe talked on and on for an hour. Various kinds of parameters and conventional formulae needed to be remembered. Many formulae further produced even more complex formulae. Overlapping one another, they finally formed a complex Willpower resonance skill — Sand Eagle, which was a combination of hundreds of complex theoretical theories and numbers.

This was a true resonance technique that was summed up by Van Doe using Crouched Eagle Talon. He continuously deduced Crouched Eagle Talon, which had only five levels, and finally, after years of calculation, he had finally gotten this resonance skill, Sand Eagle, which could increase resonance degree.

This resonance technique was rather strange. At least, it seemed so to Garen. This was because as long as it was constantly practiced, it would slowly increase Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower and the Mech’s resonance degree. This resonance technique was not used for fighting at all but for cultivation instead.

Furthermore, it could not be replaced by computers. Each time, one had to calculate from scratch and simulate it in the brain. From this kind of simulation calculations, the Willpower would produce different calculation fluctuations and affect the Mech’s core. The specific principle involved resonance theory. This world’s resonance theory had far surpassed the foundation of Garen’s own research and exploration in the Totem World and had reached a very high level.

During these days in the villa, Garen continuously absorbed these highly sophisticated knowledge systems. With his collection of the broadcast knowledge systems of several worlds, Garen actually felt that it was very difficult to cope with these things. He had only managed to deduce Sand Eagle to around 60% on his own before he was stuck. He was able to break through the previous techniques, but the later parts involved further various types of calculations. Even when he calculated until his brain felt like exploding, it was still not clear. Many times, he would feel dizzy as the calculations went on and on.

During this time, the two newcomers Milo and Nehri finally experienced the cruelty of the inner courtyard.

From the few days that they went out, they would return with swelling faces, many bruises on their bodies and sometimes even with limps. Galafil did not interfere. After all, the two had to stand independently in the inner courtyard sooner or later. If she intervened as she pleased, it would be very bad for their growth.

Moreover, the most important thing was that in the inner courtyard, veterans like them were not invincible. Professor Van Doe had old students. Other mentors also had old students. Everyone had their own troubles and opponents, and problems as such.

The two children also seemed to have integrity and were unbending. They insisted on not seeking help from their senior sisters or brothers when they came back but suffered alone.

Fortunately, although they all came back with injuries every day, each time they would recover quite well. The treatment conditions in the villa were still not too bad. Dealing with these kinds of external injuries did not take too much time to resolve. The people who bullied them also seemed to know to weigh their actions. There were no serious injuries that would cause sequela. After draining the pool to get the fish[1], they knew that there was no more income for them.

Creak!

Milo was sitting in the living room while Nehri was helping him bandage his calf. He turned his head and saw that Nonosiva’s room door had opened, after days of him not coming out.

Chapter 882: Planning 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen walked out the door. He saw that Milo and Nehri were covered in injuries but his face remained expressionless. He just calmly found Hill the smart hub, asked about something, then strode out of the living room door and walked towards the door.

“Be careful! There are people guarding outside!” Milo saw an unsuspecting Garen heading out and quickly shouted to him kindly. “There are a lot of people out there guarding and waiting for us to go out!” his face was red from embarrassment, having to admit that those people were all here because of them.

Since they could be easily bullied and robbed, this had caught the attention of more and more people. Everyone wanted to come and have a share.

Nonosiva was also a newcomer. If he was robbed due to their own affairs, Milo would feel very guilty.

“I’m not the same as you,” Garen said without looking back.

Stepping out of the door, when his footsteps had just landed on the ground of the street, a group of vicious-looking students came up from both sides of the villa and encircled him.

None of these students had the elite temperament that they once had when there were selected to enter the Inner Courtyard. They had been completely transformed by the brutal competition system of the Inner Courtyard.

“You guys… are obstructive!” Garen looked around and roughly estimated the level of the people here. There were fifteen people in total, a mix of males and females, but the most powerful force field was only of Level Three.

“Boy, what are you talking about?! We do remember the old students of this villa. With this face of yours, you still want to pose as an old man and scare us? Wake up!” a fat woman with a scar on her face sneered.

“Hand over your quest points and your Universal Units!”

“Don’t make us use our fists!”

A group of people snickered.

Milo saw this scene from the living room and instantly felt anxious. He wanted to rush out to save the man but was suddenly held back by a big hand. Looking back, it was big sister Galafil.

“Senior sister, you!”

“Don’t be noisy! That new student is not a rookie like you,” Galafil looked solemnly at the back of Garen. “Watch closely. Even as a newcomer, what a great difference there is between you two. If you want revenge, there is still a long way to go!”

Milo was stunned.

Boom!!

At this instant, a frantic storm suddenly rolled across the outside of the villa. When he turned his head around to look again, there was only Nono left. He was holding a person’s head with one hand and dangling him in the air with that person hitting his arm frantically.

Bang!

The man was randomly thrown out by Nono and slammed into a hovering car that just happened to be driving past on the road. The hovering car diverted violently and almost caused a car accident. The owner of the car did not even dare to let out a fart. He made a turn and quickly accelerated to leave. The man rolled down and laid on his back. All the passing vehicles went around him. He seemed to have fainted.

Most of the people from the group who had previously surrounded Nono were seriously injured and unconscious; some had broken arms, some their ribs had collapsed and some had warped thighs, but most of them were bleeding from their nostrils and mouth. Just by one look, one could tell that those serious injuries were directly caused by powerful Willpower.

“All of them were injured by Willpower, and the technique was very precise. There is no one dead, but without recuperating for ten days up to half a month, they shouldn’t even think of getting out of bed. Tsk tsk… how vicious,” Galafil sighed.

“So… so strong!” Milo’s jaw dropped wide open.

“Super…” Nehri clutched Milo’s arm tightly; even when her nails were about to leave marks on it, the two did not notice.

“That guy… has actually helped you cleaned up your mess,” Galafil shook her head. “I was thinking of letting you guys have more training.”

Milos lowered his head, feeling slightly ashamed. He had originally thought that senior sister completely did not care about them.

“Why… He is also a newcomer, why is he so much better than us…!”

“Yeah, similarly a newcomer, but why? Think about it.” Galafil turned and returned to her room, leaving Milo and Nehri to their own thoughts.

When they looked up again, Nonosiva was no longer visible outside the door.

******************

Inner Courtyard Library No.1

A bustling crowd was continuously going up and down the hundreds of stone steps in the library. Everyone was unconsciously keeping a safe distance from others. Though the steps seemed wide, the people behind would rather wait for others to go first, unwilling to get too close together.

There were pairs of black humanoid statues on each side of the steps at every interval of a certain distance.

Garen wore a newly-bought black trench coat and his whole body was thoroughly covered up. He was standing behind a statue of a woman holding a harp, singing with her head down. This suit of clothes had cost him all of his remaining Universal Units. Everything in his account had been spent on these clothes.

It seemed to be just ordinary clothing, but it was a powerful body-fitting armor material with Level Two defense. The most important function was that it could cut off all careful force field detection and search that were below Inherited level so that others could not figure out his level of Willpower.

Even for Inherited level, the salesperson vowed that it would still provide a certain concealment effect. However, according to Garen’s own deduction using an instrument, the most conservative estimation of dealing with Inherited-level Willpower was that its concealing effect would be useful if the other party scanned on a large scale. But, if they paid a little attention, then it would be of no use.

Having suffered such a big loss, he did not feel happy as he did not test it out before leaving.

Pilots and Secret Technique practitioners were different. Once they were unable to respond, they would just be ordinary people who were more powerful than the average person. Garen’s coming here was due to the information obtained from Anda about Fila’s recent work and rest schedule. It had cost him about twenty thousand Universal Units, not cheap at all.

Library No. 1 was a key database for the Inner Courtyard to store orbital particle data and they could not be borrowed away. One could only read the information by entering the library area and using the wireless connection to connect to the database. Upon leaving the library, all information would be deleted automatically. There was a number of administrative staff who would be supervising visitors to prevent copying.

Fila had recently been searching for information about orbital particle data and would come here every day.

Garen quietly leaned behind the statue. There were many people like him, and he looked just like one of those students out for revenge and thus was inconspicuous. This kind of scene was everywhere in the Inner Courtyard. Every day, there were people who were waiting to get their revenge.

Beside him was a pair of a young female and male who were smoking cigarettes. The female’s hair was multicolored but her face and body shape looked good. She glimpsed over at Garen.

“Hey buddy, are you also looking for someone?” she approached with a casual look.

“Yeah, you guys too?”

Garen smiled, looking gentle.

“My sister was beaten up by someone. This time, I found the guy who did it and purposely came to keep watch,” the girl puffed on the cigarette and said bluntly. “Fire Snake, you know him? It was that lad who actually dared to touch my sister.”

She was observing Garen’s expression out of the corner of her eyes, trying to spot a surprised look from the other party. However, Garen was still smiling plainly and seemed to not know the person Fire Snake at all.

“You don’t know Fire Snake?” the boy beside could not help but ask. “Forget it. That person should be reaching soon. Don’t talk to him, pay attention. Crewe’s people are also here.”

Soon, two more males came over and whispered something to that boy, as if discussing something.

A few people took out their ray guns and the atmosphere instantly became tense. The ray guns had a destructive power of Level One. There would not be a problem dealing with ordinary Level One armor and Willpower Level Three students.

Garen took two steps back and gave the crowd enough space. He watched them preparing their weapons, sharp knives, firearms and even a single laser cannon with Level Two power.

This group of people looked like they were ready for war. Using these weapons to deal with Level Four Willpower would not be a problem too. That single laser cannon could completely penetrate the Willpower field formed by Level Four Willpower. The Willpower field was something that could be stimulated individually, but to stimulate it while driving the Mech, that would need Level Five Willpower.

Garen shook his head slightly. This time, he was also well prepared. In order to cope with the Fila’s possible tricks, he had spent millions and even tens of millions of Universal Units. He had also robbed more than a dozen people and used their quest points to buy some decent equipment.

Looking at these people in an undisguised manner, it was obvious that they did not intend to keep it a secret. The other party probably also knew that they would be keeping watch outside.

Just then, a slender and capable figure finally walked out the door of Library No.1.

Fila was in a black tight-fitting outfit and was still wearing a short cloak behind him. The weird thing was that he actually had four eyebrows. There was a pair of long, red eyebrows growing on top of the two eyebrows of an average person.

Behind him were three people who seemed to be bodyguards. Each was emanating the fluctuation of Willpower fields.

The group walked out of the library. All the passers-by around made way and did not dare to be too close to the group of people.

“It’s Fila!”

“Fila who ranks top five. Tsk tsk. I heard that he was challenged by Reyla, who ranks at ninth place, today. They should be going to the battleground now,” a group of people who were keeping watch beside Garen discussed in whispers.

“Britney personally entered the Inner Courtyard some time ago and talked with Fila for more than ten minutes. Don’t know if it’ll have any impact on the North District.”

“Who knows? If whatever that was discussed by the top-levels could be randomly guessed by us, it would be peculiar.”

A group of people discussed in low voices.

The multicolored-haired girl sighed as she listened to the group’s frivolous chat. Unwilling to say much, she was bored and shifted her gaze back to her side.

“!!!”

Garen was assembling a single combined missile silo here!

A six-meter tall missile silo was almost completely assembled by this guy! And the direction of the aim…

The girl looked back and immediately felt her heart slowed down by half a beat. It was aiming at Fila’s group!

“You, you, you, you, you!!!!” she pointed to Garen and for a moment, she could not even speak clearly.

In an instant, she saw Garen taking out one thing after another from underneath his clothes.

High-powered explosives, a high-energy radiation gun, disposable biochemical acid bombs, an orbital field generator that was at least Level Five power and worth ten million! This terrifying range of weapons, with the lethality of minimum Level Four, was casually brought out by Garen.

The other people here were suddenly attracted by the things laid out by Garen. They were all dumbfounded.

These things, without tens of millions of Universal Units and hundreds of quest points, were nearly impossible to acquire.

Using tens of millions of Universal Units to smash someone…

If these things were to be used outside, they could destroy more than half of the city!

Chapter 883: Sneak Attack 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I… I… F…!!” the multicolored-haired girl could not close her mouth and was utterly shocked.

All kinds of mass-destructive weapons and powerful bombs that were only used against air battleships, so many of these were being brought out by this guy at one go!

Such a big move was naturally unable to be completely concealed. Exclamations were just heard at Garen’s side when Fila looked over here. At first sight, the two’s vision instantly locked onto each other.

With a boom, the six-meter-high silo suddenly fired a white stream of light. It made a perfect circular arc as it was accurately aimed at Fila below, racing towards him.

The two were hundreds of meters apart. The stone steps of the library were very wide, roughly more than two hundred meters. At this time, it was too late too to dodge. Fila’s pupils instantly constricted.

“Spread out!”

He only had time to yell.

Several people behind him their faces immediately changed. They promptly separated and leaped away but were still a step too late.

A mass of blinding white light exploded, covering a hundred meters area of the entire flight of steps. Many innocent students were also caught up in it.

The more than five-meters-high aurora missile, with its instant high heat explosion, could destroy a Level Five Willpower field more than a dozen times in a flash. Even so, it could be neutralized if there were more Level Five Willpower fields because it would level out the power of the missile.

Intense light and heat burst forth, and Fila could only feel a scalding sensation. His clothes were singed and burned instantaneously. Everything around him was pale white and nothing could be seen at all. He let out his Willpower field in the form of a great snake but was still hit by the huge blast, and blood spurted out from his mouth.

“Damn you!!!”

He hollered. It was the first time in his life that he suffered so much damage. He forcefully withstood the energy field of the aurora missile and darted towards Garen, who was not far away.

But just then, he saw that Garen had just released several automatic tracking-type radiation bombs, which were flying over. The bombs were like small fishes that were being released, creating circular arcs from all directions and surrounding here.

“Good luck,” Garen lifted his hand to his forehead and he flicked it lightly. He smiled and turned around to leave.

Blazing light and heat erupted again. At that moment, it was as if there were numerous birds shrieking at the same time. The large number of bombs and horrific weapons released by Garen, with their automatic tracking devices, all hit the target at the same time. The explosion caused Fila to be shaken to the core and his Willpower field had not been stabilized yet. At this instant, the pilot’s Willpower was out of control and could not be controlled.

A thick black smoke broke out behind. Harsh sirens could be heard all over the city.

Garen made several jumps and swiftly landed on the top of a hovering car. He stood up and turned his head back to look at the scene he had made.

At the entrance of the library, a pillar of smoke continued to rise to the sky. It was also mingling with Fila’s unwilling angry roars but he was entangled with the energy field generator and so, was unable to get out.

“True enough, there sure is a difference in using a huge amount of money to buy a force field generator that can immobilize battleships. The effect is so powerful.” Garen touched his chin and pondered. “Including this set of clothing, all the money that was robbed from others and this month’s income had all been used up.”

He looked at his wristwatch and there were three hundred and thirty-one Universal Units left.

“This is the power of wealth…but I have to prevent others from dealing with me the same way.”

Nonetheless, Garen knew that others could not have had such terrific actuarial power like him, who could calculate Fila’s counteractions against some of the explosive force of the weapons and how much damage the remaining destructive force would cause.

This scene that Garen made, its power seemed horrific and even Level Five energy fields without a New-Moon Level resonance degree would also perish. However, after Fila’s full resistance, the residual lethality was, in reality, not as terrible as imagined. At the most, it would heavily injure Level Three and Two ordinary students. This did not violate the regulation of no killing within the monitored area.

Garen had used more than a dozen small binding force field tools to lock all the power within a certain range simultaneously. At the moment of explosion, these binding force field tools would detonate together. As one-off props, they would offset a part of the explosion power and at the same time, blow away those who were unrelated. This was the real reason that the death of other students had been avoided.

Explosive range, possible blasting points around the lethality parameters, possible responses from Fila, and the timely use of the force field generator to prevent Fila from running around and causing the tracking blast to impact others.

All of these had been designed by Garen through multiple simulated environments and computer modeling several hundred times before he’d come up with a perfect action plan.

“This is the terrifying part about high IQ crimes…” looking at his own hands, Garen himself felt that he was terrible.

“I don’t know how the situation of that Fila guy is. He should be expected to be either seriously injured or crippled. I’ve spilled part of the strength of his energy field,” Garen smiled and looked in the direction of the library. It was only a shrinking cube at this time.

*********************

“Ah… Ah!!!!!”

Boom!!

A statue was broken by Fila and it flew out tens of meters.

He was surrounded by thick black pythons and looked like an ancient deity, except that his clothing was tattered, his body was blue-black here and there, and more than half of his hair had been burned off, like a featherless rooster. His original display of powerful force and his prestige were all lost with this ridiculous image.

He vented by smashing the statues around him ferociously and his body was releasing black smoke. He looked more like a refugee who had fled here from somewhere.

A few of his men around him had also been hurt but apparently, they were in a much better state than he was. This bombing attack was obviously targeted at him alone. All the lethality was restrained by the force field binding device in a small range and he took about 80% of it.

This horrific calculation and accuracy made Fila felt uncomfortable at this moment.

The most important thing was that the other party’s use of such brutal measures had not yet triggered the participation of the city Administrative Bureau’s automatic management mechanism. Thus it was clear that such a method had not even cost the life of an ordinary student except for heavy injuries at the most. In this era, as long as there was enough money, one who was heavily injured could be restored or even have their limbs replaced.

“This is the terrifying part…” after Fila had vented for a while, his heart gradually returned to its original calmness. The colorless silver-streaked internal armor on his body slowly lit up and continued to flow. This was also the main reason he had not been seriously injured in the sneak attack just now. Such a high-tech internal armor had counteracted most of the lethality, but it also looked like it had to be scrapped.

“…accurate to this point, it seems that the one who did this is not an average person…” Fila pulled off his tattered top and internal armor and swept his eyes across the onlooking students. The surrounding people felt as if they had fallen into an ice cave and swiftly retreated. There were not many people who were watching the excitement, to begin with. They were afraid that they would be dragged into it. After being frightened by him, everyone scattered like birds and animals and there was not a silhouette left to be seen.

His three men moaned as they crawled up from the ground. One had his arm blown off while half of the body of another was almost scorched. The last person had lost his hearing.

Looking at the terrible condition of his men, Fila was furious. He was suddenly attacked and even his own men were also tragically hurt.

“Find out!! Go find out!! Find out that guy’s identity, patronage, find it all out!!” he roared, unable to suppress his rage.

The thunderous roars echoed non-stop. Fila’s terrifying Willpower field continued to fluctuate like a turbulent river. Ordinary people might not see it, but a powerhouse on the same level could see that he was not lightly hurt.

Tens of millions of Universal Units had been burned at the same time and could destroy most of the city in the outside world. Now, all of them were gathered together at one point for him to bear it all. Even if this guy were to have countless of life-saving props, the energy field was so powerful that it was enough to confront the Red-White Shining Mech’s pilot. At this time, he was also dazed by this money-laden surprise attack.

“Tsk tsk tsk… how awkward…” at the bottom of the steps, a tall man in a green trench coat led a group of people out of the car and walked up the stone steps. The leading man was like a natural leader. There was a peaceful yet depressed feeling of heaviness. He had exquisite facial features and skin. People could not help but wonder if he underwent plastic surgery.

“The ranking changes every day. It seems that today, I, Reyla, can pick up a good bargain,” the man in the green trench coat snapped his fingers lightly and all of a sudden, all around him were crowds of people. One by one, Level Three and Level Four students slowly came out of hiding. There were a total of twenty or thirty people, all wearing green badges, obviously the subordinates of the man in the green trench coat.

“Reyla, you think you can win against me because I’m injured?” Fila’s bronze-colored upper body was naked as he stared straight at the man below.

“Win against you?” the contemptuous man shook his head slightly. “It took me so much of effort to get so many people here. It’s not to win you, but… to kill you!!”

Before his voice had faded away, all the green badge students around glowed green at the same time. With a bang, a huge green net was agglomerated. It instantly enclosed Fila and his men with the speed of light.

“This is! Dimensional ion defense field!” Fila’s expression finally changed.

“Yeah yeah, it’s that. I managed to acquire some of its wreckage sixty-five years ago, spent tons of money to deduce and perfect it. Please don’t disappoint me…” Reyla grinned, his eyes flashing with a fox-like radiance.

A total of more than thirty people’s Willpower had been gathered together at the same time to form a huge torrent energy field, suppressing Fila’s group of four in it.

“Break through!!” with a fiery roar, Fila no longer held back. His whole body’s Willpower resonated and a seemingly rhythmic pulsing black light spread out in circles of powerful force field, which counteracted the pressure from the surrounding energy field.

His entire person was like an arrow released from the bowstring. As the explosion under his feet produced a huge driving force, he charged towards the front where Reyla was at.

*****************

“How spectacular…” looking far into the green reticle erected in the distance, Garen gently jumped down from the top of the hovering car. He twisted both his feet, directly counteracting the inertia force and landed lightly on a bridge above the road.

In the direction of Library No.1, clouds of green smoke rose and a giant bowl-shaped green reticle was clearly visible. However, the strange thing was that there were no vehicles of the Administrative Bureau moving towards that side. Obviously, the guy who made his move later on also had a powerful background. Under such circumstances, the Administrative Bureau could only choose to turn a blind eye and simply stand neutral.

“I say, no wonder those weapon bombs were sold to me so easily. Now it seems that someone had planned it. This guy is very calculating and even wanted to drag me into it. Luckily, I left in time,” Garen put his hands into the pockets of his pants and took out a pair of sunglasses. The moment he put the sunglasses on, his entire face had begun to have a slight change. His body contours and features began to give off an obscure feeling. Although his body’s strong muscles were still in shape, he now looked completely different from the previous image.

Chapter 884: Sneak Attack 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“But so many lethal weapons actually could not kill him!” Garen frowned slightly. The strength of Level Five Half-Moon level had exceeded his expectations. It even could increase the force field to this extent. This kind of defense field, would it be comparable to the average Level Five Mech?

The weapons he had used in one breath, although their power was diffused, should not have been able to be withstood by the human body.

“It seems like that there is some kind of life-saving defense on him, similar to Goldfish.”

He was not afraid of the other party coming to his doorstep. Prior to the fact that Fila wanted to get rid of him, both sides had already bred enmity. As a Secret Technique practitioner himself, alertness was at its peak at all times. He was not afraid at all of others’ secret attacks because he was much stronger in this area as compared to other pilots.

As for the involvement of relatives, such things might be left unattended in the Outer Courtyard. However, in the Inner Courtyard, especially the conflicts among powerhouses, no one would do such a stupid thing. Each powerhouse was of either Level Four with resonance degree, Level Five or even Level Five with resonance degree. These powerhouses, if pushed too far and lurked as assassins, no common guard on the outside would be able to withstand them. One had to know that in the outside world, any pilots with Level Three or Level Four Willpower were able to lead a very good life. The cost of hiring was extraordinarily expensive. It also depended on the hirer’s qualification and whether the pilots were willing.

Once the rule was broken and powerhouses with Level Five Willpower or with resonance degree lurked as assassins or terrorists, this kind of lethality, just by looking at the previous Red-White Shining Mechs, one would know that with just a few people, they could destroy an entire big city. This was in fact, a result of a direct confrontation. If it were to happen in the dark… That was why the fight between powerhouses primarily targeted the opponent itself. Only the pilots who really had no scruples would use the means of dying together.

Putting aside all these, Garen recalled the energy field that Fila had released just a moment ago. That split-second outburst of energy field force was definitely his true level, and he compared the gap with his own energy field.

He held out his hand and strands of invisible, soft energy field gradually covered the back of his hands as if they were made of water, seemingly without any big defensive force.

“The restorative power from the training method given by Red Moon is strong enough, but it does not have any defensive force at all. It should be part of a certain type of combination training method,” he guessed. “There must be another part of the training method that specializes in defensive attacks.”

The more he practiced during these times, the more he had the feeling that this training method had been split up.

Looking up again at the quivering green and black lights in the direction of the library, it was clear that the guys that showed up later had engaged Fila.

“Should I go and have a look?” Garen rubbed his chin.

The quivering became stronger and suddenly, the black swelled sharply, instantly occupying the upper hand. This made Garen’s eyes narrowed slightly.

“Looks like he has used another hidden card… He’s certainly a baron who had lived for so many years. There are so many cards up his sleeve that can be used,” Fila’s appearance seemed to be, if not less than half, one-third of his actual age.

Garen carefully calculated. Although he did not remember specifically how long he had lived, he might be estimated at four or five hundred years old. Tallying up his years from a few worlds, it had unknowingly been this long.

Fila’s data did not explicitly mention his age, but it could also be roughly estimated that he should be two hundred years old. His appearance looked young but he was actually an old man.

The enhancing of life through the means of science and technology, plus a resonance degree, was enough to ensure a person who had authority and money would easily live past two hundred years old.

Seeing that Fila had regained the upper hand, Garen gave up his thoughts of going back to the watch the battle and slowly walked down the bridge. A few guys from the Administrative Bureau had rushed in front of him, hands holding high-energy ray guns.

“It’s this area, how come it has disappeared!!? It should be here according to the route of that car!”

“It may be around! Find it!”

One of them grabbed Garen’s clothes.

“Hey! Did you see this person passing by here?!” he straightaway turned his wristwatch and pulled up an image of a familiar face while yelling at Garen.

Garen looked at it. It was actually the image of his disguised face earlier on.

He shook his head.

“No, I only saw a dark shadow flashed past and disappeared… Officer, is this person a wanted criminal?” he had a calm, fearless, but somewhat curious mien.

Such a demeanor was common in the Inner Courtyard. Some geniuses with a bit of capability would always have this kind of expression.

Seeing Garen responded calmly, that person also eased up and shook his head, obviously afraid of offending someone inexplicably.

“Not a wanted criminal, just a person who had messed with someone he shouldn’t mess with… It’s misfortunate for this boy. Alright then, thanks a lot, buddy.”

He relaxed his arm and walked away. Together with the few other members, they quickly found a direction and ran towards it, disappearing on one end of the flyover quickly.

Garen silently watched those people leave and walked off the bridge from the other end, slowly heading towards the Professor Van Doe’s villa.

*******************

In front of the library

Fila bent over with both hands on his knees. His sweat, a mixture of blood and water, was dripping slowly from his hair to his chin and to the ground.

His original youthful skin was now slowly wrinkling and slackening to that of an older person’s.

“The expenditure of Willpower was too much…” he touched his facial skin. “It has been a long time since I last fought to this kind of degree…”

All his men were unconscious and there was a whole pack of people lying around; all were the men brought by Reyla.

Most of them were seriously injured. No one was killed. After all, even with their statuses, killing elite students in front of everyone would also cause a huge trouble. And so, the two had also restrained the scope of the affected area.

Reyla was half-kneeling on the steps not far away. There were bloody holes three-fingers-wide upon his body and the edges of the wounds appeared charred.

“Still, to have such great strength despite being injured… Indeed, it’s Fila,” he braced himself to stand up. “No wonder I’ve been suppressed by you for so many years. It turns out that you…”

A black line suddenly flashed and fiercely hit Reyla’s body. It flung him away with a thud and he flew into the center of a building behind him that stood opposite the library. He went through the glass and shot into the interior of someone else’s house.

“Go!” Fila yelled. Several black shadows appeared by his side out of thin air, simultaneously carried the unconscious men on the shoulder while helping him rapidly to the hovering car not far away.

The green reticle at the top of the head had been extinguished previously without them noticing.

Fila was fighting back the feeling of fainting. After holding out until he was inside the hovering car and seeing the white-haired old man who was driving, he was finally relieved.

“Return to the residence!”

“Hurry! Reyla being thrown off by Master in one shot is only temporary!” the old man was serious-looking. He could see that at the position where Reyla had been thrown towards, a green translucent tentacle had suddenly popped up, like a marine monster. A huge green octopus with a diameter of four or five meters waved countless of tentacles and wormed through the holes in the building. In the center of the mouthpiece was Reyla, laid spreadeagle. His hair was flying while his face was covered in blood, and his lower body was completely integrated into the octopus.

“Fila! I want you dead!!!”

“Resonance skill? How terrifying!” the old man was shocked at Reyla’s appearance. He looked back at the unconscious Fila and continued to accelerate. “Master shouldn’t have lost to him initially. If it weren’t for that killer… That kind of professional skills, it wasn’t like a regular rookie, definitely a veteran of veterans. The Administrative Bureau actually had nothing on him.”

As for the high-level killings of Reyla and Fila, the Authority Bureau was powerless. Both sides had a vast network of forces behind their back, offsetting each other. What was compared in this kind of situation were their individual strengths.

The old man kept on driving and frantically speeding up until he could not see Reyla’s octopus form. Only then did he slow down.

“While in the state of activated resonance skill, the individual is lacking in speed. Without the help of a Mech, he wouldn’t dare to simply give a chase. It’s still okay, still okay,” he let out a long breath.

“Uncle… Have we got away?” Fila’s somewhat weak voice came from the back.

“Managed to. We have to immediately counteract the other party’s subsequent arrangements. Reyla’s Deep-sea Organization will never let us leave so easily. He had arranged a large number of measures in this duel,” the old man nodded.

“How careless of me. I didn’t expect the killer from the beginning to actually have such a strong simulation actuarial power that he would dare to use so many weapons of mass destruction. And still, he did not kill any elite students!” Fila rubbed one side of his head, both eyes slowly leaking tears of blood. This was the result of excessive use of his Willpower and the aftereffect from the outburst of resonance skill.

“If it weren’t for the first wave of attack that had exhausted at least one-third of your Willpower, you wouldn’t be beaten by Reyla to this state.” The old man nodded.

“What did leader say?” Fila closed his eyes, found a paper towel in the car and wiped away the bloody tears.

“To have you go to the Outer Courtyard and stay away, or perform a simple task and go out to have a walk. Deep-sea has shed all pretense of cordiality and will not stop hunting you,” the old man replied.

“What’s the attitude of Black Rose?” Fila blew out a breath, picked up a bottle of water that had automatically appeared before him and drank a sip, gargled, and spat it out into the retractable trash can in front.

“Similar as Thousand Year Tree, to maintain neutrality. We can’t change their stance since we’re a foreign organization. They have no reason to care about the killings,” the old man replied.

“A group of scum!” Fila fiercely punched into the seat’s real leather. “When leader finishes the plan, all of them will have to die sooner or later!!”

“Master, aren’t you already aligned with Blue Narcissus?”

“That group of vampires just thinks of money, money, money all day long! The details are not yet completely settled, but they are already thinking of money!” Fila said crossly. “It takes too much to reach the target and their appetite is too big.”

“Remember the Willpower of the killer from the sneak attack? This type of high IQ killer must be dealt with as soon as possible, otherwise, it will be very troublesome later on,” The old man remarked in a low voice.

“Remember, but although that person does not have a resonance degree, his combat awareness is very sophisticated.”

“What level of Willpower?”

“It should be around Level Four or Five.”

“Should I inform the three Masters?” the old man took a look at Fila from the rearview mirror.

“Since he is a killer, just hire their old rivals to start with it. Give a reward of one hundred million. Best to capture alive, halve it if he is dead. Put it up on the Exterminet.” Fila gritted his teeth.

“Exterminet? The top killers there only have Level Five Willpower, can it be done?”

“It’s okay. The price floor of Exterminet is too high. We have to keep the money to negotiate with Blue Narcissus, that group of vampires. It is not enough to use that much. Exterminet is sufficient. Moreover, if they cannot do it alone, don’t they know to partner together?”

“Alright then, I will put it up once I get back.”

Chapter 885: Black Flood 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

One punch out.

Garen quietly felt the flow, changes, and the regularity of his own fist.

Retracting his fist again, with a swish, he struck an Axe hand blow.

He was studying a Mech combat technique, the special skill from the Crouched Eagle Talon course. The Willpower combat technique of the Eagle Stream learned in the Outer Courtyard could not be compared to the one from the Inner Courtyard. Because of that, Professor Van Doe specially taught him a type of powerful skill —— Black Wind, which could allow the Crouched Eagle Talon’s Willpower to burst forth for a short while.

This skill was the result of Van Doe’s decades of research, developing the powerful skill of Crouched Eagle Talon’s Willpower to the greatest extent. It could burst out the most powerful Willpower force through both arms in an instant. The principle was very complicated and one would need to feel and distinguish the finest vibration regularities and frequency of change to trigger an intricate chain reaction.

Garen punched out once again and made an exploding air blast in the air, like a firecracker.

“Mech combat techniques are divided into four steps: footwork, technique, killing move, and resonance skill. Footwork can influence the speed of evasion, et cetera. Technique is a conventional battle mode while resonating skill is a special battle trick. These are the strongest points of a pilot.”

“Unfortunately, it is impossible to have resonance skill without owning one’s own Mech. Without resonance skill, it is impossible to defeat Fila…”

Garen knew that the feud between him and Fila was deep-seated. Even if he did not take any action, he himself would make his move. This was an issue of sooner or later.

“The main problem now is to build my own personal Mech, so the energy machinist ability will be crucial… I can extract the materials by myself and even own a small-scale concentrated processing plant.”

Garen practiced the Mech combat technique while alternating between one hand and the other. The depth and precision of Black Wind were far beyond his imagination. Each move had to be accurate to a certain extent, or a careless, subtle error would lead to the emergence of chain errors and in the end, it would not be shaped.

The strength and uniqueness of this Killing Move also gave him great inspiration. At this time, he also integrated it into his own concept of martial arts.

“From the task I’ve agreed upon with Anda, I will be able to obtain Lamda Alloy. This type of material is used to make the main body of the Mech. The index is excellent in all aspects, and it can be considered within the upper-middle tier. After that, it’s the engine skill, kinetic frames system, and Willpower connection system. The main things are the material and engine. Everything else can be bought with money.”

Garen had worked it out. The most important thing in making his own Mech was the material and engine skill, to build up the main body of the shelf first before anything else.

These precious materials were not allowed to be sold on the market. As a medium-high-end Mech material, a type of metal like Lamda was a scarce resource that could not be purchased at all. Everyone would keep it in their own hands.

If you wanted to buy, it would be calculated in terms of millions of Universal Units.

As he experimented with the subtle manipulation of Black Wind, Garen was also constantly pondering the next arrangements within his heart.

Currently, he was aiming to upgrade his Living Secret Technique. But before the needed Red Peacock Stone arrived, he could only start with his personal Mech first. Regarding the area of energy machinist, he could only use his potential points for the time being. With a few points, he could only be considered as beginner level since he had not even reached Willpower Level One. The training method of the energy machinist appeared to be of high level. Without wanting to waste potential points, Garen intended to see whether the advancement of the Living Secret Technique could enhance this Willpower training method together.

If it could be done together, it would save a lot more resources and effort.

With the advancement of the Living Secret Technique, attaining the upgrade of the primary Crouched Eagle Talon, unnamed Willpower and the sub-Willpower of the energy machinist simultaneously and enhancing all three would be of exceptional value to him.

As for the extra potential points, he intended to use all of them to improve his body constitution and the various professional knowledge systems needed in the other aspects of being an energy machinist.

“Black Wind!!”

Suddenly, Garen bellowed as his arms trembled, sending out a black, visible flow of air. It flew in all directions and the black gas vanished within a distance of less than a meter.

However, Garen did not control it well and it almost met him.

Quickly moving sideways, he gave way to the oncoming Black Wind, but his clothes inevitably came into contact with it.

The black training clothes that he had originally put on were instantly destroyed into powdery grains that sprinkled on the ground. A metal button had also been turned into powder.

“Terrific!” Garen narrowed his eyes. “What kind of energy is this? Even metal alloys are so easily destroyed.”

Although the skill he displayed was through the steps given by Teacher Van Doe, he had not figured out the specific principles himself. After all, this thing was only produced by professors of high-end intellect such as Van Doe after decades of research. Furthermore, the scientific and technological level of this world far exceeded those of other worlds that Garen had experienced. For this kind of annihilating phenomenon, Garen was not very clear about it.

Seeing this scene, the initial him who had not been very invested into this skill was now suddenly full of interest in it.

“That kind of energy seems to be very powerful. Try again!”

Garen made an open stance and slowly started to concentrate on following Teacher Van Doe’s instructional steps. Bit by bit, he combined the vibrations, Willpower frequency and a certain amount of mental will guidance. Spirit, Willpower, blood flow and his own movements; these four parts began to gradually combine and condense into a form of invisible symbols and vortexes. These symbol vortexes began to further assemble and formed little pyramids.

A total number of three invisible pyramids, arranged in a triangle, was suspended in front of Garen.

“Black Wind!”

Whoosh…

A subtle black air flow appeared and the three pyramids collapsed at the same time, turning into a black wind, blowing towards the front sector in a fan-shaped cone.

It was billowed in an area of more than a meter before the black wind slowly disappeared.

Garen opened his mouth and suddenly, his vision went black and his body staggered, nearly falling to the ground. Luckily, he quickly reached out and grabbed the chair by his side.

“What a great exhaustion..!” he was secretly shocked. “With my current body constitution and the internal Level Five Willpower, I was actually unable to cope with it after releasing the skill twice. My body was drained and the blood loss is terrible!”

Only after a few minutes of rest did Garen ease back and recover his strength. He wanted to try to release Black Wind once more but unfortunately, without enough blood and spirit, there was no way to use this skill anymore.

In one full day, all of his interest was captured by this skill taught by Professor Van Doe. He began to diligently study it, trying to find out what the mystery of this skill was.

***************

The second floor of the villa

Van Doe was holding a tobacco pipe and slowly smoking it. From time to time, smoke rings were puffed out through his nostrils. They were well-formed, one linked to another, and they gave off a slight satisfaction. Sitting alone in the study room, there was a semi-transparent circular screen on his desk. The image of another person was displayed on it. He was a white-haired old man dressed meticulously in a black suit.

“Still studying the structure of Glass Fire?” Van Doe asked casually.

“Isn’t it the same as you wanting to further your Annihilating Wind?” the old man in the suit answered lightly. “These three stages of Black Wind, Death Wind, and Annihilating Wind, your Crouched Eagle Talon should have reached the peak of the Two-Moon level, right?”

Van Doe smiled.

“It’s a pity… If Crouched Eagle Talon can break through to Level Six and you use it to promote Annihilating Wind, the power will surely rise to a point of terror. The compatibility of the two is really too high.”

“You still haven’t given up after so many years, otherwise you could have reached the seventh Non-falling level,” the old man in the suit said calmly. “In those years you claimed to be invincible within two meters, the close combat of Annihilating Wind defeated the whole academy. Apart from the three big professors, no one was your opponent. But now, look at how many people who were not as good as you were, who are slowly reaching your level and even surpassing you.”

“…Do you still want to persuade me to give up?” Van Doe smoked the tobacco pipe deeply and the smoke at the end of the pipe lit up.

“I have said it too many times. I’m too lazy to say anymore,” the old man in the black suit sighed. “The materials you requested have arrived at the Inner Courtyard warehouse. You can pick them up at any time. In them are some Star Stones that I have toiled to find.”

“Thanks a lot,” Van Doe smiled. “All these years, I’ve been relying on you to help me collect the Star Stones. Whatever trouble you may have, feel free to let me know. Don’t mind it. Although these old bones of mine are not as good as they used to be, they still have some capabilities.”

“If Annihilating Wind Van Doe had no use, then no one in the Inner Courtyard would dare to say that they are still useful,” the old man in the black suit laughed. “Nothing much. Have you received the two kids I sent over?”

“Mm-hmm, they’re the last bloodline of that family?”

“Yeah… I was still a step too late… Similar to the child from the last rubble, everyone else died due to the fragments of Forbidden Mech incident… This time may really require you to go into action during critical moments. My sect’s degree of control in the radiation belt is not as strong as yours. There are a lot of variables in the radiation belt surrounding Blackboard Region recently.”

“Go ahead. Just know that my Black Flood Party will always stand behind you. Don’t worry about it. At the most, I will go to the Polar Region again to look for my seniors,” Van Doe said while laughing.

“Truly, it’s Inheriting big sects like you that are easy-going… Never fighting alone…”

The black suit old man sighed.

The two old men suddenly could not help but laugh.

“Well, this will be it. I have something to deal with here. As for those two children, I’ll be counting on you. They have good talent, which was why I chose them and sent them to you. After all, your conditions over there are much better than here on my side.”

“Got it.”

The screen was instantly turned off and the light also dissipated. It was the projection of a virtual screen.

There was still a smile on Van Doe’s face when all of a sudden, it changed and the smile on his face instantly vanished. He seemed to have noticed something.

“Just now… it seems that someone had released the force field of Black Wind? Could it be Galafil?” his Inherited Killing Move was never covered up because the difficulty of merely releasing it was far beyond the imaginations of ordinary pilots. The calculations and spirit, blood, Willpower, and movements involved required a very sophisticated coordination. Even if it were to be put out in the open for the pilots to cooperate and learn, there would be no way of releasing any bit of Black Wind force field, not to mention the substance of Black Wind.

Van Doe frowned slightly.

“Doesn’t she know that using Black Wind in the villa could easily destroy the building?”

Chapter 886: Black Flood 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Connect me with Hill,” he said plainly.

“Dear master, Hill is here for you,” the smart hub slowly formed a fuzzy black human form on the desk.

“Are Galafil, Kaneer and Ernst all back?”

“No, master. Galafil went to the training ground to teach the two new children. Ernst went out to have a drink with friends and might come back late. Only Kaneer is in the villa now,” Hill replied honestly.

“It’s him. Forget it, he has always been steady and has a sense of proportion,” Van Doe nodded and said no more. As the basic assessment criteria for the official entry into his Inheriting Sect, the difficulty of Black Wind was very scary. Even a Level Three disciple would not use this skill so easily. Presumably, Kaneer had his own thoughts.

As for the other new students in the villa, those students could only be viewed as trainees in the eyes of Van Doe, still under observation. Did they want to use Black Wind? Then they would have to wait for another eight to ten years to see if there would be any chance. At the outset, he himself, as a genius, had to spend three months before unleashing the first Black Wind, and after that, he had fainted on the spot.

For the in-villa trainees, because both parties only had a transactional relationship, so long as they could release the force field of Black Wind, they would be regarded as his entry student. As for such people, even after decades of experience, he had only acquired three people, which were these three disciples. Moreover, they did not originate from Blackboard.

As a large Inheriting sect that spanned across several regions, Black Flood Party had many powerhouses, as numerous as the clouds, even the other major regions would not dare to belittle them. In this area, it was a top ranked powerful sect that was second to none. As long as Black Wind could release a force field albeit, without the real substance, one would be regarded as a disciple of Black Flood Party.

In Black Flood Party, one would be a real top-end genius if one could release the force field of Black Wind within a month. That person would be a top elite who would immediately be qualified to go through the Sect Master assessment. So long as there were no major moral problems, becoming a Sect Master or Divine Wind General was nothing more difficult than nailing a nail into the door panel [1], with nothing more to say.

Soon, another wave of force was poured out. This wave of movement was very subtle and only top powerhouses such as Van Doe could feel it. This time, he laughed instead. The force field of Black Wind was much weaker this time. Indeed, Kaneer had his own sense of proportion.

Tapping the table, he was planning to look at the monitor of Kaneer’s training room. Each disciple and student has their own independent training room. But after giving some thoughts to it, he decided to respect his disciple’s privacy.

Looking at the color of the sky on the outside, the artificial sun showed a subtle yellow glow.

“It’s time for afternoon tea. Hill, arrange for a visit to the tea restaurant.”

“Understood. The transfer has been arranged,” Hill answered quickly.

Van Doe got up and took down his black coat from the hanger and put it on. The door opened automatically. He strode out and walked to a small single room near the second-floor stairs. Inside the room was a cylindrical silver cylinder and inside the cylinder, there were dense electrographic blue-ray lines. In the center of it was a pattern similar to a blue eye, slowly turning around.

Van Doe went to the cylinder.

Swish!

A burst of blue current flashed.

Whoop-whoop! Whoop-whoop!

Suddenly, a sharp siren rang in the villa.

“What’s the matter!?” Van Doe was still not sent away. His face sank. “Hill!” He felt the force field of Black Wind again.

“It was Black Wind that had destroyed the superconducting circuit environment in the wall!” Hill quickly emerged beside him.

“Kaneer, this boy…” Van Doe frowned and strode out of the transfer room.

Before he had stepped down the stairs, he saw Kaneer coming upstairs with a strange look on his face.

“Teacher…” the blond man with a seemingly calm appearance opened his mouth and saw Van Doe with his dark face.

“How many times have I told you, pay attention to the area when using Black Wind, take note of the range, you…”

Whoosh!

Suddenly it was a flash of Black Wind force field again.

Van Doe’s face froze, Kaneer’s face expression was also instantly still.

The two men blinked and looked at each other.

“Just now, was it you who used Black Wind?” Van Doe softened and toned down his voice and asked carefully.

“Wasn’t it Teacher using it?” Kaneer’s expression was interesting. Perplexed, curious and surprised; this handsome young man had a completely puzzled expression.

“Then… are the two of them back?” Van Doe frowned, thought for a moment, and continued to wonder.

“No, I just went to both of their training rooms. Nobody was there, so I came up to see if it was Teacher…” he could not continue with his words. He eyes met with Van Doe’s and instantly, they made from each other’s gaze a guess that was closest to the truth.

“Hill!!!” Van Doe shouted.

“Here!!!”

Hill was frightened and quickly appeared beside the two.

“Which training room was being occupied just now, take me there! Hurry!” Van Doe could not care about anything else at the moment and commanded hurriedly,

“Yes… Yes!!!” Hill was scared and hurriedly floated downwards.

The two, master and disciple, quickly followed behind. The speed of the three almost left behind afterimages.

In a few blinks, they came to the door of a training room.

“The door is locked!” Kaneer pushed the door but failed to open it.

Bang!

Van Doe kicked the door.

The door immediately opened wide. Hill stood by the side and stared blankly at the two who rushed inside and shouted.

“No one move! Raise your hands!!”

Van Doe rushed in and yelled. At first sight, he saw a strange figure standing in the middle of the training room, staring blankly at the two people who had just rushed in.

He instantaneously shifted his vision and it fell on the slowly dissipating subtle force field on the man’s hands.

“That is… Black Wind force field!!!”

“Damn!!”

The expression of the two people was a wonderful one. Kaneer, who had always been steady, could not be calm and mouthed off a profanity.

“The force field… Just now! …was released by you!??” the sound of Van Doe was quivering. He felt that human language could no longer express his excitement at this time.

Garen stared blankly at the two, his head nodded slightly up and down.

Thump!!

Two big hands smacked onto his shoulders. Then, he saw his always boring-looking teacher looked at him affectionately.

“Damn…!”

Thousands of words, all condensed in this one swear word.

*********************

After an hour of questioning…

Van Doe and Kaneer, master and disciple, both brought Garen to the encrypted meeting room, sealed off all the possibility of sound leakage, and finally, completely figured out the reasons for the incident.

It turned out that Garen was really just trying to release Black Wind. He did not expect it to be more powerful than he had imagined, so he began to study the specific response time and see the minimum threshold of how much time he would need before being able to use Black Wind again.

Who knew that the subsequent attempts were unsuccessful and he could only release the basic, weak force field. He had not been very concerned about this kind of vague force field and thought that the power was weak. But he did not expect this wave of force field to contact the wall unknowingly, eroding a large hole and even damaging the various blue-light-emitting circuit lines inside.

After that, it was the process in which Van Doe the two were stunned.

After asking everything, he looked at Nonosiva, who was sitting on his seat with a rule-abiding face. This boy, even the fluff above his mouth had not even grown thick yet. There was a mixed feeling within Van Doe and Kaneer.

The throats of the two people bobbed, but no words came out of it.

After a bit of pondering, Van Doe finally opened up with some difficulty.

“Are you sure you have never been exposed to the Black Wind Killing Move before?”

“Yes, teacher,” Garen nodded. “You could easily check it out from my home background.”

“Yeah… Yeah…” Van Doe looked at this calm-looking young man, recalling the pain and struggle he had when he was training Black Wind, even often getting headaches at night and being unable to fall asleep due to the overuse of his brain. Looking at this kid again, his face relaxed, there was nothing much to say about releasing once, but releasing a second time! And in the course of a day, he even attempted the third time, the fourth time!! The entanglement of Van Doe’s heart was like thousands of llamas dashing past [2].

Looked at his disciple, Kaneer, by the side, this guy was rubbing his temples intensely, his eyes shut with a painful expression.

“Are…you still able to release Black Wind now?” Van Doe asked softly.

“I’m afraid I can’t do it. This move is too much for my body,” Garen shook his head.

“We don’t need substance, as long as there is a little force field. The exhaustion for that is very small,” Van Doe responded cautiously.

“No problem with that.”

Garen stood up and his fingers began to twist and overlap to make rapid, accurate and complex gestures. At the same time, his Willpower was released in a filigree winding form. Synchronizing with his blood and spirit, they began to gather together. The four combined to form a kind of strange rune.

One by one, the symbolic runes were produced continuously. These runes were all optimized combinations of modeling after multiple calculations, one linked to the next. As long as one was not shaped well, it would affect the construction of the next one. Then, the effort would be wasted.

Over time, the first pyramid appeared.

A few minutes later, the second pyramid also appeared, followed by the third.

The moment the third pyramid was about to be completed, all three shattered. Traces of transparent Black Wind force field scattered away.

Van Doe opened his hand and a shapeless Willpower enveloped this wave of Black Wind force field. He gently pinched it, wiping it out.

He gazed at Garen with a complex feeling.

“Who would have expected… that I would still be able to meet such a talented student in my remaining years…”

“Hahhh…” Kaneer, on one side, could not help but sigh deeply. Compared with this junior brother, his qualifications were no different from dog’s poop. It took him many years before releasing the force field successfully. The gap between the two was greater than the hardness difference between a stone and tofu.

At this time, Garen could almost guess the teacher’s focus through his series of expressions. The difficulty of Black Wind was indeed very high. He had expected it to probably cause some commotions. However, he did not expect it to result in such a huge aftermath.

“Are… you willing to formally join my Black Flood Party?” Van Doe settled down, and officially, solemnly asked Garen.

“Black Flood Party?” it was the first time Garen had heard the name of this faction.

“This world seems to be divided into and ruled by regions, though in effect, there is also the division according to groups of factions by a collection of force,” Van Doe explained in detail. “Inheriting Sect. This is a strong force that is truly terrifying. In any Inheriting Sect, the worst pilot is also of Level Six. This is because to be able to be an Inheriter, only Level Six pilots have the right to be called Inheriting Level.

“Is Black Smoke Party an Inheriting Sect?”

“Yes, it is the second largest super-party in Blackboard Region and Polar Region. Our powerhouses in the Black Smoke Party are as numerous as the clouds. There exist powerhouse of Level Six and even above. Sect Master was the top stratum of the seventh Non-falling level many years ago, owning a corresponding Black Star Mech. Moreover, he is not yet our strongest Inheriting pilot. You will know these things later on. You just have to be clear that the power of our sect is second to none in Blackboard Region and Polar Region. Basically, nobody dares to disrespect us,” Van Doe said with a slight pride.

“Aside from Black Smoke Party, are there other factions?” Garen asked.

“Yes, but these two regions are our main sites,” Van Doe waved his hand. “The sects mostly exist in the form of academies. Blackboard Academy in Blackboard Region is, in fact, a mechanism for us and the Blackboard sect to select top disciples. After screening them in the Outer Courtyard, they are brought to the Inner Courtyard. After the brutal competition in Inner Courtyard, the strongest group can become the successors of the Inheriting level once they enter Level Six. Of course, geniuses like you are an exception.”

TL Notes:

[1] A Chinese idiom for once something has been decided, it becomes a fact and could not be changed.

[2] To express utter shock and amazement.

Chapter 887: Depart 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Prodigy?” Garen frowned. “You might have been mistaken, Teacher, my talents might not be that great…”

“As long as you’re not utterly hopeless, you can be built up with resources. For our Black Flood Party, the hardest part is that resonance skill killing moves are too difficult. Many of those so-called talented prodigies can’t manage a single one, anybody who can finish learning Black Wind within a year would already be considered highly worth cultivating. I know what your talent is like, it’s not that great, but we can still build you up with resources,” said Van Doe nonchalantly, waving his large hand.

As expected of a rich school, they had the funds for anything.

Garen’s heart calmed down slightly.

“I have a question, Teacher.”

“Speak.”

Garen sorted out his thoughts.

“It’s about matching training method Willpower with Mechs. One type of Willpower can only be matched with one Mech, so does that mean the other sub-types of Willpower would be useless? They can’t reach Inherited Level?”

“Exactly, you can only achieve resonance with one Mech. A Mech can also only match one type of Willpower, that’s something that cannot be helped. If you want to change your Willpower training method, you must then also change the makeup of your Mech, so that you can adjust your resonance degrees,” said Van Doe, nodding. “Our Black Flood Party’s strongest Black Flood’s Wind Training Method is just like that, it can only fit our school’s Black Flood Style Mech.”

Only then did Kaneer recover, staring at Garen with a complicated gaze.

“Back then, Teacher invented the Crouched Eagle Talon just so he could find a training method that suited the Black Flood’s Wind Killing Move better.”

“Teacher was the one who invented the Crouched Eagle Talon?!” This time, Garen was truly shocked. Just how old was this geezer… They say the Crouched Eagle Talon showed up more than two hundred years ago, and back then, the prodigy in the Crouched Eagle Talon’s quantum computer, those simulated fighting techniques…

Perhaps he was the same age as Garen…

Garen glanced at the old man secretly, and did find some things strange, just like he thought. The old man’s skin was slightly stiff. Somehow, he could not see a heartbeat in the old man’s chest, and even his breathing seemed overly rhythmic.

“Alright, kiddo, first I’ll tell you the general situation right now. Since you’ve joined our Black Flood Party, you can more or less ignore most of the powerhouses in the Blackboard and Polar Regions. Publicly, at least, you overpower them, but there are still some people who you can’t cross for now.”

Van Doe’s smile grew deeper.

With a whoosh and a tap of his finger, a large map appeared on the table between the three of them. The map was made out of countless blue lines, forming a large picture of the four regions, the Blackboard Region, Polar Region, Maria Region, and Royal Region.

The mountains and rivers on the map were very clearly pictured, they looked very realistic and detailed. If it were not for the fact that they were all blue, it would be no different from actually looking down at a three-dimensional sandbox from the sky.

Van Doe pointed at the center of the map.

“This is the Blackboard Region, where we are.”

With a buzz, one part of the map lit up in red. The word ‘Blackboard’ appeared on it.

“This one, slightly further away, is the Polar Region.”

He pointed again.

A part that was just slightly connected to the Blackboard Region stretched out, and lit up another oval-shaped area. All of it was red.

“The Blackboard Region had their Three Marshalls and One Star. That means the three Great Professors, those immortal geezers controlling the whole of Blackboard, and the Black Star. You can’t cross these people. Pay attention now. Especially that punk, Black Star Diofie, he’s pretty strong, and really cruel too. He jokes with you on the surface, but secretly he’ll stab you faster than anyone else.”

Garen nodded, showing that he understood.

“In the Blackboard Region, these are the people you shouldn’t cross, the others would give me face to some extent,” Van Doe said.

“And then, the Polar Region.” His finger slid across the map, moving to the Polar Region.

“This is where our Black Flood Party is based, you need to pay attention to two things. First, the Twelve Divine Wind Generals. Divine Wind General is the title given to the strongest fighters in the Black Flood Party, some of them are even stronger than the Party Leader. Don’t cross them, there are factions inside the Black Flood Party as well. You gotta understand, as long as there are people, there will be cliques. That’s especially true once there are more people, there will also be larger divisions among humans, perhaps in principles, perhaps in personalities, or maybe even in interests or hobbies. The social distances as a result of that will naturally differ.”

“And then, when there’s the occasional conflict, they would naturally split into different factions,” Garen continued from where Van Doe left off, showing that he understood.

“As long as you understand.” Van Doe nodded in satisfaction. “Of course, there are factions among the Twelve Divine Wind Generals who favor us as well, one of them being my teacher Osiris.”

“Understood.”

Garen nodded. The Blackboard Region’s Three Marshals and One Star, the Polar Region’s Twelve Divine Wind Generals, they all seemed to be forbidden existences. Their own power was enough to suppress most problems and conflicts. That was what Teacher Van Doe was trying to tell him.

“And then there’s the Maria Region, they have the Zero Pistol Sue-Anna. If you meet them, just run. They have a seven-man Anthem Brigade, every single one of them is crazy, they’re famous for being completely unreasonable. Don’t provoke them unless you’re Inherited Level. In the Royal Region, be aware of the party called Spiral Tower, no one else matters. The people in this party are all religious fanatics, they’ll self-detonate anytime if they can’t beat you. Compared to those White Light people, I think the Spiral Tower are more like terrorists. The others are all just normal school or party members, nothing much to be worried about, you should be fine seeing how experienced you are.”

Garen memorized them one by one, Blackboard Regions Three Marshals and One Star, Polar Region’s Twelve Divine Wind Generals, Maria Region’s Zero-Pistol Sue-Anna, and the Royal Region’s Spiral Tower.

These were all things he had to be wary of.

Van Doe was in a very good mood, so he took out his pipe, lit it, and started to smoke.

“Of course, you don’t have to be too careful either. It’s rare for these people and factions to make a move once in a few years, because once you reach a certain level, like Black Star Diofie, you’ll need to search everywhere for materials and techniques that suit you. You would be constantly consuming them to evolve your own Mech. After all, Level Six Inherited Level is when you start your foundations. At that level, their schedules are vastly longer than regular people’s. Although it seems like there’s a lot of them, it’s very common for them to only communicate without showing up for a dozen years or so, unless something extremely serious happens.”

Garen nodded in understanding.

Beside him, Kaneer added,

“Anyway, even after so many years of being Teacher’s student, I’ve still only encountered one of Maria’s Anthem Brigade members in the past decade or so, and even then, we just exchanged a glance from a long distance away before separating. The more active ones in the regions are the Outer Courtyard’s elite students and a few people from the Inner Courtyard. The ones who are active in the radiation belt tend to be the true Inner Courtyard elites from the different regions, they’re something like the Black-Clothed Generals. People like us, higher-ups from the Inner Courtyard, only tend to stand guard at the places that are more strategic in battle.”

“In other words, people at your level, Senior Brother, tend to be generals standing guard at important fortresses?” That was what Garen understood of it.

“Yeah, this level is mostly at Level Five New-Moon, that’s the lowest.” Kaneer nodded. Suddenly, he received a message on his watch, and lowered his head to glance at it, frowning. “There’s an assassination order for you on the Exterminet? Nono, did you offend someone important?”

“Exterminet?”

“Yep, it’s an assassination website, I do some part-time work for spare change there too.” Kanner nodded. “We don’t know who set it up, but the bounty is ten million Universal Units, that’s quite a sum.”

Beside them, Van Doe looked displeased.

“Exterminet?” he began to say something, but then he instantly thought of something, and calmed down. “Right now, we’re the ones who should not reveal Nono’s background, before he has his own Mech, it’s far too dangerous.”

“Teacher, are you saying that some people might try to make a move?” Kaneer frowned deeply as well, his expression solemn. Evidently, some people are not so easy to deal with, or at least they would be a lot more troublesome than the ten-million-unit bounty on the Exterminet.

“It’s very likely, maybe they don’t want our party to get stronger. Even if they turn hostile, as long as no one knows, they still have nothing to fear.” Van Doe stood up and started walking around the room, pacing back and forth.

After a few minutes, he suddenly stopped.

“We cannot reveal Nono’s talent, just give him the status of a normal disciple. However…” He flipped his palm, and a translucent cube that looked like plastic appeared in his palm.

“Take this.”

He stuffed the translucent cube at Garen.

“This is…”

Garen accepted the cube. It looked just like a little palm-sized brick, and was slightly heavy, but it was not hard either. Instead, it was extremely soft, if he pinched it slightly, his finger would sink inside.

“Twinkling Cube,” said Van Doe solemnly. “I left an Inherited Level Willpower blade in there, it’s equivalent to Level Six without resonance, and you can use it three times. Against an opponent who isn’t Inherited Level, you can use this thing to turn the tables on them, it’s slightly weaker than a Level Five Two-Moons Level using all their power to activate a resonance skill. It’s enough to keep you safe.”

Garen nodded heavily. This thing was evidently very precious, or else Van Doe would not have considered for some time before taking it out. He could tell just by looking at his Senior Brother Kaneer’s expression of envy.

“Thank you, Teacher.”

“If it weren’t for the fact that this thing can only keep Willpower that strong… Sigh…” Van Doe let out a long breath. “Alright, now let’s test your condition.”

“How are you going to test?”

Before Garen even finished speaking, there was a blur in front of his eyes, and he was patted lightly on both his shoulders and his back, three times in all. With his reflex speed, he still could not keep up, and by the time he reacted, he had been hit three times.

He saw Van Doe reappear in front of him.

It was a very strange feeling. He could clearly feel that Teacher Van Doe had patted him three times, but no matter what he just could not pinpoint exactly when those three hits landed. It felt as though they were all completed at the same time, but when he thought about it carefully, it felt as though Van Doe just walked over, not too quickly or slowly, and just patted him three times casually.

Chapter 888: Depart 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“It’s a deceptive effect caused by Willpower, because the difference in Willpower is too great, so there seems to be a time difference.” Van Doe smiled. “My Willpower is too much higher than yours, overwhelming yours, and creating a deceptive effect, such that your reaction speed and awareness of time are made several dozen times slower than reality. In other words, you became slow, and I became fast.”

“There’s an effect like that!?” Garen’s heart felt slightly cold, the difference in Willpower could somehow restrict his sense of the passing of time. That way, no matter how powerful his reflexes were, when they were slowed down to such an extent, he would still be several times slower than he should be!

“This is the effect of more than a complete level’s worth of difference in Willpower. Of course, the difference in the quality of that Willpower influences it as well, so at a high level, the difference in Willpower can allow peak-level pilots to take on a hundred people at once. This is the principle behind that. To normal people without Willpower, they might even be slowed down several hundred times. But of course, this suppression cannot last long, it’s a universal skill from among the explosive resonance skills. You can only use it after you reach Inherited Level, and it’s very impressive if you can maintain it for half a minute,” explained Van Doe.

“Half a minute… It doesn’t have to be that long, just a second of that suppression can make up for almost all other disadvantages… No wonder…” Garen ran through all the heroic legends about peak-level pilots in his heart. Most of them could turn the tables on others who were stronger. At the most critical moment, in the middle of raging battlefields, they won by taking off the enemy general’s head. With such an explosive resonance technique, even a pig can become a super pig…

“I hear that you plan to go into the radiation belt with some others to look for Mech materials?” Van Doe asked again. The old man did have impressive intelligence channels.

Garen secretly thought that he never mentioned that to anyone, but the old man still found out anyway.

“Yes. Lamda Alloy.”

“Lamda Alloy is not very good. At your current level, it would be better for you to use Lunar Alloy. It’s slightly pricier, but it can grow, so it would be decent for the main body of the Mech before you reach Inherited Level. If you use Lamda Alloy, you’ll need to upgrade again by Half-Moon Level, so it would be more troublesome,” said Van Doe thoughtfully. “I have some Lunar Alloy here, but it’s not enough. I’ll give you more later. It’s good for you to go to the radiation belt too, we won’t openly declare your identity for now, so you can still wander around freely. Once you go public, you might not encounter some smaller problems, but once you do meet a problem, that would be a life-or-death one.”

“I understand, the stronger I become, the stronger my enemies will be as well,” Garen nodded.

“As long as you understand. Other than Lamda Alloy, the place that you’re going has one more thing, you can go get it as well.” Van Doe flipped a small piece of dark red metal out of his pocket.

“Blood Silver. At your level, it’s perfect for the heat-insulating shell outside the engine. With this, you can use a lot of engine skills later.

“But you must remember that this thing expires very quickly, and there’s no real way to preserve it for a long time. If you don’t bring it back within two months and work with it to fix its shape, you’ll just have to go get it again.”

“Around where should I get it?” Garen carefully observed the Blood Silver’s external characteristics.

“There’s a base there, report my name once you get there. One of our Black Flood Party’s pilots stationed there will immediately pass it to you. This thing is really precious, remember not to show it to anyone. That bit is also one of the few precious things I have left…” Van Doe instructed him carefully. “Powerful engine techniques and the potential to grow in the future are all related to the materials making up the Mech, Blood Silver is a treasure that you won’t stop benefiting from, so you must remember to use it before its expiry date once you get it. Otherwise, it’ll be a huge waste!”

“Understood.”

Garen nodded solemnly.

*******************

The public radiation zone, between the Polar Region and the Blackboard Region.

It was twilight, the sun slowly setting in the red sky. Most of it was obscured by thick black clouds, and only a small portion of the light landed on the ground beneath.

The huge black mountains rose from the earth, rising and falling, forming many sharp peaks that were sparsely decorated with greenery.

The mountain peaks stood on the black earth, like so many black trees growing on the ground. Some even had branches, with pale yellow lights twinkling on them.

Several windows of different sizes had somehow opened up on these mountain ‘branches’, dim yellow lamplight shining out from within.

The taller peaks were several hundred meters tall, with the occasional red or yellow lights. Others were only several dozen meters tall, with defense cannons stationed at the top.

On the ground between the mountains, there were many scattered black or grey buildings, looking like wooden blocks that were just simply tossed there. They were of different sizes, and had no order to them at all. Around the buildings, there were patches of green farmland, with thick lush greenery growing within. The breeze constantly blew ripples into the emerald plants.

On a cliff not too far away from this housing area, four tall black humanoid Mechs were slowly landing, standing lightly on the thick and moist black soil on the cliff.

One of the Mech moved its large foot casually, and squashed a black two-tailed scorpion.

The four Mechs were all completely inconspicuous, their bodies painted to look old and damaged. There were even some broken parts here and there, revealing the old grey circuits inside.

Complete Mechs were very rare in the radiation era, and here were four of them. Although they were all extremely damaged, it was still more than most factions could afford. In a normal village of a hundred or so residents, just one of these would be treated as something of a guardian god.

Brr…

In the sky, three giant mutated black Flying Batoids flew past slowly, casting their humongous shadows. These gigantic creatures looked like electric eels but with two thick fan-shaped wings of flesh that flapped up and down as they flew ahead, dragging their long tails behind them.

Three of the Mechs underneath raised their heads and looked at them, their red eyes twinkling with scanner light.

“Mutated Giant Batoids, they look like kites from a distance. The scenery is pretty good here,” said a low man’s voice from one of the Mechs.

“It’s a kite that can move by itself. That thing is more than ten meters long, and it was born with an anti-gravity organ. When it gets violent, it’s practically inhuman!” another Mech joked.

“It never was human to begin with…” another Mech continued. Inside, Garen took out a water bottle and chugged from it hard.

“It’s so cold… Anda, where do we go now? According to the map, this should be Flying Batoid City. We still need to pass three more locations before we can reach our destination,” a woman’s deep voice asked from the last Mech.

This group of people was Anda and Garen’s team, who had come out to get the Lamda Alloy. Other than material collection, this quest team also wanted to buy facial Lamda Alloy for themselves, the price difference inside and outside the Region was ridiculously large.

Anda invited two people along, one man and one woman. Together with Garen, they were four in total, forming a temporary team for the quest. After finishing the procedure to leave, they flew non-stop to their destination, but because the distance was too great, and the energy winds were too strong, the burden on the Mechs and the energy furnace was too much. So according to plan, the four of them landed at the first supply point, with the intention of replenishing their energy resources here.

“Aves, please scan the area to see if there are any surveillance points around here. Be aware of our surroundings,” said Anda, as he began to delegate jobs.

“No problem.”

“Linda, I’ll leave underground surveilance to you.”

“Leave it to me.”

“Garen, you and I are the strongest, so we’ll stay in the middle and watch the sky, while also supporting Aves. That’s okay, right?”

“Sure.”

Since they went out on the excursion, they all used pseudonyms, and Garen went back to the name he was used to using for the past few worlds.

“They’re perfectly fine Blackboard Standard Mechs, but we camouflaged them to look this beat up. The disguise itself took me five thousand units! If we don’t earn back from this, I’ll have lost big!” Aves complained as he began to fly, advancing slowly in one direction.

Linda stayed in place, taking a long and thin black metal needle from behind her waist. She pulled with both hands, and it instantly extended to a full five meters, which she stuck hard into the ground.

Psst! The thin needle was embedded into the ground, and instantly, a wave of small vibrations spread from it. They scattered from the cliff, following the surface of the earth. Wherever there was soil or rocks, many tiny poisonous bugs were forced out of the ground, scampering everywhere like a particularly nauseating swarm.

Garen crossed his arms over his chest, leaning on a stalagmite as he quietly watched the others prepare to set up camp.

The other two people who had come out with Anda this time were Linda and Aves. One was a young woman with long brown hair, ordinary features, and a normal figure. There was nothing exceptional about her, be it in the way she did things or her appearance. Everything was by the books, and very steady. Her emitted Willpower force field was at Level Four, give or take, but he did not know if she had any resonance degrees.

And the other one, Aves, seemed like a bit of a rash man. He looked to be about twenty-four or five, and always liked dressing up and showing off. He used cologne, and seemed to make a big deal of his appearance. At first glance, he looked like a rich young master who could not handle hard work, but along the way, surprisingly, he did not act spoiled at all, and was instead very experienced in the way he handled things. He was particularly good at surveillance.

Along the way, the four of them had prepared a large amount of food and water. Within six days, they arrived at the first supply point, Flying Batoid City.

“This is the largest radiation city in the public radiation zone near Blackboard?” Garen looked at the rather small town beneath him. It did not have a wall, and even had farmlands instead. The tree-shaped mountains around it were all armed with defensive cannons to some extent, so it looked like it had good security, at least.

“To the radiation people living in the radiation belt, that’s how it is,” replied Anda nonchalantly, as he fiddled with an unknown piece of equipment.

“Flying Batoid City is most famous for having a guardian-like radiation mutated creature act as their soldiers. It’s those Flying Batoids in the sky, as long as you don’t attack them, they won’t attack humans themselves. This place has clean Level One water, Level One food and meat, and good living conditions, with stable security. Only the elite radiation people in the radiation belt have the right to live here.”

“The last time I came here with another team, the food here was very cheap. Just a bit of clean water without radiation is considered Level One Water here, one liter is enough to buy a pretty girl. Although she was a radiation person, but that body and that face… tsk tsk… I got a great feel of that, alright.” Aves had flown back without them noticing.

“What’s the point of touching through a hazmat suit?” said Anda exasperatedly, glancing at him.

“Actually, I nearly wanted to bring her back. I mean, that girl only had one tiny radiation mark the size of a fingernail on her butt, everything else was just like a normal person!” argued Aves. “I bet that even the prettiest leader of the luxury district in the city would only be at that level!”

“You can only enjoy the life of a peak-level noble here in the radiation belt,” said Anda calmly.

“Everyone’s like that the first time they come out here, right?” Aves clicked his tongue.

Garen listened to them bicker, but his gaze had already floated into the unknown distance.

An extremely weak signal was barely touching his Willpower. That was the communication signal from Red Moon, but because of the great distance, it was unnaturally weak.

Garen calmed his heart down, and carefully decoded the message in the signal. It was a very common Rice Code, a message coded through a simple combination of rhythms.

He began to translate and read it carefully.

Chapter 889: Quiet 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“We… in danger… deal… second half of training method… come quick….” Red Moon’s message was not very long, but its meaning was very simple and precise.

“They” evidently meant Clint, and his younger brother Lon. The three of them were in danger, which clearly meant that they had come across some trouble in the radiation belt.

Garen rubbed his chin as he thought about it. He allowed the Mech’s quantum computer to calculate the distance that the signal was coming from.

“If he came to the radiation belt without a hazmat suit, then he’d really be in trouble. Baylon, that kid…” He was worried that if Baylon really was infected by the radiation, and became a radiation person, no matter how small a radiation mark he had, he would still be forever ostracized from all the Regions.

Radiation disease was incurable, that was a fact acknowledged by all the regions, without exception.

Soon, the computer had calculated the distance.

‘The signal came from a distance of: 235 kilometers, 23 degrees to the North-West.’

‘Warning, warning, insufficient reserves in energy furnace, the battery must be changed now. Power remaining 4%.’

“I’ll go charge my battery first, otherwise I won’t be able to move after several kilometers.”

Garen heaved a long breath, and quickly put on a sealed hazmat suit. Actually, even if he did not suit up, no radiation would be able to infect him, because as a Peacock larva, he was already the largest source of radiation. Nobody could block the cold radiation he emitted, it could even affect their hearts. But he still had to be aware of his identity on the surface.

Inside the Mech, he held a short staff in his hand. It was the Staff of Ultimate Yin. Taking it with him, Garen was slowly sent out of the cockpit, forming a separate cabin on his own. And then the outer door to the Mech opened slowly.

Pfft!

There was a spray of white gas that emanated everywhere.

Wearing a hazmat suit, Garen slowly jumped forward, and landed lightly on the soil beside the cliff.

The other three people also walked out of their respective Mechs in their suits. They were all wrapped up in thick black clothes as though it was winter, but unlike winter clothing, they also had to wear a transparent glass helmet over their heads. The helmet was completely transparent, so unless they looked at it closely, no one would notice that they were wearing something like that. It was extremely well-hidden.

Other than that, not a single patch of their skin was exposed. It was all covered tightly, with black gloves on their hands. They even had a Blackboard pattern on the back of the hands, it looked like an eye.

Anda walked at the very front, looking at the Flying Batoid City beneath them.

“I’ve contacted the City Master already, someone needs to stand watch over the base when we’re charging batteries. The radiation people will send someone here specifically for this, we just need to pay with two bottles of Level One water. Everyone else can go explore and play around. Who’s willing to stay behind?”

“I’ll do it.” Aves raised his hand. “I can only look and not play anyway, if I get all riled up, I’ll still have to finish it off myself. What a pain. I’m not going.”

“Fine.”

The other three, Anda, Linda, and Garen, all climbed down the right side of the cliff. There was a flight of ninety-degree stairs there, covered with moss. Evidently, they were used often.

The three of them walked down the stairs for several minutes, and soon enough they came across a stone door to a guard station. There was a black person carrying a gun on his back, standing guard there.

“It’s the three sires!” The black man snapped a salute at the three of them. Their salute was really strange their right hand pressed against their forehead at a ninety-degree angle. Their accent was just a little flatter than the people inside the regions, their tongue did not curl at all.

Anda nodded, leading Linda and Garen inside.

As they continued down the mountain path, they saw more and more man-made buildings, with railing that was painted blue. Occasionally they would come across radiation people, all of them carrying large baskets on their backs, but who knew what they had come out here to pick.

Garen peeked into one of their baskets, and found that it was full of plant roots and green grass, and there was the occasionally useful herb as well.

All the radioactive people who saw them along the way, whether they were dressed simply or luxuriously, all scattered to the sides in fearful respect, allowing the three of them to pass.

A woman carrying a child even clapped her hand to her child’s mouth tightly. No matter how hard the one-year-old child cried, she refused to let go, but some sound still escaped. Anda heard it, and glanced over with a frown.

With a bang, the woman actually knocked out her own child mercilessly, and fell to her knees, dragging the child with her, her head lowered. She dared not say a single thing, and just kept kowtowing on the ground.

“These are radiation people.” Anda’s tone was mild, but it had a hint of contempt. “Forget Inner Courtyard elites like us, they can’t even provoke the regular Outer Courtyard students.”

“Over here, our position is even scarier than the emperor,” Linda said with a sigh. It clearly was not her first time here either.

“What about the ruler here?” Garen asked.

“Just a fatty who sits around waiting to die, he can’t even get up, he’s over four hundred pounds in weight,” Anda said contemptuously. “According to the rules, the rulers here must also bow and show their respect to us when they meet us, but these parasites are at the top, so of course they don’t want to do that in front of so many people. That’s why they find reasons to avoid meeting us, and get their subordinates to greet us instead. It’s a very common thing here, as long as they treat people like us well, they don’t have anything to worry about. Over here, people are worth the least, the most valuable things here are clean food and water, nothing else can match up to these two.”

The three of them walked into the farmlands of the Flying Batoid City beneath them. The green farms surrounded the whole city, but rather than the regular paddy or wheat, they were filled with a strange plant. It had a green stem like paddy, but on top it was a fat, squirming green maggot. The maggot was curled up, tightly hugging the tip of the plant, swaying and swinging in the breeze.

Soon enough, a radiation man with a strong body greeted them up front, getting on his knees and bowing in front of them in the middle of the path between the crops.

“Representing the City Master, Vendant is here to greet the arrival of my three lords.” There were four people behind him, all of them seemed to be teenagers. The two men were handsome and strong, the two women beautiful and pure. They were all subtly dressed to look pretty and sexy.

“Follow the old rules,” said Anda nonchalantly. “Garen, you choose, of the two girls, which do you prefer? These should be the best the city has to offer.”

Garen was speechless, glancing at the two girls behind the man Vendant. Although they were beautiful, while he was dressed in his hazmat suit, he could only watch and touch, so what was the point?

“These people will only act as a guide and warm your bed, we might have to rest here for the night, and leave again tomorrow,” Anda explained simply.

“Then I’ll choose this one.” Garen casually pointed at the long-haired girl who looked purer. She had pitch-black hair falling over her shoulders, like an Asian, with large black eyes, fair skin, and neatly-trimmed bangs in front of her forehead. Her lips were a very decent pink color. Her body was curved in all the right places as well, wearing black skin-tight clothes that looked slightly like a swimsuit. It was very thin, and could not cover any of the sensitive parts of her body. Especially her long slender fair legs, her clothes made her seem as though she was merely wearing underwear, so even if the girl kept trying to pull her clothes to cover the area between her legs, it was still useless. The overly tight clothes made her completely unable to cover the extra parts of her body.

Hearing that Garen choose her, her face instantly blushed with a clear red hue, and she lowered her head in a way that invited pity.

The other was a blonde girl who was also extremely pretty. Not a single radiation mark could be found on her body, but she wore a slave’s collar around her neck, to elicit a man’s urge to conquer her.

Kneeling on the ground, Vendant heaved a sigh of relief. They had hurriedly found these four slaves from the radiation people around here when they heard that important people were the Regions were coming. The slaves were all superior breeds that had less than 10% radiation marks on them, although they were still pretty, they were nevertheless slightly less presentable than the carefully selected ones from before. He was also terrified that the guests would be dissatisfied, plus there were so few of them, so he was even more panicked, but thankfully it seemed that this group was more easygoing.

“Then I’ll take the other one.” Anda pointed at the other blonde girl, he was evidently used to this process.

Linda chose a young boy who looked very shy, he was very handsome, and looked just like a girl.

The last boy was slightly disappointed as Vendant sent someone to lead him away.

“It’s a bit rushed this time, and the stock you chose isn’t that great, but we won’t blame you. We’re just here to rest for one night, and we’ll be leaving tomorrow, so hurry and arrange a place for us to rest,” Anda instructed.

Vendant lowered his head and agreed to everything. “Yes, yes.”

The three boys and girls behind Garen’s group were all slightly shocked, after all Vendant was the City Master’s close follower, so he had always been wild and irrepressible in the city. But in front of these three masters, he was just slightly better than a dog.

Walking into Flying Batoid City, Garen finally experienced the true wilderness, chaos, and rot of the radiation belt.

The buildings were white, or black, and the city walls were made of ancient cement, some places dyed with dark red blood stains that no one bothered to clean. It was unnaturally busy on the streets, with radiation people walking their mutated dogs everywhere. Some were huge, tall brutes who were more than three meters tall, but there were also dwarfs who were so small and thin they looked like children. Some had an extra arm on their backs, some had rotting noses, so their whole face was completely flat.

There were all sorts of radiation people, and according to Vendant’s introduction, these people’s various mutations caused their bodies to change in different ways.

Wherever the three of them passed, all of the radiation people were forcefully pushed aside by the soldiers, opening up a wide path. Quickly, the three of them got onto the car that was arranged for previously, it was the most broken-down model that was already out of production in the Regions, but here, it was evidently the highest form of indulgence.

In the radiation belt, the only ones who could afford to use batteries and enjoy life were all nobles among nobles, the VIPs among VIPs.

Garen was arranged in a car with the girl who seemed to be sixteen or seventeen. She was clearly very nervous, but she was also extremely curious, and was unnaturally excited to be sitting in this car.

“You were born in the radiation belt?” asked Garen casually, as he looked at the crowds in the streets outside the window.

“Y-Yes, sir.”

“What’s your name?”

“Little Bitch, sir…”

“A terrible name.” Garen was exasperated, why that of all names?

“Sir… In Flying Batoid City, only the nobles can give themselves names. If we normal civilians want to live, the higher-ups will give us names…” Little Bitch replied, looking depressed. “And we’re lucky, compared to the meat people…”

She was indeed pretty, but in Flying Batoid City, there were meat people even prettier than her.

“What are meat people?” Garen’s curiosity was slightly piqued.

“People who are reared in pens, they constantly mate in the pens, perfecting their genes like dog pedigrees. Once the mutations caused by the inbreeding are removed, they are made to grow faster using hormones. The pretty ones with good quality are sent out as slaves, the ones with poor quality are made into pigs for meat, and killed for food…” explained Little Bitch in a low voice.

Garen was shocked for a moment as well.

That was treating humans inhumanly, they were even more like livestock than actual beasts.

“In the radiation belt, what is law?” he suddenly asked out of the blue.

Little Bitch blinked in confusion, she did not understand what he was trying to ask.

Garen sighed, and said no more. Leaning his back on the leather seats, he crossed his legs and began to rest.

As the car drove on, Garen did not look at the demonic streets of Flying Batoid City anymore, and he only opened his eyes slowly when they reached their accommodation.

Getting out of the car, Garen saw a large white manor in front of him, surrounded by tall walls. As soon as they went past the gate, there was a large round four-tiered fountain, dark red water sprayed from the tip and flowed down the sides, the blood-like color piercing to the eye.

Chapter 890: Quiet 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

There were all many tidily-dressed men and women waiting inside the mansion.

After that, they were arranged rooms, and chose their style of entertainment. By style of entertainment, they meant the surroundings required to satisfy any guest.

If you liked food, for example, they would bring you into an environment made of high-quality low-radiation food. The room was made of chocolate, the bed made of milk candy, and all the plants in the garden were sweet fruits, whereas the swimming pool was filled with milk.

If you liked pretty women, they would also take you to a special place, where all the pretty women around you were naked, and there were sex toys everywhere, so you could just grab a woman whenever and play with them however you liked.

If you were gay, then there were all the best men for you to choose, beautiful ones, handsome ones, strong ones, cool ones, dressed in all sorts of uniforms to seduce you.

In this mansion, whatever you wanted, other than the luxurious Level One food and drinks, everything else you desired could be fulfilled whenever. Even if you liked killing, they would arrange people for you to kill, one after the other, in however many ways you wanted.

This, was the Paradise Mansion, the meat people mansion in mountains!

“Everyone here is a meat person?” Garen walked at the very end of the line, observing the many people lined up in two rows, welcoming him in. There were men and women, young and old, but they all had one thing in common—their eyes were lifeless and dim, only a very few just barely had a hint of consciousness, but the rest had stiff robotic movements.

“Yeah…” Little Bitch replied softly. She was clearly slightly scared, grabbing Garen’s arm tightly, her whole body practically pressed against his. “Everyone here has had chips implanted, they can’t escape at all. Some of them only have the IQ of a seven- or eight-year-old, but some others are slightly smarter, they were once normal people who committed crimes.”

“Seriously…” Garen shook his head, he had learned even more about the cruelty of the radiation belt.

In the hall, Vendant very wisely retreated, leaving Anda, Linda, and Graen standing in front of the choice pillars in the main hall.

“You can choose your style of entertainment here, if they don’t have it, you can describe what you want yourself, and enter it using Willpower. If there aren’t any conflicts with the main system, you can make new entertainment areas to your own liking,” Anda introduced. “I’ve played here a few times, it’s really not bad. Too bad the highest-grade anti-radiation medicine only comes in small shippings for the peak-level people every year, because if you can take off your hazmat suit here to play, that would truly be paradise.”

Anda was evidently a lot more relaxed than before, he looked at Garen.

“This is your first time, Garen, so play to your heart’s content. When you choose an area here, no one can enter without your permission, so you can fulfill any dark thoughts or fetishes here, hehe…”

“Boring,” Garen replied calmly, and glanced casually at the choices there.

Killing, pretty women, pretty men, gourmet food, dog pen, theme park, torture…

There was a long list of entertainment modes, it even covered the whole side of the pillar. There was even a second page, he gave it a glance, and saw at least a hundred options there. There were even categories.

“You have to choose one, this is the Paradise Mansion, if you don’t choose any entertainment, when word gets out, no one will believe you’re straight,” Anda approached Garen and said with a dark smile.

This made Garen, who was going to choose the quiet option, roll his eyes. His finger moved and landed on a random choice, he was too lazy to even look at it. Other than the violent ones, there were even many written in strange symbols he could not understand, and the mode he chose was one of these strangely-coded ones.

“Let’s go.” Garen saw the pillar indicate where he needed to go, and in the midst of Anda’s dark laughter, and Linda’s helpless gaze, he led Little Bitch and strode into a small door that had automatically opened on the left.

Anda carefully chose an option on the stone pillar, and also walked into a small door, hugging the blonde girl.

Only Linda was left, but her gaze flashed a little. She did not pick any option, but instead walked out of the hall, and raised her watch outside the door to project a virtual keyboard. After tapping out a simple code to spell out a secret message, and delivering the mail, she finally returned to the pillar and picked the quiet option, leading the pretty boy into a small door.

****************

Flying Batoid City, City Master Quarters.

At the peak of the tallest mountain tree in town, there was a huge empty hall. At the very top of the large empty black space, there was a huge throne, and a huge bald fat man, seven or eight meters wide, five or six meters tall, lay there.

The fatty was covered in fatty flesh, his layers of flesh falling downwards due to gravity, and piling on top of the flesh underneath that, forming folds like a thousand-layer crepe. From afar, he looked like a large pile of white flesh made into a mountain.

The fatty’s two triangular eyes kept blinking, and he bit a long black pipe, half a meter long. in his mouth. There were two naked voluptuous women by his side, constantly massaging his body and head.

“The ones who had come this time are Blackboard Academy’s Inner Courtyard elites, you must be extra, extra careful with how you greet them,” the fatty instructed lazily, looking at Vendant who was kneeling on the floor beneath him.

“I greeted the three lords with the First-Grade rules, please do not worry, City Master,” replied Vendant loudly, his head lowered.

“That’s good.” The City Master nodded, but his chin was too fat, so the action was not very noticeable. “Pay attention, and see if you can get some techniques regarding Repair Troughs from them. Our own Repair Troughs still lack too many critical techniques, if we can complete it quickly, we can also quickly form the Poison People Division.”

“Also, don’t let the other City Masters know that the three lords are here.”

“Yes.”

Vendant got up and was about to leave, but suddenly he touched his earpiece, where his subordinate’s report was coming in.

He frowned slightly.

“There’s one more thing, Lord City Master.”

“What is it? Speak,” the fat City Master said calmly, puffing from the pipe.

“One of the three lords wants to borrow our military strength to go out and find some people.” Vendant paused. “It is that new lord, codenamed Garen, it should be his first time in the radiation belt.”

“Oh? It’s the easiest to get good things out of new lords like that… Not bad, not bad, fulfill his desires. Since he’s looking for people, send the best Panther Squad out, and have them obey his every word.” The City Master waved his hand generously.

“Yes, I will give them the order to mobilize now,” replied Vendant respectfully.

Neither of them noticed that a pitch-black insect was blinking its compound eyes in a dark corner of the hall. Its entire body was made completely out of cold mechanics. Through some invisible waves, the voices here were transmitted to a faraway distance.

***************

Inside the Blackboard Region, in a certain private estate in Blackboard City.

Fila strode towards the second floor of the mansion, his expression dark, and saw a carefree young man watching the TV projected onto the wall, holding a remote control. Behind him, there was a pretty girl carefully fanning him.

That bastard, there was automatic air-conditioning right there, but he just refused to turn it on.

Fila cursed him inwardly.

“Where’s Big Bro?” he asked the young man quietly.

“I don’t know… Five, why do you look so unfortunate? You look like a dead dog, y’know~~” The young man made no attempt to hide his jest.

If it weren’t that he could not beat this son of a… Fila felt as though the veins in his forehead were going to pop.

“It was just an accident.” Suddenly something occurred to him, and he tried his best to reply in a nondescript manner.

“Accident?”

The young man looked just like those regular hooligans on the street, his short hair dyed blonde, and he even left a small lock of white hair hanging over the left side of his forehead, all curled up, as though he thought he looked handsome and flirtatious. His white lounge clothes did not match his dark skin, the clothes themselves were luxury items worth more than ten thousand, but when he wore them, he looked like a backwater bumpkin lord.

“Yes, an accident.” Fila acted as though he did not want to talk about it.

“Interesting.” The young man lifted his watch and checked it quickly. When he saw the process, he was instantly even more interested. “You were beaten up that badly by a newbie?” He smiled, completely hooked. “Interesting, how very interesting!”

“What’s it to do with you?! I’ll deal with it myself, I’m warning you, Ice Dragon, I’ll deal with my own matters! If you dare to interfere, I won’t consider you my brother!” said Fila coldly.

“Five, that’s where you’re wrong…” The young man called Ice Dragon stood up. “You’re all alone, and you only got a few kitties under you. If you don’t come to me, your big bro, when stuff like this happens, people will say that my little brother doesn’t come to me even when he’s in trouble, and then how will I face the world?!” he said loudly, patting his chest. “Relax, and leave this to me! I’ll deal with that punk for you directly!”

“It’s my own–” Fila acted unhappy, but before he could even finish his sentence, he was suddenly pressed down by a heavy pressure. For a second there he was completely shocked, and could not say a thing.

This guy got even stronger…!

Ice Dragon’s hands pressed down on Fila’s shoulders, as he was all smiles.

“We’re brothers, and you still act so distant…” All of a sudden, his expression instantly became icy cold. “Are you really trying to make me lose face…!” Hints of cold killing intent emanated from him, keeping Fila locked down tight.

This madman!

Fila’s heart grew cold, and he no longer dared to provoke this person, so he forced out a smile.

“Of course not…”

“That’s best.” Ice Dragon smiled again. “Recently Big Bro’s men are starting to leave some hints, everything goes according to plan. In just two more months, we can probably successfully obtain that person’s information.”

“So fast!” Fila’s expression changed slightly.

“Get ready, then… Three Marshals and One Star or whatnot, I’ve wanted to meet them for some time now…” Deep-seated killing intent flashed through Ice Dragon’s eyes. “But before that, I’ll go settle the kid that bullied my brother, that’ll be my appetizer…”

Chapter 891: Approaching Battle 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In an isolated green-black wilderness

In the large patches of black swamp and plains, there was a single little inn standing alone in the center. The grey-white building looked just like a wooden toy house used for children’s games, in that it did not look steady at all.

Clint was sprawled on a pitch-black, broken-down Mech, holding something like a tweezer tool. He even had a few oily screws in his mouth, and was repairing his own Mech cockpit with an expression of intense concentration.

“Third screw on the left, tighten it again, and be careful of the energy circuits there, if you knock them askew, you’ll have to start all over again.”

Red Moon’s instructions kept coming, guiding Clint to quickly settle some of the minor problems the Mech had.

Amidst the clinking noises, Clint spat out the things in his mouth.

“Lord Red Moon, can this thing even be fixed? I’ve been working for a few days now, but it’s still exactly the same.”

“It was damaged too badly in the chase from before, so you got no choice. You should thank your lucky stars if it can even be fixed at all,” replied Red Moon exasperatedly. “Lonnie’s one is still in one piece, at the very least, so if this one really can’t, you’ll just have to make do. Oh, and there aren’t that many energy batteries for the energy furnace anymore, so you’ll need to find new batteries. This isn’t the city, where you can find many batteries anywhere. In the radiation belt, the hardest part is finding supplies, not just for people, but for Mechs as well.”

“Can’t we just toss them into your space, like last time?” asked Clint, confused.

“Of course not, you’ll be done for if your enemies reach you here. Unlike normal pilots, you’re the fast-growing type, your Willpower improved really quickly, but at the same time, when you’re not in your Mechs, you can’t use your Willpower at all,” reminded Red Moon. “Don’t tell me you forgot?”

“Of course not,” Clint pouted. The intense pain in his butt from before was still fresh in his mind, he did not know what happened, but he did not dare to recall such terrifying memories.

“Alright, hurry up,” Red Moon rushed him.

“Clint, it’s time to eat.” Just then, Baylon’s voice came from the inn below, she was wearing an apron hastily tied on with black cloth, and yelled as she walked out of the door.

“Let’s go, time to eat!”

Clint jumped out of the Mech. The Nine Mega Cannon Training Method had drastically strengthened his body, such that it was nothing for him to jump down from several meters up.

Once he entered the inn, in the small hall behind the front door, he saw two bowls of pale yellow thick soup on the table. They looked very average, but smelled very good. He had no idea what they were made of.

There was the aroma of meat and a faint smell of green grass in the air.

“Smells so good…” Clint took a deep breath, and when he saw that Baylon was ready with the ladle, his face instantly broke into a smile.

“Sorry, there’s nothing much left to eat anymore… There were just a few cans left, I used up the rest of our water to make this…” Baylon’s expression was pained as she said that.

“It’s okay, how much longer can our supplies last?” Clint sat down and immediately began to shovel the food into his mouth.

“Two more days…” Baylon lowered her head.

“!!??”

Clint instantly looked up, his expression incredulous.

“Although the rat meat that we made into jerky has been kept into Lord Red Moon’s space, we just don’t have enough water… And in the incident last time, the Mech filter system that we took out was taken away…” Baylon replied, her head lowered.

“Looking for food and water in the radiation belt is a very troublesome matter, but compared to being hunted, it’s still a lot easier…” Red Moon said calmly, having expected this a long time ago.

It placed most of its attention on Baylon, who was slowly sitting down.

“Lonnie.”

“Ah… huh?”

“You secretly asked about the second half of the training method for your brother, and I gave it all to you. But every training method in the world requires all of one’s undivided attention, in other words, one person can only choose one training method to resonate with in their lifetime. The others can only be their support. If your brother chooses this training method as his main, then when he builds a Mech in the future, he will require extremely, extremely high-level materials. And on this planet, such materials…”

“They don’t exist?” A hint of disappointment flashed through Baylon’s eyes. “My older brother… had always been stronger than me since we were young. No matter what happened, he would always be proud, fearless, advancing without hesitation…”

Red Moon and Clint did not say anything, and just looked at her quietly.

“He will surely have a way… He’ll make the best choice! I trust him to,” Baylon said determinedly.

“Sure, but even if he doesn’t choose this training method as his main, a lot of the contents in it will still work with his Willpower and benefit him,” said Red Moon consolingly. If at first he had released this training method to stabilize Garen, now he was truly and sincerely offering a solution.

“In this world, the best things are the ones that suit you. No matter how high-level the other stuff is, no matter strong, that will still be the strength of others. Your brother… he is a prodigy… so don’t worry.”

Baylon nodded. She never doubted that. As an older brother, Nono’s image had long ago left the deepest impressions in her heart.

The two of them picked up their bowls and drank their soup slowly. After they were done eating, Baylon cleared the plates and prepared to wash them.

Suddenly there was a faint rumble reaching them slowly from afar.

The floor began to tremble, and bolts of faint electricity spread from the distance like waves.

The two of them froze at almost the exact same time.

“That’s…!??” Clint’s heart began to tremble intensely despite himself.

“It’s Red-White!” Red Moon’s yell woke the two of them up. “Lonnie, get into the Mech!! Now!”

Clint’s Mech was not fixed yet, and could not move, so the only one that was intact now was Baylon’s Mech.

Baylon’s eyes first flashed with deep fear and hesitation.

“I… I…”

“You, you, my foot! If you don’t wanna die, get on the f*cking thing!!” Red Moon began to curse loudly.

In the midst of the yelling, Baylon was all dazed and confused. By the time she recovered, she was already sitting in the broken-up old patchwork Mech.

The Willpower produced by Bright Queen Jisaiya’s training method was like so many tiny spiders, constantly spitting out blue silk threads that spread from inside her body, connecting to the entire Mech from top to bottom.

“Get ready to move!” reminded Red Moon. “Lonnie, Clint and I are depending on you to protect us now. If you don’t want to die, fight! The opponent is not really a peak-level Red-White Mech, it’s just a straggling soldier on patrol. If you still can’t beat ’em, then we’re probably truly done for.”

“I… I can’t…” Baylon’s heart was pounding loudly. The heavy responsibility and pressure weighed down on her, to the point where she was struggling to breathe.

“Just do it with all your might. Even if you fail, no one will blame you.” Just then, Clint’s voice came from inside the Mech.

“My ass!! Move aside, you idiot, even if you got a death wish, I ain’t lived enough yet!” Red Moon interrupted Clint abruptly. “Punk-ass, if you can’t beat that small fry, both of y’all will run naked!!”

“R-r-r-run naked…!!!” Baylon’s little face instantly turned into a tomato with a whoomph.

On the distant horizon, a red-and-white humanoid Mech with a wolf’s head was flying at them at top speeds.

“Go–!!” With a sudden squeeze of Willpower, Baylon felt herself dashing forward. She was actually striding towards the opponent madly, the engine behind her exploding to life, and forcing the Mech to slowly shoot towards the enemy.

Aaaaaaahhh—-

She started screaming abruptly, as she watched the wolf-headed humanoid Mech come closer and closer, closer and closer.

“Where’d this junk bucket come from?” a hoarse woman’s voice said from within the other Mech.

Seeing that the Mechs were going to crash into each other, Baylon’s heart ran cold, and she tried to salvage the situation, flustered. But she had no idea how to react.

“Idiot! You don’t even know the basic movements!?” Red Moon’s voice began to howl.

For some reason, for a second there, it was as though Red Moon’s voice overlapped with another voice in her memory.

Baylon’s eyes suddenly lost focus, as though she had suddenly returned to the past, when she asked her brother to teach her basic combat skills.

“A Mech’s basic combat is actually just like a human’s own movements, the Will-powered Mechs can perfectly express any movement of the human body.” Nonosiva’s eyes were filled with contempt as he looked down on Baylon.

“Remember, Baylon, when it comes to fighting, it doesn’t matter who’s stronger, but it’s the person who can use the power correctly who wins. No matter how weak this person is, once the power is used right, the difference between them will also be like heaven and earth.”

“Just like right now.”

Whoosh!

Nono kicked out suddenly, his foot landing in Baylon’s stomach.

“What should you do?! Tell me!”

Bam! Mrgh…

Baylon hugged his stomach, and refused to let himself fall.

“Re-retreat.”

“Moron! Attack! Attack, damn you—-!!”

“Attack…”

The familiar scenes flashed through Baylon’s eyes. The Red-White Mech in the distance was actually also raising its right leg, stomping at her. This scene was somehow coincidentally just like the move her brother Nonosiva demonstrated back then. Her brother’s voice from not too long ago seemed to still be ringing in her ears.

“Defend? Retreat? Idiot!! Defending is so you can prolong your time to attack! Retreating is so that you can find a better angle to attack. All of this is for one aim only, and that is… to kill your opponent.”

Bam!!!

In that instant, the two Mechs crashed into each other. Baylon’s arms waved around, her fists smashing hard into her opponent’s head. At the same time, she twisted her waist, and somehow eerily dodged the Red-White Mech’s stomp.

These strange moves surprised both Clint and Red Moon, who were watching from a distance.

From afar, Baylon’s Mech looked like an expert acrobatic dancer, avoiding the opponent’s dangerous attacks while at the same time using a powerful, assassin-like fist technique.

“Baylon, that punk… Who is she mimicking…?” asked Red Moon softly, puzzled.

“Mimicking?” Clint was confused. “What’s that mean?”

Chapter 892: Approaching Battle 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“The Bright Queen, Jisaiya, was one of those rare fighters who was known for having a thousand faces. She could accurately recreate the abilities of powerful pilots who she had fought before, or who had taught her in the best styles. This included mimicking their styles, personalities, and some of their special skills. Looking at it now, it seems that Baylon has truly entered our ranks. It’s just that…” Red Moon sighed.

“It’s just what? That’s a very powerful ability, if I had that too, wouldn’t I become a powerhouse in a heartbeat!?” Clint was extremely relieved.

“It’s just that when using this training method, the Willpower produced should ideally be mimicking a pilot who is powerful enough. The first person she mimics is especially important, this will drastically influence the main fighting style that she decides on in the future. I thought she picked that Red-White fella at first. But to think she actually chose…”

“Who?”

“Her brother, Nonosiva Lin.”

“Isn’t that very strong?”

“Yes, but the opponent is no normal pilot… They’re at least around Level Three, and Nonosiva is probably only at Level Three or Four right now. The mimicking level can only reach less than a third of the target at most, so against this opponent… her chances are slim.” And, after this…It did not continue about the future, as the opponents grow stronger from now on, then her first target for mimicry might…

Whoosh!!

The pitch-black glint of a sword lit up instantly. It drew their attention completely.

In the distance, Baylon was engaged in battle with the Red-White small fry, and that strange sword glint kept twinkling. Just then, Baylon’s figure actually began to merge with Nono’s Mech that Clint encountered that day.

Agile, dodging, but when she attacked, she gathered up all her power. That fierce decisiveness was not something Baylon, who was on the battlefield for the first time, could do.

Clang! The Mech’s four arms crossed, and Baylon was forced back several steps by the powerful Willpower. In a pure contest of Willpowers, she was far weaker than the enemy.

“Retreating… is also for a better… attack!!!” Cruel brutality flashed past Baylon’s eyes. Her entire Willpower somehow rose by a whole level.

In an instant, the blade in her hand shook hard, and a wisp of sharp Willpower darted into it. The blade twinkled out like an illusion, and then shot out explosively, vanishing into the air.

Boom!!

In an instant, a large chunk of the Red-White Mech’s right arm exploded suddenly, and burst into bright red flames.

“You…!!!” Inside Red-White, that woman wanted to say something, her voice mixed with shock, surprise, fear, and… pain. But she could not say it.

With a barroom, the Red-White Mech suddenly exploded. The Mech itself scattered into countless components, shooting out everywhere.

And Baylon’s Mech just stood there quietly, the era of a grandmaster slowly emanating from her. That aura was extremely familiar to Clint, it reminded him, despite himself, of that terrifying Mech that stood up slowly in the darkness back there.

“Well, f*ck me, that was fast!! This… is this a level-up when approaching battle??!!” Red Moon was a complete mess, having seen that scene. “Ain’t that my f*cking specialty?!”

“Level-up?” It was Clint’s first time seeing Baylon control a Mech too, he did not think their battle results would be so incomparable!!

“The reason she could win was mostly because of that last hit, Baylon reached Level Two Willpower. The strength of the Bright Queen Training Method lies in the mimicking, in the healing, but the key thing is that every level can increase the Mech’s speed and penetration power by two levels. In other words, at Level Two Willpower, Lonnie can increase to the speed and penetration power of a Level Four pilot using a regular training method. Add that to her mimicking a powerhouse pilot’s fighting style, and she just happens to be the weak point of any high-defense Mech! Once she reaches Level Two of the Bright Queen Training Method, even a regular Level Four pilot is no match for her, what progress speed…”

Red Moon explained solemnly.

“I just didn’t think that she could level up in her first battle. But after preparing for so long, it is about time for her. She was just one step faster than you. But even if she did level up, that opponent was no regular pilot, right…? How could she, so easily…”

Clint smiled bitterly. Even Lonnie could finish off that opponent, but last time he had been chased like a dead stray, and was nearly finished off.

“Don’t be dejected, look at what kind of opponents you faced back then! With your standards, being able to run away is already beyond your level, you’re definitely stronger than Lonnie!” Red Moon comforted him.

“No one comforts people like that, you know?” Clint was flabbergasted.

After teasing Clint for a bit, Red Moon recovered too, and kept feeling that something was off. That aura that Lonnie was emitting during her mimicry, there seemed to be something slightly wrong about it. He kept feeling as though he had seen it before… But where??

After all, even if she leveled up to Level Two, she shouldn’t be able to finish the opponent off so quickly, right? That was a Level Three Red-White pilot!

Red Moon was just going to say something, when it seemed to realize something.

“F*ck me! Isn’t that the Willpower Field that only Level Five powerhouses have!!!”

Boom!

Just then, amidst the bright red firelight, Baylon’s Mech suddenly fell on its back into the ground, motionless. Intense sparks and holes suddenly appeared on the Mech. Evidently, after the split-second explosion just now, the whole Mech was completely useless now.

“Damn! The pilot she mimicked was too strong!! Get Lonnie out now, you need to find a place for her to heal!” Seeing that, Red Moon hurriedly yelled out orders. “Mimicking takes a lot of spirit and energy every time, to mimic a Level Five powerhouse at Lonnie’s level is basically wasting her life force! Take her away now!!”

Clint’s expression changed, and he hesitated no more. Rushing up quickly, he used his enormous strength to force the cockpit door open, lifting the unconscious Baylon out from inside.

The two of them quickly kept their Mechs and some of the bits left over from Red-White, and ran into the distance.

*********************

Flying Batoid City

Garen, who was sitting cross-legged quietly on the luxurious bed, opened his eyes suddenly.

“Hm?” He seemed to have sensed some wisp of mysterious energy just now, but the moment it touched him, it vanished instantly. Those wisps of energy seemed to bring him a slightly familiar feeling.

“What… was that?” He looked around him.

Inside the fancy and luxurious room, there were many naked female bodies that were held up by metal hooks in their chins. These female corpses were all sealed in something that looked like a glass cylinder, standing there quietly all around the room like decorative pieces.

The female corpses came in a variety of shapes and sizes, but they had one thing in common. They were all extremely beautiful – innocent, seductive, adorable, knowledgeable. There were eight corpse pillars in total, revealing that naked sense of sex and violence.

Little Bitch was cowering in the inner side of the bed, leaning against the wall as she shook. She was completely naked from head to toe, and her body showed every sign that Garen had enjoyed her completely.

Garen, on the other hand, stayed between her and the corpse pillars, quietly adjusting his body’s condition. It had been such a long time since he let loose like that, so he considered it one of his rare breaks to completely relax his tense nerves.

Thinking back to that scent he picked up for just a second there, Garen still did not know where it came from, so he could only commit it to memory, waiting for a chance to catch the target again the next time it showed up.

Standing up, Garen walked out of the room, and behind him, Little Bitch hurriedly got up as well. Her body was covered in bruises from being squeezed and pinched too much, her long hair falling loose, and she wore nothing but a clean white bathrobe. She did not want to stay in the room for even a second, but if Garen did not ask to change it, she did not dare to say anything extra either, so she just had to tolerate it quietly.

There was a fully-automated machine in the room that could turn a living person into a corpse pillar, and that constantly filled her with intense terror.

The two of them left the room one after the other, and saw a beautiful, intricate little garden outside.

The red, yellow and pink flowers blossomed in bunches, with a hidden little grey-white path between them.

Some pots were suspended, some climbed up the grapevine racks, and there were even some benches and small tables placed among the green branches and leaves for leisure purposes. There were already intricate sweet drinks on the tables.

Garen looked down the grey-white path, and saw Vendant, the person who had welcomed them yesterday, standing at the door at the end of the path.

He bowed, and spoke respectfully.

“The manpower you requested is ready, and can leave at any moment.”

“Very good. As a reward, if you can find the people I’m looking for, then when I return I will give you sufficient compensation.” Garen nodded, he planned from the very start to borrow their strength in the radiation belt to look for Baylon, Red Moon, and the others.

“We are honored to serve you, but recently the White Light Organization’s Mechs are starting to patrol all around the radiation belt, so our territory has been drastically reduced…” Vendant said simply.

“Just try your best.” Garen frowned. Lifting his hand to check Anda’s message, he learned that everyone was going to depart soon, they had gotten enough batteries. “When we return, we will also pass through here for supplies, so I hope you won’t disappoint me.”

“If we find the targets, my lord, could we possibly change the compensation we receive in return?” asked Vendant, very respectfully.

“Speak.”

“We hope to obtain relevant techniques regarding Nutrient Repair Troughs.”

“Repair Troughs? Aren’t those just simple Maintenance Stations?” Garen was speechless. That was severely outdated technology in the Regions, these people’s level of technology was probably the result of researching broken Mechs that were tossed away and eliminated many years ago. To think that after so long, nobody from the Regions ever gave them the newest technology…

As though sensing Garen’s confusion and contempt, Vendant explained with a bitter smile.

“Regarding the latest technology, because we don’t have enough alloys and raw material, there’s no point even if we obtain it. Our only way is to trade for the technology we can use. There’s no helping it.”

“I see, I’ll obtain it for you when we get back.” Garen nodded nonchalantly, these techniques were sold for ten Universal Units in the Inner Courtyard, even if he gave them for free, he would not want to waste the space.

There were probably too few pilots who came out of the Regions, and even fewer who acted independently like this. Even if there were any, the chances that they would just happen to arrive at Flying Batoid City were even lower. That was why there were situations like these.

“Thank you for your generosity, is there anything else you need, my lord?” Vendant asked respectfully, his head lowered.

“This woman…” Garen looked around at Little Bitch behind him. It was her first time, and she offered it to him, plus her personality did not seem so twisted, so he could put some time into her.

“She is already your private property, sir,” continued Vendant hurriedly.

“Mn, give her a job, I’ll come check on her now and then.” Garen nodded. He wanted to set up a source of intel here in the radiation belt too. The environment here was cruel, but there was still a lot he could make use of here.

To outsiders, this place was extremely dangerous as they could get the radiation disease if they were not careful, so they would avoid this place whenever possible. But to him, such low levels of radiation was nothing.

“That is perfectly fine.”

“Let’s go! Garen!”

Anda’s voice came from the watch.

Garen checked his watch, it was around ten in the morning.

“I’m coming now.”

“Next stop, the War Wastes.”

“Got it.”

After arranging everything, Garen hurried towards the place where the Mechs were parked.

Chapter 893: Hunt 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The black mountain peaks flitted past beneath them one after the other, as the four Mechs slowly flew past the black mountain ranges, advancing quickly in a specific direction.

Beneath them, on the peaks of the various mountains, between some stone platforms on the sides or peaks of some mountains, they could also vaguely see black-grey wastes and ruins. There were even some abandoned bases, with the faint movement of creatures that could not be seen clearly within.

The ruins were scattered sparsely all over, and some had several huge yellow cogs of different sizes exposed to the elements. The cogs turned slowly, occasionally spewing out white smoke.

Garen looked down to watch the scenery and ruins beneath him.

“Are there people in these ruined bases? Why are they still moving now?”

The Mech was on auto-pilot, so the pilots were not controlling them, and basically acted as independent passengers. That naturally meant they could also talk freely and discuss other matters.

A red symbol lit up slightly on the control panel in front of him, and Linda’s voice came from it.

“Garen, this is your first time out here, and you don’t know the place that well yet. Basically no one actually lives in these ruins, the reason they can move on their own is mostly because of some geothermal sources, but since this is the radiation zone, even though the geothermal energy here is considerable, its radiation pollution is even more so. That’s why even radiation people don’t dare to approach this place too often. Firstly, because the radiation interference here is too severe, so if they’re not careful, they’ll get an even more troublesome disease. Secondly, there are a lot of radioactive mutated beasts and radioactive corpses there. Most normal people can’t handle that at all.”

“Radioactive corpses?”

“Yeah, after being exposed to enough radiation and mutating, corpses will develop an innate desire to hunt for food. That’s why they will be reanimated, and start wandering around on their own. When there is enough radiation energy, they’ll be free to hunt around everywhere, but once the energy is depleted, they will collapse to the ground and become corpses again. So it depends on your luck when you enter ruins as well, if you’re lucky, you might be able to find some documents or materials that are more valuable,” Linda explained with a smile. “I went into some ruins before as well, but it’s very dangerous in there, and regular pilots will practically just turn into food in there. Unless you are Level Three or above, it’s best not to think about going in.”

Garen agreed, and thanked Linda for her explanation. Then he began to observe the ruins beneath him.

As they continued advancing, soon enough, Anda’s voice came in through the intercom.

“Careful, there’s a flock of mutated birds ahead.”

Just ahead of the four Mechs, a swarm of black birds was headed right for them.

These birds were each about a meter long, and their bodies were not too different from regular birds. But they had two pairs, or four furry fox ears on their heads, and their mouths were not straight like other birds. Instead, they were like so many sharp hooks.

Squawk squawk squawk…

In the midst of the piercing noise.

Anda’s Mech suddenly emitted a sound wave field.

As the sound wave spread out, the flock of mutated birds instantly appeared to panic, and most of the birds scattered in all directions. Only a few of the strongest birds kept rushing at them, and seemed even fiercer for it.

Anda’s high-powered ray gun kept shooting, and a dozen bolts of white light shot out, accurately hitting the heads of these birds, and utterly destroying them. The corpses fell down, but before they even reached the ground, they were surrounded by swarms of what appeared to be blood-sucking flying bugs that came out of nowhere. In no time at all, only a bunch of skeletons were left crashing into the ground.

Garen was at the back of the team, and seeing how easily Anda handled the mutated birds, he slowly relaxed the guard that he had put up.

“Ahead of us is the largest war ruins in these parts, the War Wastes. If we search here for a bit, we may be lucky enough to find newly-condensed mutated metals,” said Anda’s voice through the intercom.

“Be careful, there are many radioactive corpses hidden in the War Wastes, and some of the mutated beasts are very strong as well. There are even things like Level Four mutated beasts, don’t cause too much of a commotion and stir trouble,” Anda instructed carefully.

The few of them all indicated that they understood, and began to lower the Mech’s height, flying towards the largest huge black mountain range directly ahead of them.

The black mountain was far taller than all the other mountains around it, compared to its surroundings, it looked like an adult towering over children. Even if three people scanned the huge mountain from within their Mechs, they still would not be able to see the edges of the mountain through their scanning visions, and could only see the large swathe of black mountain rock.

“There’s a pretty decent name here, it’s called the Sleeping Forest. If you don’t wake it up, everything’s easy,” said Aves loudly, after whistling once. “I hear that pilots have even found really precious ancient energy furnaces and nuclear weapons here, that stuff can be traded for a whole customized Mech, y’know!”

“If it’s a slightly better nuclear weapon, you’ll be lucky to trade it for a small-scale battleship,” replied Anda with a laugh. “Be careful, the radiation will reach warning levels soon, we need to use extra energy to form a barrier in there to avoid being infected. I’ve installed anti-radiation equipment in all three Mechs, but this takes up a ton of energy. If we can’t find anything within an hour, we have to all gather here, we can’t stay for long. Otherwise, don’t blame me for not reminding you if you get the radiation disease.”

“Got it!” X3

The four Mechs instantly scattered, and headed for the large black-grey metal city at the peak of the mountain.

The closer Garen got, the more he found the city on the peak strange.

It was dead, and had no sense of life whatsoever, but there was an immense pressure that seemed like it might explode at any time. There were floating pieces of metal and huge yellow twisting cogs everywhere.

As the city of ruins grew closer and closer, larger and larger, he split up with the rest of the team, and flew towards the eastern side of the city alone.

The city was extremely vast, about as big as Blackboard City. Garen simply flew towards one of the three large areas, and randomly landed one on of the colored boxes there. There were more than ten such boxes in the whole area, and each was the size of Flying Batoid City.

In the wide streets, all that was left of the old bumper car fields was a regular shelter tarpaulin to keep out the rain. The Ferris Wheel, with its many broken support pillars, was like a battered windmill. It would occasionally move randomly, creaking loudly as it went.

The angle Garen had flown into just happened to be a theme park. The Mech landed slowly, right next to a merry-go-round on its right. The spinning red wooden horses moved slowly, and even emitted crisp-sounding music.

‘Lalala… lalala… The kite is flying… fish are swimming… the quiet life needs more to be satisfied, lalala… lalala…’

Garen could even still understand the music from the merry-go-round. Although the accent was slightly strange, and it was a little girl’s voice, he could still understand what was being said.

Gusts of cold wind blew past, and as he looked across the whole city area, he found no sense of life in the theme park. Except for a few things that were moving on their own, the whole place was practically deserted.

Bang… bang bang bang…

Garen raised his Mech’s steps, and walked forward. The heavy Mech walked around the theme park, the vibrations from its steps spreading, and the empty echoes returning in response.

“This place… sure is deserted.” Garen frowned tightly, for some reason, he kept feeling a mysterious threat from this place. It was mild, and faint, but it felt as though something here could actually threaten his life.

The empty theme park gave him a very uncomfortable feeling.

Creak.

Suddenly, there was a sound from behind him. Garen quickly activated the sensor behind him, and saw that it was a swing in the empty space moving faintly, as though someone had just stood up from it.

Pulling back his gaze, Garen began to move again, pausing here and there.

Soon enough, the theme park’s entrance was right ahead of him. It was an arch-shaped painted door, but many parts of the white paint had been washed off by the tides of time.

There was a model of a clown, more than five meters tall, at the side of the gate. It was dressed completely in red, and had bright red curly hair, two round red cherries pasted onto its cheeks. It looked like it might really make a child smile.

Crash!

Suddenly, there was the sound of glass shattering.

Garen frowned, and turned on the intercom. Aves had probably gone off in that direction.

“Aves?” he tried asking, but there was no reply.

There was just crackling in the intercom, it was all just intense static and interference.

Turning off the intercom with a smack, Garen knew that it would not work here anymore. Looks like he could only contact them once he was out of here.

The instant he walked out of the theme park, Garen instinctively felt as though the clown’s eyes had moved a little.

He could not help but turn around and looked at the clown statue carefully. It was clearly made of stone and metal, its eyes were just drawn on.

“Was it an illusion?” Garen had always had faith in his instincts, but now he could not help but doubt.

He turned around and walked towards the door. Outside the theme park, there was a pitch-black dark alleyway, with tall buildings on both sides blocking off half of the light. Above, there were slightly dim, lead-colored clouds; below, it was the dark and shadow-lit streets. The ground was clean, and there were no signs of damage. But there simply was not a lot of light, so it looked rather dark and dingy.

“There should be usable materials in here…” Garen thought about it, and turned off his Mech’s scanner. However, the problem was that the interference of the radiation here was too immense, and he could not use it at all. The scanner was filled with countless red dots, it was evidently malfunctioning because of the interference.

All of a sudden, he seemed to sense something aiming at him.

The Mech stopped abruptly, and took one step to the left.

Bam!!

A deep crater appeared in the place he was supposed to walk to.

“Who!”

Garen followed the direction the bullet crater came from, and just happened to see a blurred silhouette fading away quickly.

He was just going to activate the Mech to give chase, when suddenly he felt a chill from beside him.

“Shit! It was that…”

Barroom!!

In the intense explosion of green light, the entire street and the two large buildings on either side of it was bathed in a sickly green.

Super-effective acid missiles!!

The large amount of green liquid sprayed everywhere. Even if he reacted at lightning speed, dodging part of it, a little bit still got onto his Mech’s anti-radiation barrier.

The transparent barrier sizzled on contact with the green acid.

Garen flew back far, and entered the theme park before he could check the condition of his Mech. The person who ambushed him just now was definitely no ordinary person, such super-effective acid missiles might not work so well outside, but under these highly radioactive conditions, its effect was extremely considerable. It could consume large amounts of the energy used by the anti-radiation barrier, but the opponent could not take down the barrier here, or else the intense radioactive pollution would instantly corrode the pilot and their Mech, leaving them to become radioactive people, which was a fate worse than death. To immediately fall from being a high-level hotshot to becoming the most average, low-level radiation person!

The Mech was not damaged too severely, but the explosion of the acid missile had taken up at least 20% of the Mech’s energy resources.

Garen thought back to that ambush from just now, the movements were lightning fast, and his own Willpower somehow could not lock on the target, so that person had to be at least Level Three. And most importantly, their actions seemed very well-rehearsed, they had fired off a shot and retreated without even waiting to see the results. This was the main reason they could avoid Garen’s detection even though they were only Level Three.

Chapter 894: Hunt 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the other end, within the waste ruins.

Two pale yellow Mechs were surrounding Anda’s standard Blackboard Mech, from the front and the back, in the middle of the main street.

“You never thought this would happen, right? It only took us three days since the Hunting Order was released to find you, but you sure run fast, little punk!” said one yellow Mech, laughing coldly.

“That woman sure is cold, to actually send the two of you to hunt me. I bet she really paid for it, huh?” Sitting inside the Mech, Anda’s voice was calm, but nobody could see the sheen of sweat on his forehead now. The two extremely powerful and troublesome Willpowers were suppressing him tightly, making him unable to get away and escape. Because he knew that as soon as he moved, he would be immediately destroyed by their long-range attack!

“You offended the First Young Miss and still managed to get so far away, that makes you unprecedented. Now don’t say we didn’t give you a chance, since we’re from the same family, you can make a move first.” A cold woman’s voice came from the yellow Mech behind him,

“Windling, if you get involved in a family’s power struggle for succession, you won’t get off easy even if you are a Level Five Guest, don’t you get that?!” Anda said loudly.

“Of course I understand,” replied the woman behind him. “But it was your fault for killing the Young Miss’s fiance, it can’t be helped that the two of us were invited out for that.”

“Hehe, if I don’t kill him, do I just wait for him to kill me? I have no interest in sitting around and waiting to do,” Anda laughed coldly.

“Are you still trying to buy time? Give it up, those teammates of yours can barely protect themselves, do you truly think they’ll have the time to rush over and help you?” said Windling calmly. “Even if you are all the prodigious elites from the Blackboard Academy’s Inner Courtyard, before your potential becomes power, it is still merely potential.”

“Do you still dare to kill them? The elites of the Inner Courtyard are no joke, you know.”

“Kill them? Of course that’s impossible, we just want them to retreat of their own accord.” Before Windling finished her sentence, she abruptly drew two long silver-white pistols, and aimed one of them at Anda. “Alright, let’s get this over with, quick.”

Pop-pop!

There were two dull noises from the barrel of the pistols, which flew into the air and turned into two huge yellow silk webs that headed straight for Anda, threatening to engulf him.

******************

Garen carefully used something to scratch the liquid off his barrier. The metal that was covered by the acid quickly began to emit wisps of white smoke as they corroded. It was even starting to soften, turning from solid and hard to something as soft as leather.

The opponent’s aim was very clear, they just wanted him to leave these ruins. The attack just now clearly used super-effective acid missiles to those ends, they had no intention of actually taking his life.

Glancing at the energy the Mech had left, he saw that there was only 52% remaining. After the long journey here, he had still had 80%, but now there was only 52% left. Evidently, this was the result of the acid missile just now as well as the high radiation levels here.

“Since you want me to leave here, there must be an untold secret here in these ruins. Either that, or… they want us to split up from someone in the team, breaking up our formation so we act separately.” Using the answer from before, Garen instantly came up with two ideas. “And the opponent has no killing intent, which must mean they know our team’s identity. In that case, the second option would be highly likely.”

“Garen, you there?” Suddenly, Linda’s voice came from above.

Garen turned around, and saw Linda slowly letting her Mech descend from the sky above him and to the side. “I finally found you guys, Aves has already run here. He was also attacked by an acid missile, they don’t want to kill us, it’s more like they want to chase us away. After I contacted Aves, his Mech was running really low on energy, so I told him to go back first.”

“Do you know who attacked us?” asked Garen in a low voice.

“I don’t know, but… I went to Captain Anda’s location, but I couldn’t find him. I just noticed that there were marks on the ground indicating he was attacked by missiles, evidently the people attacking us did not use acid missiles against the Captain,” said Linda, somewhat worriedly.

Garen narrowed his eyes, slightly surprised that Linda could find all three of them within such a short period of time. After all, the interference here was through the roof, the sensors on the Mech were practically disabled, so they could only rely on their own sense of direction.

But everyone had their own secrets, those who dared to accept this quest and come out here would all be above average characters. After all, the radiation belt was not somewhere regular pilots would simply agree to enter.

“What do you suggest?” Garen thought about it, and asked quietly.

“I suspect that they’re trying to separate us from the Captain. Their true aim, should be Captain Anda!” said Linda softly. It went without saying that both of them knew that Anda was also an alias.

“What I mean is, since this is Captain Anda’s own problem, we should just let him settle it himself. After all, this is his private matter.”

“Is that what you think?” Garen’s voice was calm.

“Of course.”

“Then let’s wait outside for now.” Garen had no intention of interfering with Anda’s personal matters either. And he was not worried about those attackers, he was more concerned with that feeling of discomfort he got from these ruins.

The two Mechs slowly rose into the air, one after the other, and flew towards the outskirts of the ruins.

Barroom!!

Suddenly there was an intense explosion in the distance, and they could vaguely hear Anda’s angry howl, like that of an injured beast.

“Looks like Captain’s having a hard time…” Linda stopped her Mech slowly, staying suspended in mid-air.

“What do you want to do?” As soon as Garen spoke, he saw Linda dash towards the source of the sound.

He hesitated for a moment in mid-air, but in the end Garen quickly followed her.

*****************

“Endless!”

“!” The Yellow Mech was like a peacock with its tail feathers open, instantly shooting out several dozen or even up to a hundred white laser rays from its back. Each of these lasers was as thick as a finger, and they covered the sky as they turned and pounced at Anda.

On the other end, the Yellow Mech Windling was watching coldly, her arms crossed.

Psst-psst-psst!

Countless laser rays pierced through the surrounding buildings, and rushed out towards Anda from the ground in all directions.

Anda quickly took flight, and as he performed a series of movements to avoid them, he also constantly shot out many high-powered ray gun lasers, to neutralize the many white laser rays. Even so, he was still hit occasionally, and kept groaning out in pain.

“Endless!” He also released an explosion of countless white lasers, but these lasers were nowhere near as bright as his opponent’s.

Just now, he had used this same move to fight against the opponent, but unfortunately he had failed. Be it in their Willpower, special techniques, or their skill in their killing moves, or even how well they matched their Mechs, Anda was at the disadvantage.

This time, the many white lasers he released neutralized most of the opponent’s similar white lasers, but some of them still hit Anda’s Mech’s shoulders, sizzling on contact.

With a bang, he crashed into the ground, his back leaning against the buildings on one side of the street.

“Give it up, and hand over the map, we’ll make it painless for you,” said Windling emotionlessly from the side.

“Hehe, if you want it, come get it yourself,” replied Anda with a cold laugh.

“Foolish.” Windling straightened up, and shook out her joints. Whoosh!

Four metallic silver thorns appeared from her back suddenly, sparkling in the light like a fan. The Mech’s hands reached back and pulled out two silver thorns, then she began to walk towards Anda slowly.

Beside them, the other Mech wisely chose to stop attacking, and instead let the two of them go one-on-one.

In that second, Windling’s steps suddenly crossed, and she slid, ending up beside Anda. The thorns in her hands pierced at Anda’s waist like an illusion, and her whole Mech body left a series of shadows as the other thorn stabbed towards the head of Anda’s Mech.

And by then, the speed of Anda’s Mech had been reduced considerably, it seemed to be far slower than it had been.

Just then, Garen and Linda were already nearby. Seeing this scene, Garen’s heart was slightly shaken. This Windling was actually also a real-life Level Five powerhouse. To normal people, a Level Five powerhouse was truly a peak-level pilot, and they usually could only barely see one once every few years. To think Garen bumped into a new Level Five powerhouse so soon on his excursion.

And this one was not sent here by the Academy.

He had seen the way she fought, and knew that this Yellow Mech had clearly undergone countless battles. She evidently had an unnatural level of fighting experience, there was no hesitation whatsoever in her movements. They were fast, merciless, precise.

“The two of you, please turn back for now. We’re handling personal matters here.” Just then, a man’s voice came from behind Garen and Linda.

The two of them turned around, and saw that a Yellow Mech had appeared there without them knowing. “We are the subordinates of the Thousand Year Tree, Lord Donnie Largewood, here to settle some private grievances with your captain, Anda. I ask for your kind cooperation.”

“Higher-ups from Thousand Year Tree, huh? Donnie Largewood…” Garen knew this person, he had the same status as Britney in Blue Narcissus, and was also a famous peak-level higher-up among the Thousand Year Trees. In a group like the Thousand Year Trees, anyone who could reach a high position surely fought their way up with their true power.

“Anda has an important item needed for our quest, and you were the ones who attacked us first, isn’t that a bit too much?” Linda replied loudly.

But by then, Garen had vaguely sensed that more Mechs were beginning to surround the two of them, the other side was just trying to buy time!

He and Linda exchanged a glance through the intercom, and at almost exactly the same time, just as the other side was going to reply, the two of them yelled simultaneously.

“Do it!!”

Psst!!

A small and delicate white dagger instantly flew out of Linda’s hand, and abruptly pierced the back of Garen’s waist.

Garen was just stepping forward and getting ready to dash, pulling out a long black blade with his right hand at lightning speeds. He slashed straight down at the opponent’s head, his speed instantly reaching the limits of this Mech.

But he never thought that Linda, who was behind him, would instantly ambush him!

“You?!??”

“Die!!” Linda’s dagger abruptly emitted some blue light, and became even faster, as though she was holding a blinding ball of blue light, that she smashed towards the side of Garen’s Mech.

There was a sizzling sound.

Garen turned around, and somehow managed to pull back in the unlikeliest situation. If it was anyone else, they would not be able to pull back under the influence of such explosive momentum, but Garen did it. That was how powerful his Ten Thousand True Technique was as a combat skill, as the final combination of all his martial arts, and added to his true Level Five power that he did not completely unleash yet, he could only reach the surface of Level Four Willpower.

Moving instantly, one of Garen’s hands turning into a fierce fist, crashing into Linda’s cockpit. He was actually going for the kill in exchange for getting injured himself!

Chapter 895: Abrupt Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Linda’s pupils shrunk as she wasn’t willing to fight Garen to death. She was an assassin, not a fighter who fought to the death. She was stunned as her opponent was able to react in time and counter. Her flawless assassination attempt was all for nothing.

At this point in time, she couldn’t do much but to feel unfortunate as all she could do now was take a step back far away from him.

Garen, who had been ambushed, couldn’t pay attention to her as the surrounding Yellow Mechs had released a series of white homing missiles aimed at him at the same time.

Lines of white smoke from the homing missiles were left in the air as they zoomed towards him from all directions.

Kaboom!!

The missiles exploded, turning the area where Garen’s Mech’s stood into a sea of fire as thick smoke kept coming out from it.

The Pilots inside the yellow Mechs frowned as they could sense that their opponent did not walk the same path as them, yet he was able to counter ambush them.

The lead Mech hesitated for a moment before raising his hand, gesturing everyone to fall back.

“It’s an assassin from the Exterminet, so don’t spread this to anyone else.”

The Yellow Mechs stopped attacking after they had fired all of their homing missiles. Their opponent had used them to his advantage when he ambushed them at the moment they attacked him. These members of the Thousand Year Tree were obviously unhappy when they were used by the Exterminet’s assassin, who was not to be trifled with.

“Big brother, why don’t we keep them in check here, since we outnumber them…”

“Idiot! Why would you want to fight to the death whenever you feel like it? Don’t you think that they would fight back? And when they do, won’t people die? I didn’t bring you out to simply kill anyone! I have the responsibility to bring you all back safe and sound!” the Yellow Mech leader scoffed. “That is an elite from the inner academy. He’s not some common Pilot that we can kill!”

The Mech who recommended a massacre stopped voicing out.

Garen’s body started appearing once more. Even he couldn’t avoid being injured from all that firepower directed at him in that instant. This was especially true towards Linda’s ambush, where she had almost destroyed her body’s waist support. The waist support was a critical point of a spinal support system as the body would only lay on the ground and not move once it was destroyed.

The Willpower-powered Mech was about to form similar structures to of a living being.

He was fortunate that he was able to gather his Level Five Willpower to form a Body Field which blocked off most of the explosion and repelled the ambushed attack. However, his body had been slightly damaged and he was left with about thirty percent of his energy source.

Crack crack…

Garen’s Black Mech moved slowly as he punched with all his might to the left with his fist.

Boom.

Linda’s Black Mech which appeared on the left was hit and instantly pushed back.

“Why did you ambush me?” Garen, who was inside the Mech didn’t change his expression as he asked. He who had not trusted them from the beginning had nothing much to say now that he was being ambushed. However, he was rather skeptical of this ambush in this critical period. Linda’s personality was not very suspicious and he himself knew that he hadn’t offended her in any way as well.

“Someone had offered one hundred million in place of your head,” Linda laughed. Although her body was pushed back, she seemed to possess a high defense as she was not injured at all.

“Is it the Exterminet?” Garen suddenly understood the situation. However, with his personality, he didn’t care at all as she wouldn’t be a threat to her even if she, a Level Four, tried to ambush him…

As this idea surfaced in his mind, a powerful Willpower slowly surged up around him.

Three similar Level Five Willpower-powered Mechs started flying up as they surrounded Garen. In addition to Linda who was a Level Four elite… The powers they revealed in that instant was clearly the Resonance Skills as it wouldn’t be this powerful otherwise. It was the strength of a Level Five who knew the Resonance Skill.

In that instant, there were four elites of his caliber that had surrounded Garen.

Even the Yellow Mechs had nothing to say when such a scenario unfolded before their eyes.

“Boss, what should we do now?” a Yellow Mech whispered. “We’ve just ambushed that person. If he were to lump us together with these assassins…”

“What else can we do?! We don’t interfere with other people’s business!” the lead Yellow Mech waved its hand. “Everyone retreat!”

Within a few seconds, every Yellow Mech in the scene had retreated and hidden.

They were here to assassinate Anda and were not on the same team as these assassins from the Exterminet. This person who was willing to reward a hundred million Universal Unit for a person’s head definitely had a deep background and was someone who shouldn’t be messed with. As for the ambush earlier, it would be easier to explain to the others if Anda were to survive as they were simply defending themselves from the other party’s ambush. However, if they were to be lumped together with the assassins, then it would spell trouble for both parties.

The situation was completely chaotic.

Anda was being oppressed by Windling, his body covered in injuries, on the streets between the buildings on the right. On his right over a row of buildings, Garen was being surrounded by assassins from the Exterminet.

Four Level Five Willpower had locked onto Garen’s body.

His heart sank for a moment. Even if he currently possessed the skill of a Level Five Pilot, he was still being surrounded by four powerhouses of the same caliber. Some of them were probably powerhouses from within the Inner Courtyard, who at least had a trump card or two that could at least ensure their safety. Elites who were able to enter the Inner Courtyard were at least flawless in their Combat Skills and each of them possessed unique killing moves. In comparison, they were at least on the same calibers as those Grandmasters of Combat who practiced Living Secret Techniques, where their skills were at least half of Garen’s.

Fortunately, he had taken measures against assassins from the Exterminet once he was aware of their existence.

Garen slowly took out a small and exquisite black box.

He then looked at his body’s remaining energy, which had about 28% left.

“I’ll end this battle quickly!” Linda scoffed as she was the first one to leap forward. At the same time, the other three followed along tightly as they attacked. The other two surrounded him as the last one stood behind with a Deadlight Cannon on his shoulder, with its muzzle glowing faintly red.

“Earth Shattering Slash!!” a stroke of white light in the form of a knife appeared on Linda’s dagger as it shattered the ground and slashed towards Garen at great speed.

Suddenly, the White Light Knife split into three as they arched and went towards Garen in three different directions.

Garen jumped lightly. With two black knives in his hands, Garen danced around as he took the shape of a black ball to block the incoming attacks of two Mechs from the side. The overwhelmingly powerful Level Five Willpower bypassed through Garen’s knives and clashed with his Willpower.

A buzz was heard and his Level Four Crouched Eagle Talon Willpower was instantly broken while the other two Willpowers were slightly weakened. These two Willpowers continued moving towards the body’s core. Once they reached the core of the body, the Mech would be under their control no matter how strong the Mech was.

Garen gathered his unnamed Level Five Willpower and separated them into two portions to counter them.

Boom!!

Three Level Five Willpowers clashed against one another at the same time and exploded from Garen’s battle knives. Those who were outside of the battle could clearly see that the knives’ bodies were twisted for a slight moment as an invisible force field was released.

Clank. Three of the Mechs were pushed back as Garen and the other two Pilots sustained light injuries.

“What training method is this!? For a Willpower to be able to possess such strong qualities and be able to counter one’s full force with only half of his strength?!” Linda was shocked but her greed started taking over after a while.

“If only I could obtain such a training method…”

“Fire!” the Assassin Mech from afar finally attacked as a red beam was fired from the canon, as it vaporized everything in its trajectory and the surroundings of its beam.

With a high energy red laser cannon firing at Garen, he had no choice but to evade this bucket-thick red pillar with all his might.

Linda immediately took a step back as she gritted her teeth. A black lightning grenade appeared in her hand out of nowhere, and she immediately threw it towards Garen as her heart ached.

The black lightning grenade cracked open as it shot out a huge amount of blue plasma. This plasma was glowing intensely as electric arcs spread about and behind Garen, sealing his only route in evading the attacks.

This highly concentrated plasma grenade had cost six million each and was able to deal serious damage to a Level Five Mech.

Death awaited Garen if he moved to the front and the plasma grenade had covered his entire back. It occurred the moment Garen decided to back off from the two Level Five Mechs before him.

The assassins’ cooperation was very tacit as there were not a moment of pause in between their attacks.

Garen was in a period of delay as he was slightly numbed by the barrage of two Willpowers. Although his body reacted the moment it sensed danger, his body was still a normal standard model from the Blackboard Region. It was still acceptable when reacting to a normal condition, but his follow up actions after consecutive fine-tuned response motions couldn’t keep up to speed. There was too much Willpower information in a very short amount of time and it had been bottlenecked within the Body’s system, causing his Body to be not able to react in time.

However, it was this instance that made Garen realize that it was necessary for him to have a Mech of his own for him to unleash his full potential. It would be his demise if he were to keep using a Mech that did not suit him!!

With his Mech unable to move, Garen was unable to do anything to avoid the incoming attacks.

Sizzle!!

The thick Deadlight was shot directly at Garen and huge amounts of plasma liquid kept eroding his Energy Field, depleting his remaining energy source even further.

As the Deadlight was about to penetrate the Mech’s protective field, a sawtooth-like shockwave instantly spread outwards with Garen as the epicenter without any sound and warning.

The edge of the sawtooth shockwave kept spinning and it brought forth a powerful momentum as it pushed away and disintegrated the Deadlight and plasma at the same time.

Garen sat inside the cockpit as the black box inside his hand broke down slowly and turned into a pile of fine black dust, slipping through the gaps of his fingers.

It was an Instantaneous Paper Box, a life-saving item that he had obtained from the Honorable Noble. It was able to instantly release an Inherited Level momentum that spanned out fifteen meters. However, it did not possess any lethality and could only be used for self-protection.

The sawtooth-like shockwave had such a strong momentum that it had even sent the assassin Mechs flying. Linda was pushed back as well as she crashed into the building by the side, leaving a clear indentation.

In that instant, Garen maneuvered his Body as he leaped out of the area so that he was no longer trapped. While he wanted to kill them, it would be difficult as he had spent too much energy. His power source was insufficient to begin with, and it had plunged down to the critical point as he was continuously ambushed. In the end, he was left with 12% and it would still continue to deplete.

Garen flew up into the sky and saw that the assassin with the Deadlight Cannon was still trying to attack him as he pointed the cannon towards him. However, Garen immediately flew towards him as he shut off his main engine while he fell down from the sky. He had made use the momentum gained from the gravity and engine to change his trajectory.

Boom!

The cannon missed as a red line was drawn in the sky.

Chapter 896: Abrupt Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Damn it! This guy is cunning to the point he’s still alive!” the assassin threw away the Deadlight Cannon that was on the verge of melting due to the high temperature. It was an inferior product as it could only be fired twice and could no longer be used.

“That was a one-time-use explosion instrument. It’s pure momentum and possesses no lethality! Go after him!” Linda walked forward as she activated her Mech to chase after him.

What had been thought to be a foolproof siege had failed. If they were to let their opponent escape, then they could no longer remain in the assassination business. This was especially true towards both of the Level Five assassins as they had only done so little before being pushed back by their opponent’s instrument. They were practically useless!

The intense battle had raised some attention from the other side as Windling looked at the other side through the building’s gap and was stunned as she saw Garen’s Mech flying off at immense speed. At that crucial moment, Anda executed his killing moves twice in a row as the superimposed Endless Beam was now doubled. Even though his original killing move had low lethality, it would be greatly enhanced if its strength were doubled.

Pew pew pew!!

A huge amount of white beams had densely covered the whole street. This gave Windling and the other person a run for their money. Who knew that Anda, who was on the verge of death, could still release such a horrifying skill.

An electric mist spread about around Anda’s body similar to the blood mist that could be seen when a person exploded. Although his Mech looked similar to a standard model from the outside, the inner section of his Mech had been modified so many times that it was practically one of the best in the region.

However, his Body had suffered major damage as he had used Endless consecutively in such a short amount of time. 80% of the systems were down and the body had lost its combat capability as only the engine was still functional.

Anda took this opportunity to fly up in the sky under the cover of the endless white beams towards Garen and the killers.

It only took Windling two seconds to neutralize all the white beams with her Endless Neutralization. She looked up at the sky as she stared at Anda who was getting further away with a gloomy face. He was already out of the range of her Endless long range attack.

“Chase after him! He can’t run that far!!”

***************

Garen sat inside the cockpit without any change in expression while the Body was slicing through the air at high speed. He had been chased so many times that he had gotten used to it.

Although the Body was able to enhance a person’s capability, it could only be a burden if it didn’t have any energy.

All four assassins behind him were Elites from the Inner Courtyard. He could still easily solve the situation if he were in his usual condition. After all, a pilot was only slightly stronger than a commoner under normal circumstances. If there were only three people, he could kill them directly since he had a higher quality Willpower and combat skills that far surpassed theirs. He could have easily dealt with them with his skills.

However, with the fourth person in the field, Garen’s lack of power and where his limits were were apparent to himself.

With his current strength, it would be the top news if it were to spread that he had taken care of three elites of the same level without Resonance. One had to realize that even the strongest young elite within the Blackboard Region, Blackstar, could only fight against two people when he had been at his level.

These Level Five Pilots were no ordinary pilots from common households. Those Pilots’ martial arts were filled with flaws. Excluding Garen, any same Level Pilot from the Inner Courtyard or even the Level Four could easily handle them.

Any of the four assassins behind Garen could easily kill two normal Level Five Pilots. This was the clear difference between elites and non-elites.

Take the Red-White Mech that Garen had killed as an example. If he were to encounter these four back then, he would be killed in an instant as these four people were equivalent to at least five Red-White Mechs when they teamed up. The Red-White back then had been a product of Leveling up at an incredible rate so all he could rely on was the strength of his Mech.

“How embarrassing… I can only run for my life since the Mech doesn’t have enough energy,” Garen wasn’t anxious at all. Even if he had lost his Body, he wouldn’t be infected by the radiation sickness when exposed to the external environment, unlike other Pilots. He would at most escape from his cockpit and hide.

Although he was being chased, his opponent’s energy sources were finite. They had at least exhausted half of their energy from all of the chasing, including this flight. Even if they had brought along their backup energy packs, they would still require time to stop and recharge their energy sources.

This was especially the case for Linda as her energy should be similar to his, where it was on the verge of depletion.

Garen smirked.

Although the Instantaneous Box had been exhausted, he still had more items up his sleeves…

The engine in Garen’s Mech would occasionally release a burst to avoid the long range attacks that came from behind with great precision. At the same time, he managed to reduce the air drag so he was always slightly faster than the Mechs behind chasing him at full speed.

He rushed into the forest of radioactive stone pillars the instant he landed on the ground and quickly flew out from an unimaginable angle as he escaped once more.

“This bastard!!” Linda gritted her teeth as she chased from behind.

Warnings of energy depletion were constantly sent out to the Body. She was almost out of energy and yet the Black Mech in front of her could still fly about freely.

Rumor had it that technically skilled Pilots were able to reduce the air drag to the extent that they were able to increase their speed and reduce energy consumption at the same time. The key to achieving this was the minor adjustment of one’s Willpower. She had seen this technique before from the powerhouses within the organization but she didn’t expect Garen to know this technique as well.

“Even if you can reduce your energy consumption while flying, you’ll still have to deal with them even when I’m out of energy! You can’t possibly escape from us!” she muttered angrily. She had been so confident in this mission that she believed she could easily earn the hundred million Units bounty. However, she didn’t expect her target to be so cunning.

“Fuck!!!” one of the assassin pilots shouted through the communication device out of the blue.

“Rainstorm, what are you doing!” Linda saw the Mech behind her jolted.

“The high energy fan has run out of juice!” Rainstorm cried in frustration. “We wouldn’t have let him slip through our fingers this easily if we knew that he was a Level Five Pilot!”

“I’d done a background check on this kid. He’s a normal Pilot that came from the Outer Courtyard, but how could he possesses such a powerful and high-quality Willpower training method?! Furthermore, he possessed the quality of a normal Pilot when he was in his first year and yet he has suddenly become a Level Five Pilot whose skill has risen so quickly recently with this training method. One could dismiss him as a talent who went unnoticed if he were a Level Four, or perhaps the Level Five Crouched Eagle Talon is not a big deal. However, this high-quality Level Five training method is definitely something! He’s only in his third year too! There are only a few others in this year with a high-quality Level Five Willpower and each of them has a very powerful background! He’s definitely hiding something big from everyone!” the other Pilot said in a deep tone.

“Our employer has sent his men to that bastard’s home in hopes of finding some clue. If he can’t find anything there, the least we can do is to kidnap his family and threaten him. Hehe, if we are able to reveal the secret to boost the Level of Willpower within a short amount of time to the public, do you think the Blackboard’s higher-ups will let him off the hook?” the last Pilot started smirking.

“Only us here know that this bastard possesses a unique Level Five Willpower. Since our employer isn’t afraid of breaking the rules, why should we be!” Rainstorm smirked. “Perhaps the reason why our employer is willing to go this far is to get his hands on this bastard’s unique training method!”

As these people mused with one another, they soon followed Garen to a huge crack in the ground. It was pitch black inside and was filled with teeth-like spikes as they crossed over one another. From afar, it looked like the ground had opened up its big jagged mouth.

Garen took a few turns as he went into the crevice and disappeared.

“Fuck! Chase after him!”

Linda was the first to react as she was also the only one who possessed resonance among the others. Although she wasn’t operating her own Exclusive Mech, she was still very fast in responding to situations.

The rest tried to catch up but they started to lose track of Garen’s Willpower. It seemed that the crevice possessed a strong radioactive disruption field.

Radiation came in many forms in the radiation belt. According to the existing records, scientists have identified at least six hundred types of radiation and there were at least a thousands of them that could be detected but were unknown to them. As for those that were unable to be detected but had palpable effects, there were so many that the scientists had lost count. This was the reason why humans were very afraid of the radiation belt.

They went inside without hesitation as they flew through the gaps in pitch black condition at high speed.

Within these crevices, a few radioactive people in mini Mechs could be seen by the walls as they seemed to be harvesting something from the wall.

“Who’s there!!?” a few eagle shaped Mechs started levitating beside these group of radioactive people as it rumbled.

“This is the Nottingham Household’s Mineral Zone. Outsiders shall leave immediately!!” one of the Eagle Mechs shouted.

The other two Eagle Mechs started to levitate and attempted to block the four Blackboard Mechs. They were a Level Three and Level Two respectively. It seemed that the Nottingham Household was not an ordinary household as they were able to deploy Pilots of such levels even in these places.

If it were a typical Mineral Zone, an employer would typically deploy a Level One Pilot to monitor these radioactive people in Mini Mechs instead of deploying a Level Two or Three.

“Die!”

One of the Blackboard assassins increased his speed and clashed against two of the Eagles.

Pew pew! Boom!!

Two of the Eagles turned into fireballs instantly as they shattered into pieces. These pieces then crashed into the stone walls, causing deaths and serious injuries among the radioactive people.

The fiery fireball had lit up the whole crevice.

Linda and the rest didn’t stop as they continued chasing after Garen who was just in front of them.

“Hold on just a bit more! He should be running out of energy soon! He can last ten minutes at most!” Linda shouted.

The group of four could see Garen flying gracefully between the crevices far away. When they were about to catch up to him, he immediately took a few turns and wriggled out of their grasps.

Soon they encountered another group of Eagle Mechs. However, they seemed to have received advance intel and started attacking them without any hesitation.

Two Level Fives led the team of at least ten Level Two Mechs as they approached them. They possessed tremendous power and these two Level Five Pilots seemed to be the top dogs in this Mineral Mine.

One could obviously see that this mineral mine was unusually important as a deploying a Level Five in this zone wasn’t something a typical household could do. No one had heard of the Nottingham Household before and these four assassins didn’t care in the least. If they could deal with a Level Five elite from the Inner Courtyard, a Level Five from the Outer Courtyard meant nothing to them.

Within seconds, these four had taken care of the group of Mechs without much difficulty.

The four assassins moved forwards as explosions reverberated behind them.

They were at a loss as they couldn’t understand why these people were attacking them instead of Garen.

The whole area had become quiet after two of the Level Five Pilots had been taken care of and no more Pilots dared to attack them. Afterall, a Level Five Pilot was a household’s strongest soldier and if they were disposed of this easily… This would be considered a huge loss for any Household.

However, these four assassins didn’t expect something right after they had flown away from the scene.

The old Level Five Pilot was still alive as he struggled with all his might to send a distress signal while retching up blood in the Cockpit.

“Emergency! Emergency… Unknown Blackboard Mech intruders have appeared. Their strength… is above Level Five… Requesting Annihilation…” the old Pilot shut his eyes after muttering his last word as his Mech which had its cockpit pierced through fell into the endless abyss.

Garen and the assassins whom he had lured over did not realize that a storm was slowly brewing because of their chase.

Far away in one of the bases of White Light.

As countless Mechs kept taking off and landing at the base, a pure white Great Light Mech slowly opened its eyes.

A transparent monitor appeared in front of him, showing clearly the torment that had been done by the four Blackboard Mechs towards the Nottingham Household’s Pilots.

“My Mastery Energy Mine!! Someone dared to lay their hands on my Mineral Mine!! Looks like I have yet to kill enough people…”

A horrifying white aura slowly appeared around her body as it formed into a poisonous snake which resembled a ribbon. The ten-kilometer square base started to tremble from her Willpower alone.

“What are you doing, Nottingham! Our Lord has sent you here to defend the base, not to kill people!” a melodious female tone came from his side. It was from a red slender looking Female Mech which was holding a blade and shield.

“What am I planning to do? Hahaha… Unlike that useless Danfur, I am not a coward who ran away after being beaten by Red-Whale!” Nottingham moved as her Body turned into a streak of white light before flying far away out of the base.

“Everything finally calmed down and some idiot decides to agitate this madman! Damn it! This is going to be troublesome!” The Red Mech was very annoyed as she immediately turned around and flew towards the communication tower.

Chapter 897: Accident 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen stuck his Body close to the black stone wall, as he tried to camouflage himself with his surroundings.

The Willpower around his body changed his appearance into a complex pattern slowly like a chameleon. This helical pattern covered his entire body as he managed to use his colorless Willpower to merge himself with the stone wall before him.

This was the Crouched Eagle Talon’s Exclusive Color Changing Cloaking Technique. This was different from the Crouched Eagle Talon of the Outer Courtyard as Professor Van Doe had modified this training Method to the point it had two new stronger abilities, which were Black Wind and Color Changing Cloaking Technique.

This was the main difference between the simplified version of the Crouched Eagle Talon which was spread in the Outer Courtyard and Van Doe’s Crouched Eagle Talon.

Vroom vroom!!

Four Black Mechs flew past Garen, not realizing that their target was hiding in the corner.

He could still hear Linda and the others scolding one another repeatedly.

Garen sat quietly inside the Cockpit as insects resembling fireflies drifted around him while glowing green.

After he felt that the assassins had flown very far in, Garen gently reached out his hand and grabbed the dot of light. The small green insect crawled about in his hand. It looked like a beetle as its wings were glowing green.

“Got rid of them easily,” he laughed softly as he ignited his engine and maneuvered his camouflage Mech out of the crevice. He knew that once the assassins felt something was amiss, they would immediately turn around to look for him.

However, he would have left the area safely before that happened.

As he flew out of the crevice slowly, he noticed that the surroundings were very quiet as either all the Pilots from the Nottingham Household had evacuated the area or all of them had perished. Garen felt apologetic towards these innocent people as if it weren’t for him luring his enemies here, these people wouldn’t have died.

He had relied on his aura and cloaked himself to evade any detection from these people so they were welcomed with the four assassins instead of him.

“I will remember your sacrifices,” Garen turned around and looked at the base of the cliff which was on the verge of collapse as he flew directly towards the nearest supply point.

*************

“Something’s not right! Why can’t we detect any signal at the front!?” Linda immediately stopped the chase.

Rainstorm, who was beside her, had started to suspect that something was amiss as well.

“Perhaps that bastard has some sort of Exclusive cloaking ability?”

If I have a cloaking ability, what would I do if I were being chased?” Linda rubbed her forehead as she pondered. She had been in the assassination business for a few decades and this was the first time she had met such a troublesome newbie.

“If I were him, I would make use of this cloaking ability and head towards a troublesome place in order to let the others slow us down. At the same time, I would find an opportunity to conceal myself!” one of the assassins spoke.

“Damn it! That bastard must have run outside! Chase after him!” Linda clenched her fist.

“He’s definitely going towards the nearest supply point to get some energy batteries! We…” before the assassin had managed to finish his sentence, he looked up as if he’d seen something unimaginable.

Linda and the others looked over curiously to realize that the light around the assassin’s body surface was rather strange as it was brighter than usual.

Vroom…

A deep horse stampeding noise could be faintly heard from the sky as a streak of red and yellow light flew towards them from afar.

The meteor broke the sound barrier as it drew a long, smoky yellow tail. The blinding light shone onto four of the Mechs as their Mechs reflected a faint metallic luster.

“What is that!?” Rainstorm felt something bad was about to happen.

“I don’t know…”

“What is that?! That’s an Inheriting Pilot!! Run for your lives!” Linda lost her cool as she turned around and escaped without any hesitation.

The remaining three Mechs paused for a moment before following in her footsteps. They had completely disregarded their energy consumption as they tried to escape with the maximum output.

Four streams of blue fire behind their back resembled wings.

“Great Light Chain!!” a faint tyrannical voice could be heard from the sky.

Suddenly, a few thin pure-white chains were shot out from the red yellow meteor as it zoomed towards the four assassins at a speed similar to that of a Laser Cannon projectile. The chains caught up to them easily before they tied their targets up in a matter of seconds.

These chains became tighter for three of them as it reacted to their Willpower’s Energy Field. It appeared to be becoming tighter the more they struggled.

“What is this!?”

Linda was stunned as she immediately took out a green viscous substance and gripped it tightly in her hand.

It popped and the liquid exploded, turning into a cloud of green mist. Within the mist, a face appeared as it slowly opened its eyes.

At the same time, her Mech was covered with a layer of green mist. At the center of her Mech, a face which spanned ten meters in diameter opened its eyes slowly as it glared at the Great Light Mech behind her.

Two streams of green lights were shot out as they hit the Great Light Mech at a speed faster than that of a laser.

“The Light of Numbness? It’s the disciple of Bear Angus!! Hahahaha! It’s worth coming here after all!!” ear-piercing laughter came within the Great Light Mech. “I’ll go and sort this out with Bear after I’ve captured you. I’d been considering avenging my brothers’ injuries from last time!”

The green light was able to halt her for a split second before the Great Light Mech dove downwards and pulled the chain along with the four Mechs towards her.

The four of them did everything they could to escape from the chain but to no avail. It was as if the chain was an illusion and yet it was able to tie securely onto their Body’s back.

Their faces turned pale within their cockpits as they were reeled in.

“This is the end…” Linda shivered.

Boom!!

Her final view was of countless white Flood of Light covering the sky as they went after her.

**************

Far away on a black field.

Garen looked up at the red yellow meteor which sped through the sky towards the black crevice.

He felt a faint wave of vibration as if it was an oppression which came from the root of Willpower.

“A powerhouse has arrived…” his heart sank. He was confident in escaping from these four, but this person was way out of his league. It was definitely a powerhouse with its own Exclusive Mech. Once a powerhouse had its own Exclusive Mech, excluding the troublesome power of Resonance, even the basic abilities of an Exclusive Mech which far surpassed that of the standard model’s were troublesome enough to deal with.

His cloaking technique that had been used to evade detection from his enemies earlier might not work on this person. Who knew what sort of advance detecting instruments were installed on that Exclusive Mech?

“I wonder what happened to Linda and her team. Judging from the looks of it, this person should be the powerhouse of the Nottingham Household…” Garen laughed at their misfortune as he went towards the nearest supply point merrily.

As he flew forward for about ten minutes, The resonance behind him could no longer be felt. He flew around the deserted radioactive field and occasionally spotted yellow puddles. Yellow acidic mist kept vaporizing from the water and the white bones of worms and corpses could be seen by the edge of the puddles.

Dirty, giant grey mice that were at least a meter long could be seen climbing up from the edges of the puddles.

He looked left and right and all he could see was the desert which spanned towards the horizon and his Mech was left with 2% of energy left.

He had no choice but to stop after a few minutes.

Garen had already prepared to move forward on his own in the hazmat suit.

He didn’t bring much drink and food with him as his main parcel was in the care of Anda’s team.

He flew until the smallest bit of energy was left in his Mech.

Garen looked around and couldn’t see anything. He then looked at the map and the nearest supply point was a small radioactive people’s village, which was a ten minutes flight away. It was not enough for him to reach his destination with the energy left.

As an individual weapon, the Mech was considered very powerful. However, its long-distance navigation was far inferior to the Battleship, which was the reason why Battleships were used to transport Mechs to their desired locations. No matter how powerful a Mech’s energy furnace was, it wasn’t as long-lasting as those of Battleships. Afterall, the battleship was designed with transportation and navigation in mind. In this era, the main battle forces were the miniaturized battle jets and Mechs.

Perhaps there existed a Mech that had a long-lasting energy furnace, but it would require a Pilot of a higher level in order to operate it. If a powerful Mech were to be operated by an unqualified Pilot, it would be too much for the Pilot to handle during the activation phase. The end result would either be the Pilot being unable to move it or suffering severe injuries from attempting to forcefully move it.

Kachak!

Garen opened the cockpit and walked out with his black hazmat suit on. He jumped lightly and landed firmly on the field. He even had a small staff in his hand, which was the Staff of Absolute Yin that he always carried along with him.

As the cockpit behind him slowly shut, the Mech’s eye dimmed as the energy source was completely depleted.

Garen looked around and did not see any sign of human activity.

The largest zone was the radioactive belt after leaving the city regions. This planet’s surface area was much larger as compared to of Earth.

“I need to find a fuel source for the Mech as soon as possible.”

After recalling the closest supply point, Garen immediately sprinted towards the location.

After a few steps of running, a few yellow earthworms sprung up from the ground and lunged towards his mask. These earthworms had only one bloody eye and mouth, similar to that of a spider. It kept opening and closing its mouth, giving off a repulsive vibe.

Garen gently flicked these earthworms away but his powerful fingers didn’t seem to do any harm towards them. These earthworms then sprung up again after falling onto the ground.

Hmpf!

Garen scoffed as a big blue jagged mouth opened up from his left palm. Countless blue tentacles sprouted out from it and pulled the earthworms into its mouth, ingested them and swallowed them.

The potential of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique had started to surface as his ability Devour finally showed signs of prowess after the slow evolution.

The strange radiation from the earthworms entered into his body while they were being devoured through his palms. However, under the control of Garen’s Willpower, it stopped spreading as it reached his left shoulder. It then formed into small seeds, which were prototypes of the Distorted Seed.

The huge mouth that appeared on his palm had torn his hazmat suit apart as well. Hence, Garen decided to rip the hazmat suit away from his left palm. As he was about to feel the difference between the radiations, his expression immediately changed and he sprinted far away from where he was standing.

After he left, the pure white Mech slowly appeared behind the Black Mech. The green diamond shaped crystal on its body was structured in such a manner that it formed a huge green light network. This network was clearly in the shape of the word ‘light’ in the universal language.

It was the Great Light Mech from White Light.

“Aren’t you fast at running away!” Nottingham scanned her surroundings.

“You managed to lure people in and kill two of my Level Five underlings! If I were to let you escape this easily, doesn’t that imply that I, Nottingham, am practically useless?” She scoffed. She raised her left shoulder and a small compartment opened up under her arm, revealing a bottle of bubbling dark green liquid.

She used her other hand to pull out the test tube and threw it in front of her.

The test tube broke and the green liquid exploded into a cloud of green mist, spreading into the surroundings slowly.

Soon, clear footprints appeared on the field. These footprints were illuminated green and they stretched forward in the direction Garen was running towards.

“This way.”

Nottingham smirked as she followed the green footprints.

Chapter 898: Accident 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen ran forward hurriedly. His enhanced physical qualities allowed him to move at a great speed for an hour and a half without any difficulty.

He could vaguely see the edges of a dilapidated village in front of him.

Suddenly, he stopped, thinking and muttering to himself for a moment, before his Willpower shifted again and concealed his entire body completely before he fumbled towards the fence at the side of the village.

This village resembled a ferocious-looking fortress that was covered in sharp spikes. It was completely grey and there were puncture marks and holes that were left behind by cannons everywhere. He could vaguely hear the sound of human cries echoing from the inside. Meanwhile, a few stray dogs with festering bodies that were leaking pus from the sides roamed around the empty areas outside. The ground was barren and filled with potholes formed by cannon balls and explosions.

This was the true portrayal of most of the villages in the radiation belt. As the people here had neither strong nor sturdy protective measures, it was completely impossible for them to confront the powerful mutated creatures. Furthermore, it was even harder for them to withstand the various types of strong and abnormal radiation.

Garen circled the fortress once while evading a few peep holes.

The sky darkened gradually while a large cluster of grey clouds floated across the sky. They gathered closer before becoming denser above his head. He could hear the sound of thunder vaguely and realized that it might rain soon.

Garen carefully altered the footprints that he had left behind when he arrived and rearranged them as if he were walking in the direction of the fortress. Next, he looked for a smelly yellow pond and immersed himself inside it gently.

Just as he entered the water, a large swarm of underwater blood-sucking insects that resembled flies made buzzing noises beside him and flew over. However, they collapsed when they were killed by the tremors that were formed when Garen used his Secret Techniques.

He could not smell the disgusting stench from the water due to the filtration system in his hazmat suit. The Cold Radiation that was released from his palms blocked off the parts of the water that it touched and froze the liquid into ice immediately.

Garen entered the pond gingerly.

He felt the sticky liquid submerge his legs, lower abdomen, and finally his chest. It felt as if he was soaking in a pool of glue.

Finally, his neck was the only part left. Garen relaxed his breathing and hugged the Staff of Absolute Yin tightly while sinking downwards slowly.

Shh…

“Warning! Warning! Warning! A large amount of toxic radioactive liquid has entered the face’s gas filtration system! Please change your hazmat suit quickly within one minute! Please change your hazmat suit quickly within one…” the sound stopped abruptly. The hazmat suit’s simple intelligence system had been completely eroded and destroyed.

A pungent stench corroded through the hazmat suit suddenly before completely enveloping Garen’s entire body within it.

A huge colony of radioactive mutated parasites was present in this liquid. These tiny creatures that resembled maggots writhed around constantly while attempting to burrow their way into Garen’s pores.

However, they were destroyed and killed by the tremors that he produced constantly.

Garen maintained this vibrating state slowly while concealing his qi.

Earlier, his exceptionally sensitive five senses had been detecting serious threats all this while. He understood from the first moment that his strong opponent had definitely caught up to him. Therefore, he chose to escape quickly and immediately.

However, the extremely thick radiation and venomous insects in the smelly pond where he was currently inside had cut him off from his sense of crisis completely. At the same time, it obscured his qi fully as well when he fused with the whole pond.

Rare feelings of excitement filled Garen’s mind. A long, long time had passed since he had encountered and felt nervousness like this. He had not experienced the feeling of being suddenly and almost fatally pursued by an enemy or the adrenaline that came from the likelihood of a sudden death for an extremely long time. Stimuli like this allowed him to truly feel like he was living in this world on this planet.

Despite hiding inside the pond now, he could still faintly feel thin shrouds of qi that guaranteed that a crisis was about to happen. Although it was much weaker now, it was definitely still present.

“I’ll take a gamble. Since I can’t detect my opponent’s qi, it’s very likely that he can’t sense my current location either!” Garen’s mind became quiet while he tried to subdue his qi as best as he could.

After a few continuous quakes, he soon realized that it was more convenient for him to use the Cold Radiation to speedily chase the harmful radioactive mutated insects away. Instead of suppressing a part of his Cold Radiation, he might as well allow it to disperse freely while lowering the rate of his heart beats simultaneously.

As expected, these initiatives were extremely effective and it was clear that his opponent was securing his tracks according to his life qi.

“If he still manages to discover me despite everything or chooses not to appear at all, the only thing I can do is lose a Soul Seed and reincarnate once again…!” Garen made up his mind and fell into a deep sleep as his heart rate slowed itself down gradually. This was the most effective way of preventing himself from being detected by the other party.

His heart fell into a state of complete stillness quickly. Layers of ice and frost covered Garen’s body from head to toe fully. He was frozen into a large block of ice that sank into the depths of the pond. As his heart stopped beating, Garen’s consciousness became completely still as well and he became fully comatose.

**************

In front of the fortress beyond the pond, a spotless White Mech soon emerged slowly. It looked as if it had blinked out of thin air and was now standing upright at the head of the fort.

Within Nottingham’s gaze, a light green silk thread that only she could see was constantly directing her towards the tracks of the escapees in front.

“Huh?” the light green silk thread in front of her eyes trembled suddenly. It had been pointing towards the back of the fortress when it broke abruptly and became blurry before it was no longer able to detect directions anymore.

“You can’t even find lifelines? Something’s up.” an expression that indicated that she had discovered her opponent appeared on Nottingham’s face instantly.

Her gaze fell on the fortress in front of her while she waved her hand casually.

A white chain of light flew outwards suddenly and pierced through the numerous layers of defensive boards around the fortress continuously while making crackling noises. The sound of numerous human cries and moans of pain echoed from the inside. She could faintly hear a bout of flurried noises.

Boom!

The fortress’ heavy black metal main door was yanked and sent flying at once.

Motley groups of soldiers with looks of despair on their faces were revealed inside. These people held firearms and simple cannons. All of them aimed their weapons at Nottingham but none of them dared to shoot.

“Respected Mech Pilot, sir! We never…” an elderly man with white hair came forward and spoke loudly but was sent flying by one of Nottingham’s slanted chains before he could finish speaking. He fell on the faraway plains with a ‘bang’ while the flesh on his body became a bloody mess. It looked as if he was no longer alive.

“Of course I’m aware that you’ve already paid sufficient protection fees, but what does that matter?” sneered Nottingham. It was obvious that this was not her first time doing this as she was extremely familiar with this set of excuses.

Terrified looks appeared on the crowds of men and women of various ages inside the fortress. A few soldiers who were clad in Miniature Mechs carried ray guns and old-fashioned cartridge firearms but could only stand on the spot helplessly as they were too afraid to even raise the barrels of their guns. Women who were carrying their children could only cover the mouths of their young tightly to prevent their cries from escaping.

Some people were praying to God or a certain Forbidden Mech Pilot.

Boom…

The sound of thunder became clearer while dark clouds filled the sky as if a storm was about to begin at any time.

While looking at the group of people that resembled lambs that did not even dare to breathe in front of her, Nottingham was filled with a sense of boredom suddenly.

“How boring… Hey kid, if you still refuse to come out, how about I kill every single person in front of me here?”

After waiting for awhile, there were still no movements at all.

“You’re doing this on purpose… To think you were able to hide from my Lifeline Tracking!” Nottingham looked at her surroundings while cruel thoughts stirred in her mind.

“If it’s going to be like this, I’ll just destroy this whole area completely!! Let’s see how you’ll hide then!”

She sneered while her Body soared into the sky suddenly. Numerous pure white chains flew out of her hands continuously and dispersed throughout all four corners of the area while constantly charging towards the ground below despite the terrain.

“Resonance Skill! Hurricane Chains!!!” Nottingham stretched both of her arms out widely while countless white chains flew out of her hands suddenly at once. They formed numerous white silk threads when they dispersed and flew downwards.

While glancing over at these countless dazzling chains, one could see that there were actually more than thousands upon thousands of them!! Compared to Anda’s family’s Endless, it was clear that she had exceeded their numbers greatly. Endless could only make it seem like there was an abundance of a certain thing for a short time. In reality, Endless could only create a few hundred more of that item while the Hurricane Chains were able to create more than ten thousand of them at once. Moreover, every single one of these chains could overshadow the fully released Willpower of an average Level Three or Four Mech Pilot.

While floating in the air, Nottingham removed an outer shell-like layer that covered the interior of her Cockpit slowly before exposing the inside of the Cockpit that was protected by transparent crystal glass.

A cold-looking woman with white hair that resembled a lion’s mane sat upright in the driver’s seat. Both of her hands were pressing the buttons on the control panel while her fierce eyes that resembled that of a goshawk gazed on sharply and threateningly.

She was appreciating the scene that was formed by the large amount of Resonance Skills that she had released. There was a terrifying hurricane comprised of 9999 chains of light which could destroy an entire area of a range of a few hundred meters within moments.

Within the light chains, the fortress was constantly being pierced through and exploded before it collapsed. Some of the people inside were stabbed while others were killed by the explosions. Most of them were trampled to death by the panicked crowds. Fresh blood and the remains of the building flew everywhere while the fields outside became bumpy like the crater-filled surface of the moon instantly.

Suddenly, her gaze was drawn towards a strange pond immediately.

There were two light chains that clearly exploded within the vicinity of the pond earlier but it had not destroyed the pond at all. It seemed as though extremely cold air was being released at the bottom of the pond continuously while she could vaguely see something that was resisting the repercussions of the light chain explosions there.

“Hiding here?!” the corners of Nottingham’s mouth curled up into a savage arc.

She held both of her hands together before a pure white Light Sphere appeared there.

She threw it downwards violently.

Boom!!!

The intense white light exploded suddenly while countless rays of light dispersed and scattered everywhere. The polluted pond water evaporated instantly during the explosions before a pale blue block of ice within the large amounts of gas exploded into smithereens. There was nothing else besides that.

“Huh?”

Nottingham furrowed his eyebrows.

Inside the pond, Garen’s body had become extremely muscular. Actually, he had sunk further into the sludge at the bottom of the pond after the tremors from the last two light chain explosions before he was buried deep inside.

Due to this, the following Light Sphere that exploded against his back violently now formed a large bloody wound there.

He furrowed his brows slightly. He had regained consciousness for a moment because of the intense pain but continued to suppress himself determinedly.

He knew that fighting an Inherited Level master with his current powers would undoubtedly be like countering a rock with an egg as the difference between their strength levels were too great! He could only have a chance of defeating his opponent if he either possessed his own personal Mech, grasped the Resonance Skills, achieved higher levels of his Living Secret Technique or upgraded his physical Attributes to thirty points on average.

In this universe and age, Inherited Level Mech Pilots were top class professionals that could dominate their opponents. They would always be a highly ranked army general within the main forces.

Nottingham’s eyebrows were knitted together tightly while a pure white Light Sphere appeared in her hands again. He wanted to continue probing this strange pond for awhile.

“Nottingham! Would the genius that was known as the fifth-ranked member of White Light show such shameful behavior?” a faraway voice echoed over suddenly.

Within the blurriness, a gust of pitch black wind blew over from a distance like a gigantic sandy tornado. The black wind pulled everything from the ground and everything that it sucked inside seemed to disappear without a trace as if it was a deep bottomless pit. It swallowed everything around it continuously and formed an ebony tornado that grew more and more violent.

“Black wind? Is it someone from the Black Flood Party?” Bloodthirsty intentions appeared on Nottingham’s face immediately. “What good timing… I heard that the Black Winds of the Black Flood Party possess terrifying powers. What a rare chance for me to encounter it today…”

She glanced at the blue ice block in the pond below her and sneered coldly while furiously flinging another Light Sphere that was even bigger than the previous one.

Boom!!!

While the sound of the Light Sphere’s explosion rang out, another loud noise could be simultaneously heard from the Mech that he was piloting when it collided frontally with a gigantic black tornado.

Within the sludge at the bottom of the pond, the Light Sphere exploded suddenly and caused a large amount of mud to gasify. The icy blue ice block was blown to pieces instantly, vaguely exposing Garen’s body below.

This surprise attack that was amplified by Nottingham’s Inherited Level strength had cracked the ice block above Garen’s body instantly and pushed him further into the ground violently after the explosion.

Garen opened his eyes gradually and exhaled resolutely while detecting the two Inherited Level Mech Pilots that were flying far away from the fight while white light and black winds intertwined in the sky and whizzed constantly.

He withdrew his Willpower and crawled out of the deep pit with much difficulty. Although his body was badly damaged from the explosion, his restoration abilities from his Potential Points and his automatic healing from the Peacock’s body were currently repairing his bodily wounds at a speed that could be seen by the naked eye.

As long as he was not completely killed in one hit, he would always have the ability to heal himself and his serious injuries.

Garen patted his body and removed the Staff of Absolute Yin that he was holding against his chest tightly. Suddenly, the expression on his face darkened when he looked at the Staff of Absolute Yin in front of his own eyes.

More than half of the gemstone at the very top of the staff had been destroyed!

He used his hands to rub the remaining gemstones quickly and did not move at all after that.

Garen’s emotions sank to an all-time low instantly!

Chapter 899: Worsen 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Staff of Absolute Yin was the only thing that could provide him with Potential Points. However, it had been completely blown to pieces during this accident.

Garen stared at the staff in his hands and put it down quietly after a few moments.

He had never been one to overly rely on Potential Points and a long time had passed since he had been the Garen of the Secret Technique World that had to depend on Potential Points to improve by leaps and bounds. Without the Staff of Absolute Yin, his suddenly improved speed would now slow down slightly. Meanwhile, the hundred-odd Potential Points that he had accumulated previously would only be sufficient for a period of time.

While standing up from the deep pit, the wound on Garen’s back healed itself quickly.

He looked at the black cloud and white light that were constantly blending and intertwining with each other in the faraway sky. They were actually two main Inherited Level Mech Pilots who were currently engaging in battle.

“What a scoundrel…”

Suddenly, a male voice could be heard from the side vaguely.

Garen raised his eyes and looked over. He could already detect this person’s Willpower much earlier on before they had revealed themselves. It was extremely familiar.

A man in a black hazmat suit was standing beside a deep pit nearby quietly. White smoke was continuously wafting out of the exploded pit under his foot.

There was a filtration helmet over this man’s face that resembled a gas mask that had two pipes at the back, making it impossible to see his face clearly.

“Anda, you’re not dead yet?” Garen smiled while lifting his feet quickly and walking in the direction of the other man. As expected, the master of the Black Flood Party was probably a guardian that his teacher had called to assist him. Otherwise, it would be unlikely for a rescuer to appear so coincidentally in a remote place like this.

Therefore, he would need to leave this place as soon as possible during this gap in time.

Both of them ran in the direction of the ruins quickly. Their movements were completely in sync during this period of time, as if they had planned everything beforehand.

After going through the ruins of the fortress for a while, Garen discovered a perfect energy battery immediately and carried it on his shoulder. Anda found a large box of energy batteries that he was looking for as well.

Unlike Garen who lifted it in one go and carried it on his shoulder, Anda could only pick up a few energy batteries with higher densities from the box quietly.

When he saw Garen pick up a few hundred kilograms worth of energy batteries from the ground in one go easily, Anda’s face contorted for awhile. Finally, he could only helplessly glance at the energy box that he had found before giving up.

“You don’t want it?” Garen asked when he walked over and pointed at the energy box in which only a few energy batteries had been taken.

“…”

“I’ll take it then,” Garen grabbed it with his other hand and simply carried the entire box of energy batteries off the ground in an extremely relaxed manner.

Anda’s eyelids twitched and his mouth gaped open as if he was about to say something. However, he did not speak in the end.

Once both of them had found their required items, they ran quickly in the direction where their Mechs were previously located.

Garen carried two boxes of goods on his own. He did not plan to conceal his physical fitness this time. He was moving faster now than when he had arrived. When he arrived, he was constantly getting rid of the tracks that he left behind. However, he did not have to do that when he was returning.

They returned to the location of their Mechs within a few minutes.

As expected, Anda’s Mech was parked here as well.

“I saw that you had left your Mech here and I came over after hearing the fighting noises over here,” Anda shrugged behind him. He looked on as Garen flung the heavy boxes of energy batteries in both of his hands on the ground.

Bang bang!

Two heavy banging noises could be heard before two deep depressions appeared on the ground when it sank downwards.

“This freak!” Anda’s mind was filled with fear. Regardless of his combat standard, if he were to use this abnormal strength on a person, they would definitely suffer serious injuries if they did not die. He made a mental note to avoid clashing with Garen in the event that he did not have his Mech.

Both of them remained silent and opened the energy boxes in their respective Mechs quickly while dumping the energy batteries inside at once.

Garen dumped more than half of a box’s worth of energy batteries inside and filled the Mech’s energy to the brim at once. He carried the remaining ones into the Cockpit on his own, making it obvious that he had no intention of sharing it with Anda.

Garen had just entered the Cockpit when he immediately heard an unknown message that was left behind.

‘I can only hold him off for twenty minutes. It will be up to you after that, be careful.’

The message did not have a beginning or an end but Garen understood immediately that this was probably a message from the Inherited Level master of the Black Flood Party.

“Twenty minutes…” he took a deep breath. “That’s enough!”

The red warning light went out and was replaced by numerous blue light sources that were fully charged and lit up brightly. They illuminated his face in pale blue and white shades.

After touching the control panel in front of him gently, Garen investigated the state of the Mech’s damage. Many parts of it were damaged but there were no major issues. There would not be any problems as long as the engine was still working.

Willpower was transferred into the Mech’s Body quickly.

‘Launching engines at full power!’

Without taking the energy consumption into account, blue flares that resembled a waterfall flowed down the back of the Mech’s entire Body suddenly.

Boom!!

While the entire Mech trembled for a while, a large and deep pit appeared on the ground when it was hit by the spurting flares. Next, Garen flew forward in one direction.

“Hey, Garen! Wait for me!” Anda flew closely behind.

“Why are you following me?”

“When I invited you to join me in the beginning, I was considering if the guys that you provoked would be able to make good scapegoats. This clearly proves my initial brilliance now!” said Anda in a somewhat pleased tone.

“If it wasn’t for you, I wouldn’t have been able to escape from danger so easily either. I was initially certain that I would die this time! You’re actually a great supporter!”

“So now that we’re even, you don’t have a reason to follow me anymore!” answered Garen simply.

“I realized suddenly that following you has given me the best fortune I’ve ever experienced in my life!” Anda had made up his mind to latch on to influential people. Upon discovering that Garen was actually a supporter of the Black Flood Party, only an idiot would not follow this group closely behind after finding out this secret or give up an opportunity to escape danger like this! His own household was stronger than the Black Flood Party that was basically scum!

The two Mechs staggered but flew quickly, one behind the other. Soon, they had left two light grey marks in the sky.

Garen could not be bothered with that other guy Anda. The troublesome part now was that the guardian of Black Flood Party could only hold his opponent off for twenty minutes. If he was unable to break away from Nottingham’s fatal pursuit within those twenty minutes, he would truly fall into a dangerous situation this time.

The key point now was that he was too afraid to turn back and return to the original path. That route was too exposed and people with the slightest bit of awareness would definitely arrange for their subordinates to conceal themselves along this path.

Therefore, it was particularly important for him to find an escape route.

While sitting in the Cockpit, Garen glanced at the damaged Staff of Absolute Yin while a trace of ruthlessness flashed across his eyes.

“Nottingham… I’ll make you pay for this next time!” he had been badly injured while his precious treasure had been destroyed. He did not even get half of his desired Mech materials during this trip and ended up using an Instantaneous Paper Box instead. After being subjected to such terrible damages, he had simply suffered great losses.

“You’re merely returning after being forced to escape with a body full of injuries. Are you resigned to that?!” the sound of Anda’s intercom echoed behind him.

“Do you have any other ideas?”

Garen knew that this man was well-informed. He often had clever thoughts inside the Region and he was certain that he had a particular plan in mind now.

“Nottingham is the fifth-ranking Mech prodigy in White Light and he’s known as one of the Great Lights. However, prodigies are always incredibly arrogant. Therefore, he has definitely offended many people before…” sneered Anda cunningly. “There are surely a few people who would hope for the opposite of a peaceful life for him…”

“Why don’t you tell me your plan?” Garen had always been too lazy to use this part of his brain. Now that there were people who specialized in this aspect, he could naturally relax.

“Although the White Light Organization is very powerful, it is still an merely an organization at that is filled with internal disagreements and conflict… From what I know, Nottingham’s nemesis Anlusa is another one of the seven Great Lights who cannot get along with Nottingham at all. Both of them have always been at odds so we just need to inform her that Nottingham has been surrounded by powerhouses from the Black Flood Party. If you could contact your Teacher…” a sinister smile appeared on Anda’s face again.

“Do you think it’s so simple? Even if she was surrounded, she would still release a call for help before she died, right?” asked Garen while furrowing his eyebrows.

“Of course it won’t be simple. However, conditions are merely things that are created by people… While there are places where one can transmit messages easily, there are definitely other places where communication is impossible…” said Anda mysteriously.

“You’re saying lie low beforehand to allow White Light’s Anlusa to obstruct the support teams while my Teacher ambushes her while she’s alone?” Garen furrowed his eyebrows. This plan was actually very possible, but he would need to safely transmit his message to White Light’s Anlusa on the other side first. This was difficult because both sides were in warring states. Therefore, their messages would undergo strict encryption. Furthermore, they would change their encryption methods after a certain period of time. If they were able to decipher these messages easily, they could simply become the decoding officers in the intelligence departments of the army by now. Individuals who could easily decipher their enemy’s decrypted messages would be undisputed trump cards and first-rate talents in any force.

The second difficulty was that his Teacher in the Black Flood Party would not listen to plans properly. Moreover, it was usually the teachers who instructed the students, not the other way around. Meanwhile, the great distance created an issue with whether his Teacher would be able to arrive in time.

“You have good ideas but it will be difficult to put them into practice. Do you have any way of getting into White Light’s encrypted information channels?” Garen continued to ask.

“I have a friend who managed to accidentally get into the decrypted channel that White Light is currently using.” he could tell at once that Anda was not being fully honest when he answered. It was obvious that this person was a highly secretive individual.

“We don’t have a great success rate,” Garen pondered carefully for a while and shook his head. “Try thinking about the losses that we incurred during this trip. We didn’t do much but suffered terrible injuries and heavy losses instead.” He had initially planned to come out and personally look for his little brother and the others. His other goal was to train his Mech Controlling Skills for awhile. Looking for materials for his Exclusive Mech was merely an excuse. However, he had not expected that he would encounter these incidents instead.

“Spending some money to reward those who forge alloy as one of the materials of Exclusive Mechs should not be a problem, right? You could just release a few quests asking others to help you. Since you came out all this way on your own, you would surely have another goal,” Anda reasoned. “I have another plan. Since Nottingham has been pursuing you all this while, don’t you want to breathe a long sigh of relief?”

“What’s your plan?” Garen was really curious now. Nottingham was an Inherited Level Mech Pilot who could kill the strongest Level Five Mech Pilot within seconds. This guy merely possessed normal Level Five powers and did not even have Resonance Degrees. Did he really have a way of retaliating against an Inherited Level Mech Pilot?

“Mastery Energy Ores, have you heard of them? Supply ores that need to be melted in the Mechs of Inherited Level individuals. I discovered a canyon when I was coming over here previously that may be the reason why you were being pursued. You lured the Mech Pilot guards that mined for Nottingham and killed all of them. It would be surprising if she wasn’t furious,” said Anda in a relaxed manner. This guy certainly had a nimble mind as he was able to make accurate guesses by connecting a series of inferences and verified information to make the entire truth of the situation come to light.

“Are you talking about… stealing from the mine?”

“Correct! Mastery Energy Ores need to be stored in extremely low and freezing temperatures. These items are continuously needed by Inherited Level Mech Pilots as well because all Mech Pilots constantly need to melt new alloy into their own Mech Bodies. Therefore, these things are always used as universal exchanging currency among Inherited Level Mech Pilots. After all, they don’t lack Universal Units at all as the only thing that they require more of are resources that will help them improve,” explained Anda quickly.

“Lead the way!”

“Follow me!”

Anda did not say anything else before turning around and charging towards a new direction.

A short while later, both of them returned to the front of a deathly quiet large crevice again. The inside of the canyon that was filled with interlocking saw-like growths was completely quiet except for the whistling sound of wind.

Two Mechs passed the teeth-like cracks, one after the other. He did not know what techniques Anda was using to be able to find a grey wall immediately without having to detour at all. This wall did not look any different from the other stone walls around them.

He raised his hand and punched it violently.

Boom!

A large hole appeared on the wall of the mountain while dense white cold air surged out from the inside instantly.

When he looked inside, he could see clusters of identical icy blue ores that were the same size as energy batteries stacked inside neatly like a little hill.

These ores had blue metallic surfaces while slight shape changes had occurred throughout the areas that had somewhat higher temperatures. It looked as if they were in a state where they could melt.

Chapter 900: Worsen 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“So many!!!” even Anda was shocked by the contents of the cave before him. “No one would even sell one of these Mastery Energy Ores on the market for less than ten million Units… I wouldn’t be able to use all of these either…”

There were more than a thousand pieces in front of him here!

Layers upon layers of blue rectangular brick-like objects were stacked on each other. At a glance, he could tell that there were at least ten thousand of them!

“I’m rich!!! I’m rich!!! Hahaha!!” Anda leaped over while laughing maniacally. He jumped into the pile of Mastery Energy Ores and rolled about.

Garen’s heart was currently involuntarily pounding in his chest as well. He had experienced many worlds but had never seen riches worth hundred of billions in front of him at one time. His emotions became slightly stressed as well. These things were items that were needed by Inherited Level Mech Pilots were always in short supply!

“Stop wasting time and take as many as you carry quickly. Go immediately!” although he did not know how Anda had discovered such a hidden mining spot, the most important task right now was to take all of these riches away hurriedly!

“You’re right!” Anda forced himself to suppress his emotions and calm down slightly. Although his sight was still tinted by feelings of unsuppressable frenzy, at least he was much better now than when he was dizzy with success earlier.

A problem had emerged. How would they be able to take all of these Mastery Energy Ores away when they were so many of them?

The Inherited Level Mech Pilots were the only ones who were authorized to use Space Equipment while the others with lower level Willpower did not have the same right and could only carry them with their hands.

If they planned on using both of their Mechs to lift all ten thousand pieces of Mastery Energy Ores, they were merely looking down on these little Mastery Energy Ores as the weight of these items were actually three times heavier than energy batteries!

The weight of more than ten thousand pieces was simply terrifying.

A box of one hundred energy batteries would weigh almost one hundred kilograms while more than ten thousand energy batteries would weigh over ten thousand kilograms!! They would weigh almost ten tonnes, while the Mastery Energy Ores were three times heavier!

The current amount weighed almost one hundred tonnes…

A hundred tonnes!

After converting the weight, Anda was not the only one who seized the items maniacally. Despite possessing physical fitness that greatly surpassed that of regular people, Garen’s eyelids began to twitch wildly. If his body could reach an average of thirty points, he could consider this, but now…

“Take as much as you can!” Garen stepped forward determinedly, jumped down from his Mech at once and began to carry piles of Mastery Energy Ores into his Cockpit. He added more energy batteries into his Mech worriedly and filled up his slightly depleted energy resources once again.

Unfortunately, he could only carry a few hundred pieces before he was exhausted. Without Space Equipment, these things were far too dense to the point where their weight would overload most Mechs. Garen’s Mech was Blackboard’s outstanding military system Mech. It was a Captain Level Mech that given to squad captains like himself as its functions were slightly more powerful than regular Blackboard Mechs. However, once it was filled with three hundred pieces of Mastery Energy Ores, he could only lament helplessly and look on while leaving the rest of this big pile of riches behind.

Meanwhile, Anda was could not bear it at all. After carrying more than ten pieces with much difficulty, he began panting from exhaustion. His Mech frequently reminded him that there were insufficient resources for the journey back. When its weight increased greatly, the Mech would use up even more resources. However, he had not taken enough energy batteries earlier…

Both of them finally suppressed the greedy intentions in their minds and backed out of the cave. After exchanging glances with the other man, Garen grabbed a rock before flinging it inside both furiously and precisely. It struck the automatic cooling unit inside coincidentally.

A clicking noise could be heard as the cooling unit leaked gas slowly. It released a large amount of unknown white gas before the temperature inside the cave rose rapidly.

“What a shame… Truly,” Anda shook his head and sighed. Once the Mastery Energy Ores were removed as individual pieces, if they were not stored at low temperatures, they would become deformed and deteriorate before becoming another useless metal. Moreover, they would also release a lot of heat energy.

“We don’t know how long these Mastery Energy Ores have been stored here because there are so many of them. If we destroyed all of them at once, Nottingham would definitely go insane with anger!” he laughed sadistically.

Garen turned around at once and flew along the path they had come by.

“Let’s go!”

“Hey, wait up! I might not have enough energy batteries and I don’t think I can make the journey back after traveling for some time. I was hoping that you could share some of your energy batteries with me. After all, I found this place so a little request like this wouldn’t be too much, right?” Anda took the opportunity to bring up his requests.

“I’ll give you ten pieces for one Mastery Energy Ore of the same size,” Garen answered casually.

“What the?! You’re robbing me!! One energy battery is sold for only ten Universal Units on the market!!! You’re crazy if you’re trying to take advantage of my bad luck!!” Anda cried angrily.

“The energy batteries now and the energy batteries then are different, no?”

Two Mechs flew further away and disappeared into the sky quickly.

Almost half an hour later, a white Great Light Mech flew towards the entrance of the cave quickly.

Nottingham was slightly bruised while the surface of her Mech was covered with traces of corrosion.

“Damn you, Black Flood Party! Just you wait! Sooner or later…” she said before continuously cursing bitterly.

“I need to move the hidden ores away,” during the period of time when she had discovered the Mastery Energy Ores, she had begun to reduce the production rate of the ores secretly. In order to evade paying heavy taxes to the organization, she had quietly hidden more than half of their production numbers. She did not dare to put these hidden ores in her own base so she formed a cave beside the mine and hid them there instead. She had taken half of these ores previously to refurbish her Mech completely and was confident that she would enter the next level. When she heard that there were issues in the mines this time, she rushed over in a panic because she was worried about the large number of personal ores that she had concealed there!

These ores had been stockpiled there for almost half a year! Most Mastery Energy Ores would be exhausted in half a year. In other words, these hidden ores made up at least half of the mine’s entire worth!

“I’ll return once I’ve taken the ores quickly. I should be able to pound and smelt them to the next stage. Wait for me to enter the Great Light realm, Anlusa! Hehehe…” Nottingham laughed coldly while being filled with bloodthirsty thoughts.

She had entrusted her hopes in these mineral reserves for more than half a year. They were also important safeguards that could guarantee her future promotions. Furthermore, a lot of her blood, sweat, and tears had gone into concealing these great riches.

Suddenly, she could see a large hole in the wall of the mountain from afar. Uneasy feelings rose in her heart faintly.

Her Mech accelerated and flew over quickly before landing in front of the cave.

“This… This is…!!!” she looked at the hole in the damaged mountain wall blankly. It was completely empty on the inside. All of the Mastery Energy Ores had released frighteningly hot temperatures after they had melted, causing the entire cave to glow bright red.

“My ores…” she collapsed with a ‘plop’. She had initially planned to take all of the Mastery Energy Ores back with her when she returned after killing everyone else. Without proper cooling measures, these things would not be able to freeze quickly. Instead, they would release a large amount of hot air rapidly and destroy themselves automatically.

She had initially planned to pick a jumping spot and return right after visiting the mines.

However, now… Now… Everything was gone!

Nottingham’s pupils shrunk immediately as a disheartened look appeared on her face.

“Ahhhhh!!!!!”

She lifted her head upwards suddenly and yelled angrily. She felt as if her heart had been painfully smashed by a hammer.

Blood surged through her veins as she shouted.

“Aurora!!!”

A circle of white light exploded suddenly with her at the center. It seemed as though thunder had exploded throughout the ground. There was a crashing noise as a large crack appeared in her surroundings. A grey pillar pierced through the sky and collapsed abruptly while scattering everywhere. Moments later, it formed a huge sandstorm that covered a distance of a few hundred meters!!

**********************

Inside a tattered, abandoned, and unmanned little house

Clint’s body was covered with painful injuries. Famished and thirsty, he cradled Baylon in his arms while carefully hiding in the shadows by the wall below the window inside the house.

“When will Lonnie wake up, Lord Red Moon?”

“How could you be so stupid! I’m not a human so how would I know when she would awaken?!”

“Then will the people from White Light continue to chase us?” Clint thought carefully for a moment before asking a different question.

“There’s something wrong with your brain! I’m not a White Light member so how would I know if they’re going to chase us?!” said Red Moon impatiently.

“So what should we do now?” asked Clint in a slightly guilty tone.

“Could you be any stupider?! I’m not you, so how would I be able to tell you what to do now?!” Red Moon yelled.

He had tried to contact Nonosiva numerous times continuously. Unfortunately, the disturbances were too great and the connection was always intermittent and ineffective. Every time he tried to speak clearly, the line would disconnect automatically. Until now, he was unable to send a single message clearly.

This filled him with even more fury.

“But… our food… is about to run out soon…” the scoldings had caused Clint to hang his head extremely low.

“You are basically as brainless as a damn pig! Do you know how pigs die? They did from stupidity!!” Red Moon was fuming with anger.

“I wouldn’t be able to magnify my Lord’s exceptional intelligence if it wasn’t for my stupidity,” Clint had decided to abandon his principles after being scolded numerous times.

Red Moon was in a daze.

“Damn! When did this guy learn to speak like this?”

After being interrupted by Clint, the fury in Red Moon’s mind subsided slightly. He truly felt that it was wrong to vent his anger on Clint whenever he encountered trouble. He decided to make it up to him properly.

“It’s not a big issue that you’re lacking food now. You must know that there are still many edible things in the radiation belt. As long as you understand basic biochemistry and botany principles, you can survive in the radiation belt safely. However, I must mention beforehand that this is a matter of luck as well,” his tone had finally lightened up.

While looking at Baylon who was lying in Clint’s lap, he recalled that this girl was too aggressive earlier. However, she had drifted into a deep coma now and her body’s immunity had decreased greatly while being in the radiation belt, which was an abominable environment. This had caused the initial radiation contamination in her body to speed up as well.

Large pieces of rotten grey skin had appeared over Baylon’s face and body now. Most of the skin and flesh on her hands and arms had rotted as well and her bones could almost be seen underneath.

After forcing her to suffer for so many consecutive days, they had thought of every possible method to heal her but could only watch as her condition kept worsening.

“Looks like we can’t save her…” at a glance, Red Moon could already tell that the radiation disease had already entered Baylon’s internal organs by now. After failing to contact Nonosiva many times, he knew that his only hope that Novosiva would send medicine over had been destroyed.

No one understood the radiation disease. When the previous White King had attempted to analyze the essence of the radiation disease, he had ended up failing in the end as well.

Frankly, Red Moon could not bear to watch the kind child-like Baylon gradually inch towards death without being able to do anything.

However, forcing herself to break through previously had caused a great strain on her body. Without enough medication, she would be completely helpless.

“Just give up.”

“What? My Lord, did you say something?” Clint changed his sitting position to make himself more comfortable while cradling Baylon carefully.

“… I said, just give up…”

“What are you saying? Lonnie is still fine. She’s just sleeping because she overexerted herself earlier,” said Clint, smiling.

“You can’t save her anymore…” Red Moon said honestly while his emotions remained downcast. “Without the anti-radiation drugs or the ability to get out of an environment that has been contaminated by radiation, I can’t heal her with my Imprints either…”

“I believe that Lonnie will be fine!” the smile on Clint’s face had disappeared and was replaced by an unfamiliar firmness. “The anti-radiation drugs… will definitely be found…”

Chapter 901: True Nature 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Glug…

A string of bubbles in the green liquid inside the cup rose up slowly before the surface of the water exploded.

Ice Dragon leaned across the tabletop and looked at his own drinking cup. Through the walls of the cup, his eye that was stretched wide open could be seen.

He lifted the cup and gulped the contents down quickly in one go.

Glug glug glug…

A few swallows later, all of the light green liquid had disappeared completely without a single drop left.

“Ice Dragon, the people from Exterminet have failed,” a bald man who wore a face mask murmured in a low voice while standing behind him.

“Failure was something that I had anticipated. Where are we now?” asked Ice Dragon while placing the cup down.

“We’ve almost arrived at the radiation belt. According to the speed of our battleship, we should be able to reach the assassination point by midnight. However, the intelligence officers have analyzed that Nonosiva has probably joined the Black Flood Party. A few Black Flood Party members have left to meet him earlier.”

“I don’t care what party he’s in,” laughed Ice Dragon. “Anyway, I’m just here to let my brother vent. That bastard Fila has always been a hypocrite. It’s obvious that he really wants my help but he just rambles on instead. Does he really think that I’m unaware of his intentions?”

“Should we continue to exert ourselves then?”

“Exert ourselves? When did I ask you to exert yourself? Perhaps you really thought that Fila would count on me to get rid of that Nonosiva?” Ice Dragon did not possess the features of a newly rich individual that was apparent when Fila spoke. Instead, it was replaced by reservation and experience. His frivolous exterior hid his inner composure and shrewdness.

“You must know that there are ranking disputes within the interior of White Light as well… Of course, it would not be a bad thing if we actually encountered that little bastard. I wouldn’t mind taking action and practicing for a bit.”

“What do you mean?”

“Find me a Level Four Mech, I’ll use it to get Nonosiva. It won’t be any fun to kill him with one shot… Perhaps I’ll be able to learn a thing or two from him as well,” Ice Dragon had never been a reckless person but had always been combative instead. However, the basis of his combative nature was to strengthen himself. Compared to everything else, his greatest interest was to improve himself through actual combat. Meanwhile, his favorite hobby was to place himself on the same level as other first rate Elites so that he could learn from their strong points and make up for his own weaknesses.

“But… Fila would not have placed all of his hopes on us only. Therefore, he might have gone to look for his…” said the masked man while furrowing his eyebrows.

“No problem, if that Nonosiva dies so easily, I’ll just take this opportunity to come out and take a vacation to relax,” Ice Dragon smiled.

***************

“What? Someone’s here again?!” Van Doe held a teacup while his hand trembled slightly. “What about my junior, Brian?”

A man in a red robe stood in front of him and answered respectfully.

“Master Brian has suffered light injuries after blocking White Light’s Nottingham and has returned to replenish his energy batteries first. It’s temporarily impossible for him to attack.”

“So many powerhouses are already after Nono even though he only left for a few days? He really knows how to create trouble for me!” Fila was completely speechless and lifted his teacup to drink a few mouthfuls of tea. “Relay a message to the Seventh Divine Wind General for me and get him to assist us for a while. Tell him that this will repay the mercy that I showed him previously.”

“Understood.” a red light flashed around the man in the red robe before he disappeared in front of Fila’s eyes immediately. Apparently, he was just a three-dimensional holographic image.

Once the man had left, Van Doe knitted his brows together faintly.

“However, the trouble he stirs up can be beneficial at times too. The people of White Light have always been cancerous in this region. Perhaps this will be an opportunity for us to drag them out once and for all. Geniuses can only mature when they charge forward… Just like the Divine Wind Generals of the past, which one of them did not emerge from the bloody slaughterhouses?”

Despite speaking like this, his actual actions were not ambiguous at all. He released a chain of messages quickly before the lines of his countless relationship networks were activated.

It had been extremely difficult for him to obtain such a strong and amazing first rate prodigy. If he did not take care of him properly, he would definitely regret it for an entire lifetime!

His numerous planted agents and open-wire lines began to stir.

******************

On the black plains

Two Black Mechs flew in the direction of Blackboard Region while carrying heavy burdens. These Mechs looked heavy but no one knew the exact weight of the load they were carrying. This caused their Bodies to shake slightly as if they could collapse at any time.

Garen and Anda had traveled for three consecutive days already. No one had tried to ambush them along the way but the sole presence of the mutated beasts that they passed by was enough to give them headaches.

In order to maintain a low temperature inside the cabin to store the Mastery Energy Ores, Anda was on the verge of death. Despite being a Level Five powerhouse, he was unable to sustain his own body temperature and was on the brink of collapsing. However, it was still commendable that half of his body’s energy was still remaining. Furthermore, the flying and sanitation functions in his Mech were still working even though the other functions were almost destroyed in the terrible battle earlier.

“After finding so many Mastery Energy Ores, it seems like we’ve reaped a lot of rewards after returning from this trip,” said Anda in an exhausted voice.

“This was all thanks to you. Otherwise, I wouldn’t have been able to find so many ores.” Garen sighed with some emotion. Unlike Anda, his current state was way too relaxed. His own Cold Radiation abilities had frozen the Mastery Energy Ores to prevent them from melting. Moreover, low temperatures did not affect him at all.

“Sigh… How much longer will it take for us to arrive…” Anda sighed.

Garen did not reply as he was pondering the troubles regarding the Staff of Absolute Yin. The Staff of Absolute Yin was not exclusive and there were other people on the Mother Planet that had this item. However, as most of them did not actually use it, it was purely used a symbol of power previously. Therefore, most of them would only think of it as a collectible.

Nonetheless, obtaining another Staff of Absolute Yin would not be something that he could easily do now. Firstly, he would need to find people who actually possessed these Staffs of Absolute Yin.

When he thought of this, Garen felt his head ache slightly. Each person’s collected articles were actually their personal secrets. Therefore, if they did not reveal these things willingly, no one would know what they collected. The Staff of Absolute Yin was once an emblem of the Planet Elder’s power and those who managed to collect it would be extremely wealthy. The price in exchange for it would definitely be great.

His mind became stressed when he thought of this. After Nottingham had destroyed his most precious staff, this excursion would have been a terrible loss if Anda had not found the hiding spot of the Mastery Energy Ores.

He recalled Nottingham’s ultimately oppressive strength. Garen simulated it in his mind and wondered about the reactions that would occur if he used all of his Potential Points on his physical Attributes. In the end, he knew that it was impossible.

His opponent’s Mech already possessed too much power on its own.

Its explosive force was basically equivalent to a heavy-duty battleship that could release full-powered explosions. When the support from the Black Flood Party powerhouse arrived, the movements from the violent fight between them resulted in repercussions with Level Four strength. The terrifying difference in power between Inherited Levels and those below them could be seen clearly.

The differences in power were not merely caused by individual differences in Willpower. Instead, they were mainly affected by the difference between Mech qualities as certain Mechs could amplify their power several times, greatly exceeding the average Mechs.

While his mind remained impatient, Garen tried to use his Potential Points to increase the level of his Willpower.

Unfortunately, there was no way to upgrade it. It was clear now that his nameless Willpower had reached a point of qualitative change and could not simply be upgraded just by accumulating them.

Meanwhile, it seemed as though his Crouched Eagle Talon could still be upgraded. However, Garen understood that the main problem right now was still his Mech as there was a ten times difference between the magnification of an Exclusive Mech and a normal Mech.

This was another main reason why he was unable to withstand the little Light Sphere that Nottingham had suddenly thrown at him previously.

The Light Sphere that Nottingham flung over previously possessed powers that were of the same level as Level Five Mechs that attacked at full force. As for the power of the thousands of Level Three light ray attacks, they were even scarier because one hit was equivalent to an assault from almost ten thousand Level Three to Four Mech Pilots who were controlling their Mechs simultaneously.

He glanced at his Living Secret Technique again. He felt as if this Secret Technique was not particularly useful because his Mech and himself had suffered damages and injuries after their last consecutive encounters. It seemed as though he had no retaliation abilities at all as his Living Secret Technique was not especially useful in the Mech Pilot universe or eras that were heavily influenced by explosive weapons with terrifying powers.

“How am I going to bring the Secret Technique’s advantages into play?” Garen flew while sinking into deep thought. He had thought about this problem previously but had never experienced it so vividly in his life until now.

Living Secret Techniques were truly terrifying when they were trained to the point of the highest realm and could definitely contend with Inherited Level Mech Pilots. However, there was still a long way to go before he could reach the highest realm. It was not just the Holy Spirit Level that he had yet to achieve. Instead, he was not even at the Demon King Level or even the Army Level below it.

Another important factor that led to this dilemma was the need to reconstruct the people of this world. Their physiological structure was completely different, forcing him to investigate the processes and experiences that he needed to practice again.

After thinking carefully, Garen realized that ever since he came to this world, there was not much leeway for him to develop the advantages of his Living Secret Technique.

Other than that time when he killed his Red-White enemy previously, there were no other opportunities for him to use them. Furthermore, he did not dare to release them carelessly either.

‘The advantages of Living Secret Techniques affect one’s physical fitness. Therefore, during individual battles that are fought outside of the Mech, there would probably be two advantages of my Secret Techniques. Firstly, once I obtain my Exclusive Mech after entering the Inherited Level, most Mech Pilots custom-make their own Exclusive Mechs according to the various factors of their qualities. Those with stronger physical bodies will get Mechs that are able to bear heavier loads, allowing them to choose Mechs that belong to stronger levels. My physical fitness would definitely exceed that of most Mech Pilots, as I’ve been coursing through a higher level since the beginning,’ Garen thought.

‘The second advantage refers to the abilities that are derived from my Living Secret Technique. Three examples of these are Devour, Distorted Seed, and Cold Chaos which are actually suitable to be placed in the logistics or support positions. However, there are unsuitable for facing direct attacks. Devour allows my fighting abilities to last longer, Distorted Seed lets me control certain parts and units and turn them into killing machines while Cold Chaos weakens my opponent slightly and creates confusion. These abilities have actually been reminding me that the Hellfrost Peacock Technique is not a Secret Technique that can be used for direct combat at all. On the contrary, it is a strategy-type Secret Technique that is used to manipulate other units and subordinates on the battlefield!’

Garen had only begun to vaguely understand the qualities of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique now. Moreover, once he had broken through the foundation level and entered the real levels, these abilities did not increase his physical fitness like the Divine Statue Technique at all. However, its resistance against radiation was simply insane. The signs from all sides clearly showed that the Hellfrost Peacock Technique was truly a strategic Secret Technique that was suitable as a support base.

He did not make any wrong guesses. Actually, during the warring period against the Warlocks, the Hellfrost Peacock Technique had always appeared as a mincing machine on the battlefield. Whenever it was present, death by cold and chaotic minds would cause a lot of casualties on the opposite side. If there was no way to counter it, a single Hellfrost Peacock would be able to destroy an entire civilization completely!

‘Therefore, if I want to solidify the Hellfrost Peacock Technique’s Soul Seed this time, should I walked on the path of logistics instead?’ realization bubbled up in Garen’s mind. As he was merely using logistic and support-type Secret Techniques to strengthen his External Techniques previously, it would clearly be impossible for him to find the right path.

However, this was also related to specific features of the Living Secret Technique. Living Secret Techniques would not release all of their own information from the beginning but would continuously reveal those Secret Techniques memories slowly as the individual trained and improved. This allowed people to gradually understand the true features of Secret Techniques.

When Garen successfully fused the Hellfrost Peacock Technique and another Evil Technique in the beginning, it was fully considered as a direct combat method. Therefore, he had mistakenly included this specific Secret Technique as a pure direct combat Secret Technique.

Once he had thought about the key factors properly now, his head had cleared up immediately.

Therefore, the most important part of the Hellfrost Peacock Technique is that it can affect control while acting as the support as well!” when he thought of this, Garen’s eyes lit up at once. Suddenly, he thought of another suitable direction that seemed pretty good

— Energy Machinist!!

Coincidentally, he had two sets of Willpower Training Methods that were aligned with Energy Machinists; One of them was Glowing Radiance that had been obtained through an exchange with the Honorable Noble. The other Training Method had been obtained from Professor Van Doe’s information databank.

Strictly speaking, Glowing Radiance was the Training Method of an ancient Modulation Engineer. Modulation Engineers were mainly focused on biochemical technology and less focused on mechanical technology.

Meanwhile, Energy Machinists were the opposite as they focused less on biochemical technology and more on mechanical technology.

Garen turned his thoughts into actions. Using his watch, he opened his databank and flipped through the Energy Machinist Training Methods that he had bought earlier.

‘Energy Machinist Training Method — NIS: An orthodox school founded by the ancient Elsie Republic’s grandmaster, Neer. They have the most standard progression stages of Energy Machinists. Their fusion of machinery and biochemistry has achieved levels that are second to none. They were mainly famous for manufacturing flying insect-types of Energy Machinery.’

‘Training Method Specialities: Each level upgrades the experimental platform to produce energy machinery with 0.5 level of basic defense and 0.5 level of speed.’

Once he had established his direction of development, Garen adjusted his route to perfect strengthening himself once again.

Although the Nameless Training Method was good and at a sufficient level, compared to the perfected Inherited Crouched Eagle Talon, it fell short by a substantial degree. He decided to purify his Willpower and specialize in the Crouched Eagle Talon in the future to support the NIS Energy Machinist. He would also specialize in Mech combat while using energy machines to support it.

There were too many roads to power. However, no one possessed enough energy to strike a balance between all of these roads. Therefore, they could only walk to the highest point by concentrating on one path properly.

“I never expected that I would walk on the wrong path because I had unknowingly been too obsessed with Training Methods of higher levels…” Garen’s head was completely clear now. The thoughts that had unknowingly entered his heart when he had first come to this world were finally being stripped away slowly.

“Although the Crouched Eagle Talon is not strong yet, with the Inheritance from the Black Flood Party, it is still much more powerful than the unknown Nameless Training Method. Apparently, I was forsaking the things that were in front of me for others that were much further away…”

Garen relaxed his mind immediately.

He looked at the Willpower of the Nameless Training Method that was spinning inside his body constantly.

A thought stirred in his mind.

Hum…

A shapeless force dispersed throughout his body suddenly. Next, they continuously turned into light breezes that dissipated slowly.

The composition of the Willpower of the Nameless Training Method was breaking down as Garen was voluntarily giving up this unknown high-level Training Method. The structure of the Willpower that was trained by this method was currently breaking down while the Willpower of the Crouched Eagle Talon was being absorbed slowly.

As the nameless Level Five Willpower disappeared slowly, although a portion of it was reabsorbed again by the Crouched Eagle Talon, almost half of his Willpower dispersed out of his body after turning into just forces, completely breaking down into waste.

Chapter 902: True Nature 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen did not seem regretful at all. He had always been fumbling through his journey while going forward as he needed to experience different paths to condense Soul Seeds. In other words, it was impossible to condense even more Soul Seeds if he walked along one path resolutely. This was another key reason why so many people in the Ancient Endorian civilizations had found it so difficult to break through despite having long lives.

Faint forces were forming around his body now. Two imprint marks appeared clearly on both of his arms again. They were the imprints of the Crouched Eagle Talon’s Willpower. After absorbing a large amount of the high quality Level Five Willpower that had dissipated earlier, the Crouched Eagle Talon had finally underwent qualitative changes. When there were no more Potential Points to force his upgrades, Garen’s entire body trembled suddenly.

The imprints on both of his arms became dim and were replaced by two black Willpower Imprints on his shoulders. These were Imprint lines that would constantly need to be condensed and simulated. Every time these lines were condensed, it would be considered as practice. Garen had sketched them within a short amount of time as he could still easily remember the Imprint of the Level Five Crouched Eagle Talon.

Sketching Imprints was another way to practice one’s Training Methods.

Without his Level Five Nameless Willpower, Garen did not know what to do. Despite being weaker now, he felt more relaxed. Feelings of complete clarity floated through his mind constantly.

Only then did he understand that he had been too greedy and had wanted too many things previously. As for not being pure enough, he knew that desiring for excessive much power instead of developing his own strength was actually barely satisfactory. If he was someone else who did not have strong martial arts experiences to support themselves, he would have died in battle much earlier on.

Once most of the Nameless Willpower had dispersed and he had finally cut off the beneficial relationship between Red Moon and himself completely, the only thing that remained was a faint Imprint.

He was also left with Level One Nameless Willpower. With the bond preserving his Imprint, Garen could faintly feel that the Crouched Eagle Talon’s Willpower would be completely destroyed as well if he got rid of this last bit of Level One Willpower fully. This was another key element that was had been used to threaten him in the pool earlier.

“Just Level One Willpower,” Garen laughed coldly and was unbothered by it. The absence of a method to solve it now would not mean that he could not find a way to fix it in the future. Instead, he focused his attention on entering Level Five again with the Crouched Eagle Talon this time.

There were no particular differences. Other than the muscles in his arms becoming more solid, his explosive force increasing by one level and his Willpower increasing, there were no other changes.

“My future focal points will be the Crouched Eagle Talon and Energy Machinist NIS,” Garen decided on his direction. He felt that he had both gained and lost too much during his previous pursuits. Although his Living Secret Technique upgrades were able to upgrade all of his Willpower as well, another problem that he faced was not wanting to use the hundred over Potential Points that he had accumulated.

Life was about winning and losing. Therefore, he would just go and look for more Potential Points if he ran out! There would be losses and gains in everything anyway. When he thought of how he had continuously stopped himself from advancing merely because he was trying to save up on Potential Points, Garen laughed softly.

He was also slightly apprehensive of the various obstacles that he had unknowingly encountered on the path forward.

He knew that part of it was caused by using too much of his Potential Points to upgrade himself in the past. This had prevented him from going through many mental experiences that now caused problems to surface.

He fixed his issue of going in the wrong direction and also got rid of his Nameless Willpower.

Garen began to concentrate on investigating the Energy Machinist NIS Training Method in his hands now. This was the standard Training Method that was used by five out of ten Energy Machinists. However, its progression rate was extremely slow as most people who were not first rate geniuses at mathematical calculation would assume that everything was nonsense when they first entered.

Most of them would study it intensively for a year but the majority would not be able to understand even one percent of it.

Even though she was Professor Van Doe’s elite disciple, Galafil fell into the above category as well. One could only imagine its true difficulty.

‘Individuals who are not mathematical geniuses should not even think of attempting.’

These were the first words that had been said when he had opened the Training Method.

Garen had instinctively overlooked this. His Intelligence Attribute possessed enhanced calculation abilities and he did not believe that his current 2.1 points of Intelligence could not meet the requirements of this Training Method.

When he ended up glancing at it quickly, the first question made him somewhat dumbstruck.

‘Level One requirements: Solve two equations simultaneously. Extract the root of these equations to the twelfth decimal point. The time limit is ten minutes.’

Simple mental arithmetic was already a terrifying request that most people could not complete. Meanwhile, they were now requiring him to simultaneously solve two… And he was only given ten minutes?!

After coming to this world, this was the first time Garen had felt the terrifying importance that the people of this world placed on brain development.

He furrowed his eyebrows and gritted his teeth.

“Try it then talk!”

After glancing through the test questions, Garen closed his eyes and memorized them. He pressed a button on his watch to start the timer while his brain began to calculate answers quickly at the same time.

He had participated in all of the classes in the Academy but their level of difficulty had never been as troublesome as what he was experiencing now. Although his 2.1 points level of Intelligence and memory were shocking, currently, he clearly understood why less than one in a hundred people were able to progress through these elite conditions. These Training Methods were basically specially designed for bookworms and top students.

It did not require anything else except for mathematical calculation abilities!

While closing his eyes and calculating, the nerves on Garen’s temples almost bulged out as well.

Ding.

Ten minutes were up.

He opened his eyes impatiently and had barely managed to calculate it…

He stated both of his answers and compared them with the answers that were displayed on his watch’s information screen before exhaling a long breath firmly.

“I was barely able to calculate it, how scary… No wonder there are only so few Energy Machinists despite this being an era of terrifying mental developments. No wonder, no wonder…” he finally understood it completely.

He shut his eyes and rested his mind for a moment before opening it again and browsing through the contents at the back.

Sure enough, the strings of calculations at the back were extremely complicated. Most of the time, the conclusions and inferences from the calculations in front were used in the calculations at the back. The conclusions and inferences became longer and more complicated as well.

Unconsciously, the amount of sweat on Garen’s forehead had increased. He needed to constantly memorize the conclusions in front. Otherwise, he would not be able to understand the quick calculations at the back that were linked to one another.

There would even be occasional leaps sometimes. The information would display the conclusions matter-of-factly but Garen would need to spend half a day calculating before he would be able to understand the inferences and conclusions that they used as formulae. Other times, he wondered about the clever methods they used to calculate the final answers, as too much had been left out of the calculation process in the middle…

Less than an hour had passed but Garen’s body was almost entirely soaked in sweat!

“No! I need to think harder!”

Garen closed his eyes quickly and shifted his attention towards his Attribute Pane.

After browsing through so much information, he realized that the Energy Machinist’s power was mainly obtained from Energy Machinery that was cultivated from biochemical pools and experimental platforms. The power of the Energy Machinery was derived from the Training Method amplification. The forging materials belonged to similar levels as piloted Mechs except that they were switched with driverless Mechs.

Garen desired combat method would be able to utilize his Secret Technique abilities fully. It would use his radiation to affect the biochemical pool to forge even more powerful biochemical Energy Machinery. He could condense the Distorted Seeds as Energy Machinists would need to use either intelligent chips, biological brains, or hearts as the core of their Energy Machinery.

After carefully rereading the information, Garen verified the feasibility of his ideas.

The stronger the core of his Energy Machinery was, the greater the changes made towards the mutation of its materials would be. Hence, many Energy Machinists would enter the radiation belts to find radioactive mutated materials that were strong enough. Furthermore, Garen was unfazed by the radiation on his own Distorted Seed anymore.

It was important to note that a good core could not simply be found when needed. However, he could have as many Distorted Seeds as his heart desired! By using his Distorted Seed as a core or a heart, as long as he had sufficient materials, he would be able to use the biochemical pool to quickly forge single-use war weapons by using the mutated creatures that he cultivated.

“It’s very feasible!” Garen made up his mind. As some Energy Machinists would engage in gang fights, it would be an issue if those who served as cannon fodder were unable to upgrade their strength because material cores were too difficult to find. Unlike the rest, as long as he had a sufficient amount of Distorted Seeds, he did not even have to use control chips because of his body. The parasites of the Distorted Seeds would not be able to attack him because he was the main body. Moreover, they could be somewhat controlled by him as well.

The only thing he required was the cultivation means of the Energy Machinists.

“I’ve upgraded my Intelligence slightly because the direction that this Training Method is going towards is exhausting my brain…”

Garen felt a slight headache oncoming. When he glanced at his progress, he already knew that he had only improved by 0.5%. Although it was much better than most people, if he were to use this progression rate to train as an Energy Machinist, he would not even need to dream of entering the first level until a few years later. Level One Energy Machinists could only forge scouting Energy Machinery while Level Twos had slightly more combat abilities and were able to forge small-scale combat Energy Machinery.

He would need to reach Level Four or Five at least if he wanted to form combat abilities. Only then would he be able to forge medium-level Energy Machinery where one individual would be equivalent to a small-scale army.

The Training Methods of Energy Machinists involved more than simply sketching Willpower Imprints. Instead, they would require people to constantly solve calculation cycles. Difficult calculations like these would automatically stir up Willpower to naturally form Willpower Imprints. Strangely enough, the Willpower Imprints of Energy Machinists would not be on their own bodies but would float an inch away from the back of their heads where it was impossible for the naked eye to see.

Garen’s gaze fell on his Attribute Pane. He pushed the large pile of topics behind him and allowed his eyes to scan across the single Attribute Pane immediately.

‘Nonosiva Lin — Strength 3.1, Agility 3.0, Vitality 4.7, Intelligence 2.1, Potential 12530%. Soul Limit 40.’

“I have 125 Potential Points? I’ll increase my Intelligence first!”

This time, Garen could truly feel that the Energy Machinist path would correspond with his own Living Secret Technique very well.

His gaze focused on his Intelligence and there was a brief whooshing noise as his Potential Points began to decrease quickly while his Intelligence started to increase and become clearer from its blurry state.

As long as each Attribute had a value of less than five points, ten Potential Points would be enough to upgrade one Attribute. Almost thirty of his Potential Points had disappeared at once and he was left with 98 Potential Points. Meanwhile, his Intelligence had increased to the 5 points immediately.

Garen paused. There were still many uses for his Potential Points and it was unnecessary for him to use all of them on his Intelligence. Five points of Intelligence was sufficient.

He attempted the cycle calculations from the question bank. It was much easier this time as his arithmetic abilities had been enhanced by twofold. Garen was now able to complete the first level of the question bank easily.

He felt as though these complicated calculations were merely math questions that were slightly harder. They were not at a level that made his head dizzy anymore.

Unknowingly, Garen had finished calculating the entire first level of the question bank.

Hum!!

A tiny music note that was shaped like three chestnuts appeared an inch behind Garen. Apparently, it was so simple to achieve Level One! The moment the music notes condensed, bouts of Willpower surged out of one of them quickly and rushed into Garen’s brain. They formed little silver spouts that resembled cyclones and occupied a small corner in Garen’s mental space where his Soul Seed was located.

“Apparently, it’s this easy!!” Garen widened his eyes in shock. He had never expected that Energy Machinists would be able to achieve the appropriate levels instantly as long as their arithmetic abilities were sufficient! There were simply no major obstacles at all! The thing that shocked him the most was the information and messages that he received after entering Level One. It stated that Level One Energy Machinists had the right to use Space Equipment!!!

His mouth gaped open and he was at a loss for words. Energy Machinists were basically the cream of the crop and perfect beings among the Mech Pilots.

Chapter 903: Return 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Carefully checking the function of Willpower imprint of Energy machinist.

No ability to attack and no ability to recover; sure enough, without the Biochemical Pool and the test bench, the Willpower of Energy machinist was useless.

After trying out a variety of methods without any result, Garen also slowly gave up. He knew that without the Biochemical Pool and test bench, he could just stop thinking about this Willpower.

He proceeded to look at the second part. Unfortunately, the second part was a very complex 3-dimensional spiral formula. It was a 3-dimensional building model that was made up of a large number of formulas from the top to the bottom. The strange part was that the formulas shared similar elements to many other computational formulas, from the calculations to the answers. Each equation formed an extremely complex model structure.

“It’s a fine piece of art,” Garen squinted at it, impressed. Almost not a single digit on the building model could be changed, otherwise, the whole model would collapse immediately.

After looking at this model, the prerequisites for the second part finally came out.

“Construct a 9*9*9 (diminishing from the bottom to the top) pyramid structure based on the classical computational formula rules on the first part.”

“Sure enough…” Garen went speechless. The conclusion from the first part could be used as a formula. There were hundreds of them and they were going to be used to build this kind of mathematical model.

This structure was a bit similar to the traditional Sudoku game except that it was a lot more complicated because the calculations involved were sequential and the numbers that were derived have to be shared. The condition was that it had to be done by mental calculations or else there would be serious consequences.

Garen did a bit of the calculation and was temporarily unable to get a lead on it. He had been the top student from a prestigious university and the top chemist from the Totem World. However, to complete this level of combination models in a short period of time using only mental calculation, this difficulty could not be described using the word ‘difficult’ any longer; it was the difference between heaven and earth.

He did not dare to imagine how other Energy machinists were doing the training. This level of mental calculation was almost inhuman.

After getting no result from the calculations, the two Mechs had almost arrived at the destination that was set previously—Cole Town.

In the radiation belt, those towns with the name Cole, Kirino, Tom and the like were numerous. Though they were called towns, in fact, they were just small villages.

On the black plains, only a single hill could be seen in this area of dozens of kilometers and Cole Town was constructed inside this hill in a semi-enclosed way. A lot of mutated plants were also transplanted around, making the concealment quite thorough.

Garen came all the way just to come to this Cole Town. He even had a small dispute with Anda due to this. After seeing that he could not persuade Garen, he did not leave and followed him around closely.

Garen was too lazy to be bothered with him. He did not forget the purpose of coming out this time.

Swish Swish!!

After the sound barrier was broken twice, two black Mechs arrived on top of the hill.

Garen sent a message through the channel that was given by his teacher, “I am Nonosiva.”

Soon, a small opening appeared automatically on the hill and an unmanned aircraft flew out. It looked like a miniature helicopter with a small black baggage hanging on it.

Garen stretched out his hand and grabbed the baggage.

At this moment, the computer screen in front of him suddenly flashed and blurred with a hissing sound and a middle-aged man with a bald head in the middle appeared.

“Sir Nono, this is the harvest this year, please check. Also, Sir Yefei had arrived at the Flying Batoid City. The Lord had informed that you can go back to the Flying Batoid City directly,” The bald-headed man said.

“Understood, it’s been hard on you,” Garen nodded and said with a smile.

“This is what I should do,” the bald-headed man hurriedly bowed his head to express his subservience.

After the screen went off, Garen had almost finished disinfecting the baggage and used the robotic arm in the compartment to open it. Inside was a freezer that was giving off white smoke. The freezer contained a transparent crystal ball and inside it was filled with mercury-like translucent viscous liquid that was blood-red in color.

“This is Blood Silver?” Garen relaxed. One of the goals of this trip had been achieved and there was just one more; that was searching for his younger brother Baylon, Red Moon and the others. Since he had taken over Nono’s body, making the lives of his friends and relatives better was one of the repayments he had to do.

Besides, without the sacrifices of Baylon and his family, the original body could not have entered the Blackboard Academy so easily and even got a good foundation for progress.

“Where are we going now? We’re not going back yet?” after receiving the Blood Silver, Garen and Anda’s two poor Mechs quickly flew in a random direction for a while until Anda finally opened his mouth.

“We’re going to the Flying Batoid City, but we can’t just go straight there. We need to find a safe route,” Garen answered casually.

“You want to go back to Flying Batoid City!?” Anda said shockingly. “So many people are waiting to ambush you on the way back! Going back to die?”

“So what?” Garen was unmoved. “How about you stop following me?”

Anda sat in the cockpit rolling his eyes.

“No way! This is for your safety, this is the first time for you to come out to the radiation belt, and it will be bad if you get some radiation sickness. So, it’s better for us to move together.”

Garen clicked his tongue knowing that this guy wanted to rely on Black Flood Party to avoid the White Light’s pursuit.

After some energy batteries were consumed on the way, the weight on the Mechs was reduced and the burden from bearing the Mastery Energy Ore was a lot less, making their actions easier. Garen had shamelessly taken over the Mastery Energy Ore that had been stolen previously.

On the way here, he had made clear the value of the Mastery Energy Ore. Although there was a price for it on the market, no one would sell it. There was demand for this thing but there was no supply. Generally, the inheriting pilots did not have enough for themselves to use. Using it for transactions with Inheriting pilots would totally be lucrative.

Garen had calculated that if he turned the amount of Mastery Energy Ore he had gotten into resources, he would have enough to construct his Mech with low-level materials. As long as he had his own Mech, he would have the qualification to move toward the Inheriting Level. Without his own personal Mech, there was no use thinking of resonance degrees. Without resonance degrees, he could not even achieve New-Moon Level, much less Half-Moon Level, Full-Moon Level, Two-Moons Level and Inheriting Level.

There were about hundreds of these Mastery Energy Ores occupying about 90% of the weight of the Mech which greatly reduced the flexibility and speed of the Mech.

Therefore, both of them could only try to change the course of their route so as to shake off their possible pursuers.

“Do you want to know why I’m being hunted by those people?” bored, Anda began to chat with Garen.

“Why?”

“Because… I killed their young chief. Or maybe I should say ‘our’ young chief because I was once a member of that clan,” Anda smiled and said.

“Then?”

“Then? Then I obviously escaped. I entered Blackboard Academy because only the elites of the Blackboard Academy were feared by the clan and they would not dare to commit murder inside the academy,” Anda laughed.

Garen made an ‘en’ sound. He was not interested in continuing to listen anymore. After all, it must be something along the line of facing difficulty in advancing, working hard, coupled with some luck before escaping from the clan’s grasp and now barely had a firm footing.

Anda made a ‘hehe’ laugh and noticed that Garen was not interested, so he changed the subject.

“Hey Garen, you know…our Mechs carried so much load and it’s all so valuable, if we encounter a few elite Mechs attacking us now, then there’s gonna be a lot of fun… hehehe…”

“Hehehe…,” Garen also laughed, his face turned green while looking at the white humanoid Mech with a dragon head on the plains in front of him. “You are one hell of a talent…”

Anda also turned pale. His laughter became smaller and smaller.

With a ‘Pa’ sound, he slapped himself on the mouth.

“This crow mouth!”

“What to do now?”

“Escape!!!”

Garen turned around and escape without another word.

With such a large weight, a slightly complex action might cause the engine to be unable to keep up and crash. However, if they were told to give up the Mastery Energy Ore, forget it, they had put their lives on the line in order to get it, and giving it up so easily was not the style of them both.

Looking at the two Mechs escaping, the dragon-headed humanoid Mech was puzzled and pulled out the white sword that was stabbed into the ground in front of it.

“Didn’t they say that guy was very fierce? Unless he encountered an opponent that he absolutely could not withstand, he would normally fight first, why is it so different from the data?”

In the white cockpit, Ice Dragon touched his chin and wondered.

“Sir, the special detector found a high-energy response from the two Mechs! The other side seemed to have activated the low-temperature refrigeration function!” a subordinate on the stealth battleship that was hidden in the sky above appeared on the Mech’s screen.

“Oh? High-energy response? They’ve got some good stuff? No wonder they ran away when they saw me!” Ice Dragon’s eyes immediately brightened up. “Let’s go! Catch up and see what the stuff is!”

He clapped the dashboard and the dragon-headed humanoid Mech spat out white flames and headed straight for the two Mechs ahead.

On the black plains, there were two black Mechs fleeing in front and behind them was a white Mech catching up to them. The distance between them was rapidly shrinking.

With the peng peng peng sounds of running, the two Mechs in front were unable to continue flying. They were half-flying while borrowing the kicking force from their legs, looking cumbersome and clumsy. It was apparent with one look that the Mechs were too heavy.

“He’s catching up! What do we do now!?” Anda shouted, looking at the dragon-headed humanoid Mech that was getting closer. He could recognize at first glance that the other party was one of White Light. At the second glance, he could see that although the other party’s Body only had the fluctuation intensity of a Level Four, his Willpower’s sense of crisis was constantly warning him to run! Run! Run!!

“You stall him! I’ll get reinforcements!” Garen shouted. His speed suddenly increased a lot. He was actually using the special technique of reducing the air resistance and overtook Anda.

“Stall your sister!” Anda was shedding tears. He could finally see clearly Garen’s shameless nature. “Why don’t you go and stall him instead!?”

“Hehe, I am faster than you, the probability of me escaping is higher,” Garen answered and laughed.

Chapter 904: Return 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“You!!” Anda clenched his teeth and turned around to look at the white dragon-headed Mech. To his astonishment, the Mech had actually caught up to within 20 meters.

Boom!!

Anda started worrying. An amount of Willpower was ejected behind him like a bullet all of a sudden, which actually increased the Mech’s forward speed.

“Trust me! I will be back to save you!” Garen yelled from the front, “I guarantee you on my honor!”

“As if your honor is useful!” Anda shouted. Seeing he had almost been caught up to, he quickly fired off another burst of Willpower. As he accelerated his Mech, the Mech behind him slowed down.

“Why are the both of you running around?” Ice Dragon asked from the back, “I’m not even planning to kill you!”

“Then why are you chasing after us!!!” Anda shrieked.

“It’s your guilty conscience. You were both running, so there must have been something going on. Either you were doing something bad or sneaking around, either way, it’s nothing good!” Ice Dragon contemplated, “After all, I am a person who loves punishing the evil and praising the good!”

“Are you crazy!” Anda roared.

“If you’re cussing, you’re definitely not a good person!” Ice Dragon was getting kooky again, letting out a devilish laugh as his speed hiked up once again.

“I -” Anda urgently released another spurt of Willpower.

Both of them knew that their Mechs were loaded now and if they were to battle, needless to say, their combat power would not even be able to defeat a normal Level Five Pilot, let alone the terrifying creature at the back who was able to send shivers to their Willpower by just the sight of him.

That was also why Garen started running without a word in the first place.

The three of them put up a fair fight – catching up for a moment, then being thrown off the next second, closing in on each other, then getting thrown off again.

In the beginning, Ice Dragon was just fooling around. However, even when he started to get serious, he was still unable to catch up with the two people in the front. Naturally, he was shocked.

Nonosiva at the front was still alright with his Hurrying Technique, all smooth and quick. However, Anda at the back clearly had no techniques but he had plenty of weird tricks up his sleeves such as blasting out stone columns. Although the attacks were simply dismissed, they still successfully slowed down Ice Dragon’s speed.

Occasionally it was the ice on the ground, a slip of attention and one would actually trip, even slightly affecting the ejector engine.

There was also a minor shift in the Magnetic Field. A sudden alteration of the field and the Level Four Mech already almost fell. Although Ice Dragon seemed young, he had actually lived for almost two hundred years already. Even at his Inherited Level, there were some tricks even he was not able to recognize.

Nonetheless, tricks were still tricks after all and they had their limits at the end.

Ice Dragon could finally confirm that Anda had used up all his tricks. After approximately an hour’s chasing around, he was getting bored already. With just a flip, the Mech rolled and shrunk its body. It leaped in front of Anda and landed with a thump, blocking off Anda’s route entirely.

At the same time, with a wave of an arm, a ray of white light shot directly through Garen’s body.

The white light was sharp and soundless, just a vague thin line right at Garen’s spine. Once the spot was hit, his body would be instantly paralyzed and he would be unable to move.

At this moment, Garen yanked out his sword and swung it fiercely.

Clank!

The exact moment the blade met the white light, both bounced off each other immediately.

Garen promptly stabled himself, then noticed a small chip on his blade. The white light darted through the ground, vanishing underground with just a tiny hole left to be seen on the surface.

“Alright, alright. Come and fight me for one round then. If you make me happy, I would consider letting you leave,” Ice Dragon smirked.

“Anda! We’re counting on you!” Garen yelled, decelerating his Mech.

Ice Dragon actually stopped and directed his attention to Anda, as if Anda had finally picked up his interest. He had no plans of killing Nonosiva anyways, neither did he planned to save Fila. As for standing up for his brothers, he could just return and report that he killed two people.

He was now more intrigued by the fact that Anda had tricks even he himself had never seen before.

Anda was close to tears but could not bring himself to shed a tear. Once again, he was awestruck by Garen’s shameless self.

“You bastard!!”

Garen could not believe that this guy would be so easily killed and that he had no intentions of killing. At most, he just deserved a mean beating. As for abandoning his comrades and such treacherous beliefs, he never cared much about such little things. As long as there was an adequate opportunity, he would definitely not be constrained by what the average person scrupled.

He believed that Anda would not take long to recover from a beating to catch up.

Continuing his journey, he soon came across the black plains. The yellow grassland was before him, where tracts of yellow-green meadow were being disturbed by the harsh wind.

This time around, standing at the front of the meadow were two familiar white Level Five Shining Mechs from White Light.

The area was completely empty except for the two Mechs standing quietly on the ground. Both bodies were exuding a faint sense of force intended to kill as if they were surrounded by an army of hostile Mechs.

“Special Willpower Training Method!” Knowing this bunch would not be an easy defeat, Garen’s heart sank slightly.

Even in the Inner Courtyard, people rarely revisited special training methods. These methods were not necessarily able to strengthen your Consciousness but the ability to keep track of all kinds of abilities made one impossible to guard against.

Furthermore, those who dared to practice Special Willpower were confident geniuses.

“After chasing you for so long, we finally caught up,” the Mech on the left whispered in a low tone which resembled a young man’s. “I didn’t expect you to actually be able to avoid our ambush for so long even though you almost escaped our range. Gee, you’re actually not bad…”

An intrepid killing intent erupted from his Willpower, forming a clear round whirlpool that blew the grass and dirt around.

Bang!

His body took the first step as he leaped into the air.

“Go to hell!”

Clang!!

A white moon appears above Garen’s body, glowing as drops of white liquid dripped from it.

Instantly, black dual blades, crossing against each other, appeared in Garen’s hands. A surge of black breeze brewed in the sky as the white liquid trickled on his head.

Ding!!

Garen narrowed his eyes..

********************

“If you can’t do it, why not just give up hope in the beginning?”

At the other end of Radiation Belt, Red Moon was quietly watching Clint who was kneeling beside Baylon. The young teen showed an unfamiliar look of perseverance and determination, making him seem foreign.

“Since it’s already decided, there’s no giving up halfway, end of the discussion,” Clint muttered. “Lord, tell me, how do I do it?”

“You have to think it through, there is very little hope left for Lonnie. Now that we are fully surrounded outside, it won’t take long for the white Mechs to come. When that time comes, you might not even have the chance to run away,” it was just like the first time Red Moon had met Clint in his memory, this normal child was just slightly cowardly but tough at the same time, just like any other average child.

“If Lonnie dies, you can find a brand new compatible imprint. However, if you do decide to save her, she doesn’t stand much chance! In return, her recovery percentage can’t even reach ten percent,” Red Moon spoke solemnly.

Clint did not answer, but raised his head and calmly stared at his virtual image. In this teen’s eyes, it was as if a familiar surge of burning red flames was ignited.

Red Moon’s heart soared.

“Bring her along this escape route, then use the small technique I just taught you and swiftly switch directions. Only Shining Mech Pilots are able to bring along some radiation drugs. Otherwise, it would be the chaotic city shops. Which do you choose?”

“Which way is the fastest route?”

“Find the Shining Mech, but each Mech is a Level Five Mech Pilot. You wouldn’t stand a chance against them even one-on-one.”

“Lord, now that you’ve brought this up, there will certainly be a way to solve this,” Clint said sternly.

“Are you really willing to risk your own life?” Red Moon could not help but ask once more.

Clint was silent, then stressed on each syllable and said.

“I will not give up on my comrades!”

“…”

“The front five transitions must not have the slightest mistakes. I’ve already worked out the best way to avoid, all you need to do is to follow suit, even your actions at the back can’t be greater than 10% deviation. I will mark clearly on the Mech’s computer. If you can’t do it, not only will you die, but she… will die as well.” Red Moon could see the determination in the young teen, and so made his own efforts to squeeze a tiny ray of hope.

“After leaving the encirclement, the opponent’s body has approximately less than three seconds of a reflex gap. If you are unable to transform four times within three seconds, they will begin their long-range attack, and the chances of you being hit is a hundred percent. However, continuously changing your body will be a severe burden on your body. In the end, once you’re almost nearing the Mech, the opponent only requires one Willpower Pierce to finish you off with the short distance between the both of you,” Red Moon stated calmly.

“What about after finding the Shining Mech?”

“By that time, you will have to rely on your luck. I will help you steal the drugs, all I need is fifteen seconds. If you can survive that period of time, then Lonnie has a chance of surviving.”

“Fifteen seconds…” Clint bowed his head, hands pushed deep into his hair, an unspeakable fear was constantly stirring in his mind. He knew the extent of a Shining Mech.

That was the true complete picture of Red-White’s power levels, just one Willpower Pierce and he would be gone. Maybe even just a glace, and he’d be facing death.

“You can’t do it,” Red Moon’s voice softened, “This isn’t even risking your life, you’re practically committing suicide. Give it up, Clint.”

Give up… Give up… Give up…

Give up…

Give up… ?

Questions constantly echoed in Clint’s mind.

He was just a Level One Willpower Pilot, and he was actually planning to pin down a Level Five Pilot within fifteen seconds. Even if he practiced the top training method, it was only equivalent to a normal Level Three Pilot, and he would still stand no chance against a Level Five Mech.

Even with Lord Red Moon’s imparted skills to self-mutilate, Clint understood that his survival rate was very, very low.

He looked down at Baylon’s half corroded face.

He stood back up.

“Let’s go, Lord, it’s time to get prepared.”

Chapter 905: Blocked 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ding…

The dark storm welcomed white droplets, making sounds of crisp percussion, just like bells blowing in the wind.

Garen squinted his eyes when a glaring white light exploded right before his eyes.

“You fell for it! Hahaha!!” the shining white Mech moved its body, passing like a phantom around him, and stabbed a knife against Garen’s vest from behind.

The stab happened silently, as well as the shining white light; not even the slightest sound could be heard.

Usually, Pilots would not even know where the opponent attacked from.

However, Garen was different; he instantly felt the ambush behind him. Just when he was about to whip out his blade to block the attack, his engine was overloaded so he could not make it on time.

When the engine load got too much, the body’s reflex would be slowed down by a large scale.

“Boom!”

He growled.

An ice-blue force of air crashed against him, spreading outwards as he stood at the center.

Layers of frost covered the once withered meadow almost immediately, even the insects that were still crawling around were frozen into ice.

A large amount of frost started spreading from the surface of Garen’s body and soon covered the entire body.

The blade attacking from behind was affected by the ice-blue radiation and abruptly slowed. Right when the tip of the blade came into contact with Garen’s Mech, there was a vicious tremble.

“Changing Blade!” this man was still calm and collected. Facing the trembling tip of the ice-blue blade, it was as if a lot of blades had appeared at the same time. All of a sudden, what seemed to be a straight raid in the first place instantly became a prick on the ramp, stabbing Garen’s Mech in the back of its head.

“What an expert!!” Garen’s heart skipped a beat. Generally, ordinary people, under such encounters, would only manage to change moves once in that instance.

However, it was different for stronger experts who would be able to respond by changing their moves twice. Not only was it just a matter of reflex, the consciousness involved in decision making played a big part too. Even a little hesitation would not reach this level when it came to transforming moves.

Although it just seemed as if it was just one more transformation move, the requirements for the mind and speed of response were extremely harsh.

For those able to transform thrice in just an instant, they would already be nearing the realm of King of the Century.

Being able to transform moves four times in an instant, Garen’s martial arts realm has already gone beyond the realm of the King of the Century. To be able to transform his moves four times after making a move was already terrifying in the eyes of ordinary people, but he was still unsatisfied. He was still in pursuit of a higher realm.

After coming to this world, he had met a lot of expert masters but fighting-wise, he had yet met one who had impressed him.

The man in front was, in fact, the first true combat master who had actually swayed him so far, unlike other pilots who merely relied on their Willpower.

“Nice move!”

Seeing the opponent’s move transform once again, Garen’s heart jerked.

His body shifted to the left when the blade in his hand pierced right beneath his armpit.

Among the sounds of sneering, the blade accurately blocked the ambush from behind. Both blades made contact, producing a loud bang.

Under the strong impact, both blades bent, cracked and broke. Both tips of the blades shot around with a chi-chi sound, unexpectedly shooting towards Garen and both Shining Mechs.

As the blade whooshed by, both Shining Mechs split apart. Garen’s body remained smooth whereas the opponent’s body was clearly stabbed by half of a blade.

“Brilliant!” the Shining Mech exclaimed in awe. “It’s such a shame. You’re such a good fighter, but you’re going to die here in this wasteland.”

Judging by his tone, it was not the same young man anymore but an odd young man’s.

“Who are you people?” though Garen had his own speculations, he could not resist the urge to ask them directly.

“There’s nothing to hide, we’re just people hired by Fila. Kid, you offended plenty of people in this city whom you shouldn’t have. Just blame your bad luck,” the Shining Mech that had made the first move previously took a step back while the other one, who had been sitting back and watching, took a step front. Both Mechs stood side by side, emitting a vague white light.

“I’m sorry, kid,” the Shining Mech that was about to make a move started laughing, “Your combat level is strong indeed, but do you actually think you can handle the both of us at once?”

As the last syllable came out, both Mechs roared up and rushed towards Garen. Two honed leg blades, side by side, slashed diagonally across Garen’s waist in an ‘X’ shape, the white blades aiming to cut Garen’s Mech in half at his waist.

The sharp piercing sound of the blades resembled a shrill whistle, close enough to pierce through one’s eardrums.

Strangely, when the two Mechs moved at the same time, they gave off an extremely tacit understanding, as if both Mechs were of the same person, like images reflected by a mirror.

“Twins?!” Garen went silent. After all, his body was slowing down due to the tremendous load. Looking at the incoming assault from the front, he fiercely lifted the Mech and kicked upwards.

Dodging the strikes from both Mechs right on time, he kicked one of the Shining Mechs.

Clang clang! At the crisp sound of impact, both Shining Mechs darted downwards at the same time at the same speed. The move made just now turned out to be just a decoy.

As the leg blades intersected, Garen twisted his body to avoid the frontal edge, then landed a kick on the side of the tool.

With a wham, the three separated. Garen flipped over once more but the right half of his body was marked by a clear scar already.

Seated in the body, Garen’s eyebrows were knitted tightly against each other. He knew he did react but because of the overload burden on the body’s engine, he had been delayed for a moment. Stopping briefly in the middle of combat against an expert master would actually cause him his life.

In addition to the gap between the two Shining Mechs, the other side of the body seemed to be able to react quicker than him. It was all thanks to his martial arts realm being stronger than his opponent; it gave him the opportunity to transform once more and escape on time, or else he would have probably been dead by now.

“It seems like I have to leave the Knowledge ore here…” Garen knew deep in his mind that if he continued dragging the ore around, he might actually be unable to escape because the load on his body would reduce at least half of his power.

If his body was just a little lighter, he would be slightly more at ease to deal with these two Mechs.

On the other hand, the Frost Radiation did not seem to affect the enemy. The anarchy caused by Cold Chaos was not hundred percent effective, but there is a certain probability of an onset. Needless to say, this moment was certainly a no-show.

“One more time!!”

Both Level Five Shining Mechs rushed forward once again as a flash of white moon appeared and a drop of white liquid dripped down its edge. Without Garen’s offense this time around, the white liquid exploded into a wheel of white light, nearly blinding Garen’s sight.

Hidden within the white light, two blades whirled towards Garen.

In the cabin, Garen tracked backward lightly. Even if his eyes were temporarily blinded, dodging an attack was still extremely easy.

But then, a click sound emerged from the engine and the entire Mech moved.

Chi chi!!

Two marks appeared on Garen’s body once more.

Garen’s face darkened as the Mech’s engine once again delayed his reflexes.

“Black Wind!!”

He extended both his arms as a trace of black air blew out from his arms. Suddenly, with just an action and a crooked aim, the large whiff of Black Wind immediately rushed towards the two Mechs, but surprisingly, it failed to hurt either one of them.

The two Shining Mechs were startled and once they realized that the Black Wind had missed them, they let out a breath of relief.

“It seems that you have yet to master this skill!!”

Using Black Wind one more time, Garen felt uneasy. An uncomfortable feeling started to spread from his arms and his skin started to hurt severely. He knew that this was the aftermath of overusing the Black Wind as this was a highly destructive skill. He had tried it once at Professor Van Doe’s and he could not even use it several times back then. His limit was at least once every two hours as he needed the two hours to recover from just one shot. However, this was the very first time he was able to use it twice continuously in such a short amount of time and clearly, something was wrong.

An excruciating pain shot through both his arms.

Just then, two fleeing figures loomed on the prairie behind the trio. It was Anda and the dragon-headed Mech.

“Garen ~~~~” Anda started shouted from far away, a look of sorrow written all over his face.

Garen turned back and glanced swiftly.

There was no any other way anymore. It was time to let loose of the load, get rid of these two and leave straight away!

His intuition told him that the dragon-headed Mech would be far more dangerous and a bigger threat than the two Mechs in front of him. Even his Willpower was warning him already.

He snorted coldly. The isolated cabin behind his body suddenly released a bunch of Mastery Energy Ores, at least a quarter of the entire load!

His Mech instantly recovered it’s engine power from the red negative level back to its normal level. On the other hand, the Mastery Energy Ores released outside started melting immediately. Observed by the naked eye, the ores melted into a pool of silver-metal liquid then began to evaporate rapidly.

This could have made billions of fortune…

Even Garen could feel his heart aching.

However, under the reduced weight, merely two Level Five Pilots who have yet reached the New-Moon Level could still be easily dealt with within three moves as there was no more burden and the body could accelerate under such circumstances.

Garen’s eyes narrowed as the blade started vibrating slowly. The shock technique used by expert warriors was used, causing the blade formed to be as lethal as an electric chainsaw.

“Actually!!?? Nevermind, I don’t want to play anymore! Scram!”

Contrary to what he expected, both Shining Mechs in front of him glanced at the two figures chasing up behind and straight away turned and ran without a word!

Two rays of white flames were ejected from the rear of the body as the Shining Mechs darted towards the distance.

What a big loss… !

Garen turned around and stared at the pool of melted Knowledge ores, his heart hurting a little already. A quarter of the ores gone all of a sudden, that could have been thousands of dollars already! A market value of tens of millions, that was the extent of billions of dollars.

But now was not the time to be bitter.

Raising his Mech’s engine. Garen blasted full power without a word and flew towards the other direction.

What he did not know was the two Shining Mechs were actually the Ice Dragon’s men and not sent by Fila. Even Ice Dragon did not have the rights to assign such masters like them for such quests. In fact, they had just wanted to come out and have fun. But if the Ice Dragon was to find out that the Mechs had left their assigned positions just to come out and play, they would have gotten into deep trouble. That was why the mere sight of Ice Dragon had been enough to chase them away.

Just like the Ice Dragon, his elite Pilots were also highly skilled masters and obsessed with all sorts of violent combat. When they fought, life and death were not an issue to them as they view such combat as merely a game. This was why their combat skills were able to be trained to an extent that was recognized by the powerful Garen.

Three Mechs arranged themselves in a line, one chasing after the other, constantly flying over the prairie.

Chapter 906: Blocked 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As the afternoon passed, the sky dimmed and the sun glowed upon the grassland, dyeing everything in golden red.

At night, the lights on three Mechs shook like they were high-speed floating cars.

In the morning, a flock of mutated birds flew across the sky.

Anda feebly turned around and took a glance; that dragon-headed humanoid Mech was still there.

“…This guy… won’t get tired?”

“Fun! Hahahaha…!” Ice Dragon’s refreshed laughter came from the back. “It’s been a long time since I last had such a marathon exercise, Hahahaha!!! One two one! One two one! One two one…”

This guy even started yelling cadence calls.

“My God!” Anda slapped his forehead. “This guy is a psycho! I was running a one-night marathon with a psychopath all along?”

Suddenly, Ice Dragon seemed to have received some sort of message while sitting in his cockpit. His face that had been all smiles a moment ago suddenly frowned.

“What is this! What a bummer! Even though I was able to meet with such a fun guy,” he curled his lips and touched his chin.

“I say, Fourth, you’re someone who’s going to break through the Seventh Non-falling Level. Is it okay to play house with a mere Level Five?”

A white-haired man at the corner of the screen said helplessly.

“How about just killing them off?” Ice Dragon touched his chin, his eyes suddenly flashed with an intent to kill.

“Forget it, you still have to go back and change to another Mech before you can do it, as for Fila’s problem, let him handle it. If he can’t even handle this kind of problem, he doesn’t have the qualification to be the Fifth. However, it’s not that Second brother likes to lecture you, but you are so emotional and you always do things based on your mood, it makes people very uncomfortable! We can’t even find you when we need you.”

“Second, this is your mistake. I, Ice Dragon, have always obeyed the arrangements of my superior. I’ve always listened to what they said,” Ice Dragon laughed.

“I said don’t call me Second[1]!” the white-haired man’s face twitched.

“Second, you have always been second, if I don’t call you Second, do I call you second younger brother?” Ice Dragon feigned a frightened expression. “Second younger brother, what happened to you!? Second younger brother!”

“I say…Fourth…,” the white-haired man closed his eyes as the veins on his forehead bulged. “I am your second elder brother! Not your second younger brother!”

“Is two bigger than four?” Ice Dragon was surprised. “My number is bigger than yours, why can’t I call you second younger brother?” suddenly his expression changed, “Un… unless you want me to call you… second elder sister?!”

Boom!

The sound of the screen bursting came from the other side.

“Don’t stop me, I’m going to kill him!! Kill him!!!” the sound of Second raging came on and off.

The screen was completely dark now.

Ice Dragon stroked his chin.

“Second, you really have a mental problem… from narcissism to transsexuality… huu…” he shuddered. “Now that I’ve realized the fact that I had lived with a pervert under the same roof; that was dangerous!”

Suddenly, his expression changed.

“Unless the reason that the First made him the Second is… because…he doesn’t have ‘Second’!!?? [2]”

His expression changed rapidly.

“It’s over, it’s over, it’s over!! Living together for so many years, has my chastity been long gone??”

This guy was totally a psycho, talking to himself. He completely did not notice that although the screen had turned dark, sounds could still be transmitted.

“F***!! Ice Dragon, if you dare to come back, I’m going to f****** kill you!!!” Second, on the other side, had totally blown his top. The surrounding people were trying to calm him.

“Be honest, Second! Have you ever done anything to my chastity! Be honest!” Ice Dragon’s expression had turned gloomy.

Boom!

The screen had totally turned black and no sound came out again.

“Sure enough… silence means that you admit it!” Ice Dragon shivered. “I didn’t think that I’d recognize your true nature now! Second, you truly are a pervert!” he shouted to the sky.

“I was only five years old at that time! Five years old!!! Yet you had the heart to do this!!”

Two lines of tears flowed out from his eyes.

“Er… sir, you seemed to have been seven years old when you joined the organization…” the voice of his subordinate inside the headset could not help but remind him.

“Er… seven years old? Did I remember it wrong?” Ice Dragon wiped away his tears. With doubt in his eyes, he seemed to have finally recalled something and rubbed his temples. “A lot of people said that my brain has problems, does my brain really have problems?”

“How could it be!? Sir, your brain is number one in the world, how could there be a problem, anyone can remember things wrongly! You have nothing to worry about!” the subordinate quickly comforted him.

“Really?” Ice Dragon stroked his chin. Looking at the two people running in front, he suddenly felt down-hearted.

“Forget it forget it, all of you go back, I have to properly check the problem concerning my chastity. These two should be solved by Fila, that brat, himself.”

“Yes, sir.”

Ice Dragon did not say another word. He turned around and ran, looking as though he was a murderer that was escaping.

***************

Hu…hu…hu…

Anda and Garen were breathing heavily.

Let alone Anda who was tired like hell, even Garen, who possessed extraordinary physique, was tired. They had endured a long-distance marathon that, while consuming Willpower to support the Mech to escape, had lasted nearly two days one night. Even if his recovery was astounding, his mind was exhausted.

It was evening again and two Mechs was lying down on the grass, disregarding any image they had. The two people in the cockpit completely relaxed their bodies to recover themselves rapidly.

“That madman is finally gone!” Anda was very weak now. With severe thirst and hunger, on top of exhaustion of his Willpower and body, he had two dark circles under his eyes now. He had lost weight and looked like a skeleton now.

Garen was still the same except that his body and Willpower were exhausted.

“That guy is probably an expert of Full-Moon Level, we were lucky to be able to escape,” he took deep breaths and quickly exhaled in a rhythmic way.

“What do we do now?” Anda had decided to follow Garen all the way.

“What to do? We fly straight to Flying Batoid City,” Garen calmly got up from the ground. “Let me give you a suggestion. That dragon-headed Mech was actually playing around with you. The next time you see him, escape right away.”

Anda gave a wry smile and also struggled to stand up.

The two of them stood up and looked far away at the sky where two white spots appeared. Astounding killing intent came out from the white spots.

One of them was Windling’s Mech that was hunting Anda. With her arms crossed and her Mech straight, she was rushing towards this side.

The other one was a Mech as white as a jade that did not conceal the fluctuation on its body, which exceeded Level Five. Although it exceeded Level Five, it had yet to reach Inherited Level but was somewhere in between.

Looking closely, they could see that this Shining Mech had been specially modified. Although it was not an Exclusive Mech, it was not a simple Shining Mech either.

“Windling, you dare to collude with the White Light’s terrorist organization!” Anda saw them and roared while trying to suppress the tremble in his heart.

“Collusion?” Windling sneered. “After killing you guys, no one will know about this relationship right?”

“It’s for real this time,” Garen whispered. He had abandoned one-fourth of the Mastery Energy Ores. It would not greatly affect the Mech’s performance now which was about 80% of its total strength. It was just that there was no way to use the Black Wind now. Originally, he was supposed to wait for one hour for his body to recover, but due to his continuous usage previously, both his arms were now injured. He estimated that before he recovered, there was no way for him to use Black Wind.

This kind of injuries on his body had been recovered by Garen using the Potential points once. It had been effective and the wound had closed up, but the strange thing was that he still could not use Black Wind. He did not know what other place had been injured that even Potential points could not completely repair.

Black Wind was not available, thus he could only use the ordinary Ten Thousand True Technique to go against opponents. If they had some strong special skills, then it was going to be tough for them.

Although the Ten Thousand True Technique was very useful for Mechs, when it encountered some strange special skills or those resonance skills, the outcome would be hard to predict. There were a lot of special skills and resonance skills in this world that were totally unreasonable and strong to an unbelievable extent.

For combat techniques like Crouched Eagle Talon, it was sufficient when facing common Mech pilots, but to deal with opponents such as those in front of them, they would just die faster.

Perhaps Professor Van Doe had some matching battle skills but for whatever reasons, he did not give them out. Garen could only use his own set first.

“Anda, if you don’t want to die then throw away part of the Mastery Energy Ore,” Garen directly send a message over.

“I’ve long thrown them away…,” Anda gave a wry smile. “Or else I would’ve been caught by that Madman.”

“…How much did you throw away?”

“Half of them…”

Both of them had treasures on them. If they just went all out and clashed with them, they were both reluctant so they had to think of a way to escape.

“Do you have any idea?” Garen saw that the other parties were approaching and asked. His heart had also grown tense. His intuition told him that the two in front of them were not like the ones playing around. The two in front of them were here to kill them!

“What Level can you handle? That Windling is a New Moon Level Five.”

“I don’t know, but I should barely get by,” Garen had seen the power of resonance skills, having tested in the inner courtyard. When he had the nameless Level Five Willpower, he had been able to cope and delay for a while. Now that he was Level Five in Crouched Eagle Talon, he reckoned that he could barely get a draw at most.

“The other one is also New Moon Level Five. It’s getting troublesome now,” Anda gave a bitter smile. “If we really cannot do it, then let’s just throw away the Mastery Energy Ore and escape.”

The problem now was that the other side was more powerful than them, and they themselves were weighed down by the Mastery Energy Ores causing their combat capabilities to diminish. If they really fought, there was no way to keep the Mastery Energy Ores safe. There was no use in having money if they lost their lives trying to secure it.

Of course, using the ore as bait to lure and delay the other party in order to escape was no problem. However, this meant that the dangers they went through these days were all in vain and they gained nothing.

The problem now was that they would have to throw away the ores to keep their lives, and keeping the ores meant throwing away their lives.

Garen did not have the confidence to fight such strong opponents under the condition that his Mech could not perform fully. However, he had decided that once the fight broke out, he would immediately drop all the ores and lure them to pick them up while he escaped.

Compared to his life, materialistic gains were something that he could get again. However, throwing away so many Mastery Energy Ores, the progress to building his own Exclusive Mech would return to zero. He would have to search for sufficient resources again and after reaching Energy Machinist Level One, and he also needed a large number of resources to build his Biochemical Pool and test lab. The Energy Machinist was an occupation that burnt a lot of money. He did not know how long it would take to build a suitable Biochemical Station even if he saved up his millions of Units income every month.

Chapter 907: Deadpit 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Blackboard Academy

A few young ladies dressed in yellow with metallic bracelets on their wrists were standing in front of the central classroom building.

It may be hustling and bustling, but regardless, whoever who passed by would stole a glance at the ladies, but not daring to look straight at them. Not because of their beauty, but because they exuded a presence so strong that made people uncomfortable and flinch, yet somehow would not dare to look straight at them.

“Rumors had it that five elites had recently emerged from the Blackboard Academy. I wonder if we will be able to meet them officially during this trip.” One girl in yellow dress said while toying with her curly hair.

“Apart from the Little Three Marshals and One Star, there’s nothing else to explore in the Blackboard Academy right?” Another girl asked.

“Our Zero Gun elder sister will deal with Black Star Diofie but from the way I see it, other than Diofie, the rest are all losers. We, as one of the Nine Phoenix, have already reached the outer court but no one is here to welcome us.”

“That’s right, the Blackboard Academy’s people is really proud that they don’t give Nine Phoenix face. They knew we sneaked in, but did not even bother and even pretended to not know about it. Why don’t Elder Sister directly challenge the inner courtyard training tower?”

The few girls kept chatting but a girl standing in the middle amongst them kept her face straight and cold. She had short eyebrows, slanted high on both sides above her eyes.

She kept looking at her wrist watch and seemed to be searching for information from it.

A moment later, she looked up and said quietly.

“Let’s not wait any longer. No one is going to greet us when we are the ones sneaking in. Other than the Little Three Marshals and One Star, are there any other people who are that good?”

“There is, Elder Sister. The three big organizations here have some elites. They even made a ranking so the people up there should be quite good. They should conform to the standards of our objectives.”

Just as she finished her sentence, several people wearing student uniforms came down. They looked grim and dark.

The few girls also suddenly found out that without them realizing, they had been surrounded by the outer court students who gathered around as if to watch a show. The students surrounding them even had a kind of three layers by three layers formation.

The students of Blackboard Academy were not fools. These people had stood for so long in front of the general classroom building and they did not looked like they were here to tour the Academy, albeit sometimes they do get visitors who do just that.

Those who were observant noted the uniforms the girls were wearing. The unique uniforms belonged to the Maria Region, and could only be found from the true elite of Maria Academy. This was the real reason that more and more people were gathering to see what was happening.

Why were the Maria Region’s people here? The Maria Academy and the Blackboard Academy never got along with each other.

More and more people were gathering, and the sound of whispers grew louder. Most of the crowd were there to see what was going to happen; whereas some people went off to inform the other elites as it seemed like these girls were here to cause trouble.

“Ladies, who is Rapid Gun Leanna from the Nine Phoenix?” The young man in front asked.

He had a scar on his nose that originated from a burn, adding on as a little flaw to his good looking features. The moment he opened his mouth, he was asking for the leader of the party straight away.

One girl stepped forward and replied in a polite tone.

“The reason we came here this time was due to the rumor that the Blackboard Academy recently had talented students which include Red-Eyed Medero whose name had spread wide and far. Elder sister Leanna coincidentally passed by this region and wanted to come and see how excellent the students here are.”

As soon as she finished speaking, sounds of booing immediately broke out among the surrounding crowd.

“Rapid Gun Leanna? We have never heard of her? You want to compare with our Sir Medero, you have to see how much you’re worth!” Someone in the crowd sneered out loud.

“That’s right! How random for a ‘rapid gun’ to just walk in and challenge our Sir Medero anytime? When will he have any time to rest?”

“Sir Medero is not someone a random mob can challenge!”

The crowd suddenly got into a commotion.

Leanna raised her eyebrows slightly and gave a cold smile.

“You all have a point. If that’s the case, then I will just casually challenge an inner court elite other than Medero. Let me see if there is someone worth looking for from Blackboard Academy.”

She stepped forward.

“I will stand here and accept any challenge. If there is anyone who can win against me, I will give away Silverlake Alloy on the spot, how about it?”

Silverlake Alloy!!

This was a material that was a lot more precious than the engine materials like Blood Silver. There’s a high price for it but there are no sales as not everybody would be able afford it as one Silverlake Alloy at its lowest standard purity would be priced at 2.5 billion for just a mere one kilogram!

The crowd fell into a dead silent.

Even if the Academy is a place where all rich children from the Blackboard Region gathered, it is still shocking to know and face somebody who could just throw out a few billions just like that as part of a bet.

A group of guys who were walking past the crowd also heard Leanna’s proclamation. The leading guy in blonde hair had a sudden thought in mind and instead of heading to the dormitory, he turned around instead and strode towards the crowd.

“There is no need for Sir Medero to come out. I, Kanasien, ranked twenty-sixth will challeng you!” Greed flashed in the eyes of the blond guy. He was gathering materials to construct his own Exclusive Mech and the materials came right on time!

Leanna curled her lips.

“Alright, you’ll do. Whether it’s Willpower combat or martial arts, pick whichever you want. Of course, if you want, you can also choose resonance degrees Mech combat.” She flipped her long hair and said.

Just as her voice faded away, Kanasien’s complexion suddenly change, resonance degree??

This opponent was an elite who had at least reach the New Moon Level!

At the same time, those in the crowd who were fast to catch on also now realized something amiss.

This group of ladies led by Leanna came here not for some friendly interaction…they were either here to cause trouble or here with some other agenda!

“Let’s begin!” Leanna smiled and stepped forward, the remaining girls behind her sneered at the dumbfounded Kanasien.

*******************

Radiation Belt

Garen and Anda both looked at the two elite Mechs flying in the sky getting closer.

“Together or separate?”

Anda smiled helplessly. “Let’s separate and joined up at Flying Batoid City, any problem?”

“Alright.”

Garen did not say another word. He turned around and flew to the right side as the legs of the Mech leapt.

With a bang, black soil and grass flew around everywhere. The Mech also used this recoil force to fly and shot towards the distance.

Anda on the other side was close to the ground and gaining speed faster and faster. Soon, a trace of faint silver light appeared on the surface of the Mech. Just as this trace of light glittered, Anda’s speed suddenly increased much more.

However, inside the cockpit, Anda was enduing an intense pain. His face was flushed with veins popping out on his face as if his blood was going to explore from his body anytime.

“Chase them!!” Windling and the other pilot split up and chased after them.

Garen looked at the ground that was increasingly speeding back behind and his heart grew calmer.

After a long journey and without sufficient rest, parts of the Mech Body were now highly fatigue. Adding on to the toil was the radiation that seeped through the erosion damage which was inflicted on parts of the Body. Thus, energy consumption was higher and speed was not up to par.

Black Wind had not recovered yet and the Nameless Level Five Willpower was not there. Now he did not have the capability to confront a New Moon Level. With only the Crouched Eagle Talons, he was far from being the opponent for the people chasing close behind. He had gone for a simulation battle with a New Moon Level opponent in the training room before. Without the Mech, he could confront them and it was a tie on the battle. However, with the Mech, he was far from being a match. It was due to the resonance which provided large amount of support in the manipulation.

“Coming out this time, as long as I can keep this batch of Mastery Energy Ore and the Blood Silver, all will be worth it!” Garen calculated in his mind. He activated the rear sensor and swept through the Mech chasing behind. The opponent’s speed was faster than his and was about to catch up!

“I have to think of a solution.”

Garen narrowed his eyes and worked his brain furiously.

Suddenly, the grass in front of him appeared wet and the ground seemed to be soft.

Garen’s mind lighted up.

The Body suddenly rushed out and stomped on this area. He stepped on the area that was harder compare to others.

One second after his Mech Body passed by, the white Body behind also shot out at a high speed and stepped on the area which he had just stomped on.

Both of them were trying to preserve energy in the engine that was used for the flying and relied on running with their legs. This allowed Garen to formulate a plan.

Suddenly, Garen’s Mech Body in front seemed to twist slightly and lost a little balance. This balance, in the eyes of the powerhouses, only needed a moment to adjust back but the common pilots generally were not able to detect it.

However the white Mech behind chose this moment to increased its speed explosively.

A sinister laugh came out from inside the Mech.

“Still thinking of running! Gale Claw!!”

His Mech Body stretched out its hand and brought out greenish energy blades which formed a large green hand extending out to press upon the back of Garen’s Mech.

Garen staggered and swerved to avoid the claw in the nick of time before landing on the right side of the grass.

The white Mech laughed and stepped forward.

Chi!

Suddenly the leg of his Mech unexpectedly sank into the ground.

A quagmire!! Not good!

The white Mech was startled and suddenly a bright light flashed in front of his eyes, and a strong, black line struck down.

Wu…!!

The black line flashed and split the quagmire, hitting the white Mech on its hands which it raised up in a haste.

With a loud clanging sound, golden sparks came out from the clash between both Mechs. The sword slipped from the claws and sliced in the same direction towards the white Mech.

“What, again?!” The white Mech was not able to take action fast enough and stomped on the ground instinctively wanting to borrow the force to get out of here, but its Body was sinking deeper.

Although this guy had resonance degree and belonged to the New Moon Level, he was far from the people he met previously. His combat experience was so bad!

“Resonance skill! Poison Vine!!”

The white Mech seemed to have blew his top. He was forced by a guy with no resonance skill into this chaotic state. A roar came from the cockpit.

Garen’s complexion remain unchanged and stepped back. His legs condensed a small piece of ice on the quagmire, just enough to borrow its force.

Traces of invisible Cold Chaos Field came out and seeped into the opponent’s Mech.

There was no one else here. Even if he released Cold Chaos, no one would realized.

At that moment, a large amount of illusory twisted green vines spurted out from the white Mech’s surroundings and flew out in all direction. At the same time, his overall speed, dexterity and power had increased by at least 30%!

Noticing the change in speed, Garen quickly retracted his sword and retreated but a large amount of vines followed him closely. Each of the vines was as thick as his Body’s waist and wherever it passed by, it released a green gas which corroded the grass into black puddles. The poison was horrendously evil.

The white Mech released five large vines and more than ten small vines as though it had turned into a mutated creature. It bared its claws and let out a roar.